Welcome back
Previous two steps created capitalism
Will try and understand
Happening
UT
Deep mappings.
We have created TobyMac created mapping some hello
Ulta
Created a Halo
Well being
Also present in here for example
Give me a few important questions that could
What is
Dispatcher salary
Actually we have not done anything about dispatcherservlet to who is considering this purchaser
What does dispatcherservlet do
Who is configuring the area map
Set of questions that you would have based on whatever you have done in the
Previous two steps
And water
Industry will slowly look at all
I would want to actually start
I need this application
In something call
Debug mode
The baby can do that is by going to application. Properties
And consequence
Logging
11 only considered spring framework to art
Spring framework
Is equal to I would say
I'm sitting in logging level for August Prince Ember to debug and
6 Vista
Give me a piece. Now you'd see a lot more
Then
Because nowhere is debug logging
Spring boot is outputting a lot of stuff
Being shown in
What are the important things that you would see in here
The auto-configuration report
Consist
A lot
If you look at
The auto-configuration log
One of the important things is configuration of
Purchase
Auto-configuration
Dispatcher servlet Auto consultation match
Because it found a
Class call dispatcher servlet on D class pass
What is happening here
I did in a starter on
Spring boot
Dr.web
And spring boot starter web
Has a dependency
One spring fat NBC
The flame book
Beautiful
We get the
Dispatcher servlet class
Glasspack
Spring boot Auto configuration says
So let's go ahead and configured
Dispatcher
Nothing you'd cease on NBC
Auto-configuration
So it says okay these classes are found on the class but so we would need to configure
Configuring a basic error controller of you are attributes
The other page which we looked at earlier was divided label
Oedipus
This was the thing which was generating that editor
Use Somebody
All these consecration is getting fired
Because of something called
Spring boot
Auto configuration spring boot looks at Aldi classes all the Jazz which are available on the class but
It tries to Auto configure different things
Dispatcher servlet in addition to whatever we have discussed
The other things which are
Message converters
We had the
And I took
DHCP message converters were responsible for doing that
So what is happening is something called Jackson to object mapper
Actually does the conversion from
Jason
Beans to Jason who's going to dispatch service finger.
Converted to Jason it's also because of spring water consecration because the message converters and the jack
Jackson beans are getting
Chili's
Who's confident again spring boot Auto config
Create a default error page for us
If you look at the log you see something like this
What is happening here is
Dispatcher servlet is handling
All the requested this is the truth of the Bible
Flight attendant
I know you type a URL into the browser whenever I type hello world in into the browser
What would happen if
The request would go to dispatcherservlet
Dispatcher servlet would be divine which would be handling that
This is falling apart n
Friends
Controller
Special abilities different controller for spring web MVC framework
Dispatcher servlet
Dispatcher servlet knows all the different mapping switch at present in the app
Application to helloworld get method
Is map to this method
Dispensers of lymph nodes that hello world Bean
2D specific method
So once it gets the request
It determines which is the right controller to execute that request
So it looks
Add d u r a n d
Request method
Dispensers of lettuce
Okay there's a Gupta quest to high-level Bean which is the right controller that would be able to execute it for me
He pretty fine this specific method that high-level controller. High-level Dien
Is this right one to execute it would execute that so it would make sure that this matter is
Executed and this being is return back
Once the venous return back
Then dispatcherservlet looks at how do I send a response back I have a bean now
How do I send message back
Is something called response body annotation
One of the important annotations which is present in rest controller
Response body
What would happen
Controller
Is this response from that
Would be mad
Bite a message converter
Into some other format
So here
The message converter which is going to be used as Jax
Dispatcher servlet would say okay
Buddha Jackson conversion Judah conversion to Jason
It would actually convert LOL Bean
And since this
Halo bulb in request goes to dispatcherservlet dispatcherservlet find the Halliwell controller the specific method
Call Sid
Lydia Walking Dead
String vest
Dispatcher servlet
Please
Will further discuss about dispatch
When we talk about other things
Like
We tried to take a quick look
Adaville behind this
Dispatcher servlet
How it controls the entire floor
What's up
We looked at some of the things to check configured by default
By Spring boot autoconf
If a few of these things are not really clear view
Not a problem at all
Will discuss about this
A lot more indecency