In this video
You'd start with an important concept
Call
What is
What is the best all about
Transfer
Just going by Roy
If you remember dry cleaning is the guy also
HTTP protocol
Sleeping apart
Bad.
They would want to make best
What is it
Take a quick overview let's go to Google
I want to search for what is a web service
The browser comes back with the response
I can choose
One of these days
Cricket and I can choose any of the link such a pleasant
Hear ASL
This is how we
Things which were happening in the background please how was simple infraction
Happens within the browser and any of
Service of the websites you are visiting
Example Google
What happens is
Request is being sent
Today
Website server
And the website to respond back with a response
Important thing that you need to talk about
What is
Format of this request
Respond
Request and response
Define
Hypertext
Transfer protocol
In a URL
In the browser
Lipsense
Agate request
The server response back
With a history
ATP response
Containing the HTML
Andy serwer is sending back
Response
HDPE response
Containing the HTML
The browser
Looks like that response
Dixie HTML
And this place it on this
Listen to the form I'm filling up with a list of them
Details and submit button
Emboss conductive
Scenarios
Typically
Via creating a post request
HDPE Define
Along with the response
Saudi body
Addition
Request header
Andy requestbody
HDPE also defines
Something called
Request
Methods
You can indicate
What chain you are doing
Request methods
Get I'm trying to get the D
Dates of Summer
I'm trying to
Create something
I'm trying to update
HTTP response on the other hand will also include
HTTP response
Data School
Was it successful
What is not found 404
And things like that
Troy Fielding set
Why do we need to reinvent the wheel
Make
Yusuf hdb
To develop our web services as well
And that's weird
The concept of restful web services
Restful web services
Tri
Define services
Choosing the different concepts that are already present
Most important apps
Destruction
Andreas
Something called
Anything
That you'd want
Exposed to the outside world
Who You Are
Education did users
Who is using it
What are the two deuce
Also can be a resource a specific to do is a resource list of Truth is also a research
We are always thinking about
Resources
What are the resources in my app
Application how to do a user a list of to do what we do is we would assign a URI
Resource
For example
DUI rates
The resource
Panda
Is/user
You are right
Flash user manga
Do you want to eat
First Resource that ranga has
You are stronger
Resort
Wrist
Does not worry about
Is it HTML
Is it Jason
That does not really matter
The most important thing
Is it fact that you define your resource
And perform the actions on the results
Just like we discussed earlier if I want to create a resource
I would do a post
2 / users if I wanted to eat something
You would delete
2 / user / 1
Flash users get / user / 1
Important thing about rest
Is the fat
You have to
Think in terms of resources
Location that you would want to expose
Other applications
Second thing
If you want to do any operations on the resource
You have to use
Develops
Picture quality specified by
And things like that dress
We don't really have any restriction on the data exchange format
Why Jason is very popular race does not worry whether you using Json XML or whatever format
I want to use
Important thing is transport is always
Http
Left is completely built on top of it
There's no standard service definition which is attached
That can be a drawback in some scenarios because when a client wants to consume a service
Request format and response format to a service definition v w a d l
Vacation
Definition language Bible is one of the forms in which you can specify your dress. Services
Swaggin swaggin is gaining a lot of popularity
Andy would you Swagger in this course
How do you perform actions on them
Making best
She was off