Hi there
Very dry and
What is
Avatar
Let's consider a simple definition of a verb
A service
Which is delivered over the web
Is that a complete definition
Think about it so if I
You might be using
Adorable applique
Facebook
Twitter
Your shopping app
Ride variety of Apple
All of them web services
It's considered to do application that I have
This application
Helps you to login logout
Time in Egypt
You can add new Tuesday
And also update
Simple web application
To build using Java
And spring MVC
Is it a web service
What's considered a situation
A friend of mine he's building a social application
Lips
Something like that
Facebook writer he wants to add the features to manage
Toulouse
Into his application
He wants to be used some of the functionality from art to do application which
Really be able to use the application
As it is
Application as we have built it
HTML is a format which is design
Put rendering data on the screen on the browser
HTML support
Like I want my manusia I would want
This data I would want this buttons on my
I can use HTML to design. Kinda
18 minutes. Lilian format which is designed for application to apply
Vacation Inn
My friend does not want to give up so easy
He says okay yeah I'll put that you're delivering in
Stop consumable by map
What are the other options that represent he comes to me and tells me
Haven't you drill design your application very well
Your application is really having
Well defined as you have
You have a business layer and the data layer
Give me reviews
Do stuff from your business where you are
I cannot use it
Can I see use your business logic
It comes to me and says okay can I
Create a jar
And we use that stuff
That's a good option right think about it he wants to create a jar out of the business logic
Can he use it as it is
What is the data layer need
The data layer really needs a database right
Needs a database
Talk to what my friend needs to do now is to
Install a database and also
There will be other dependencies
So he would need to make sure that all of the dependency societies
Think about when does a change in the business logic select
I am updating my to do application to have some new business logic will he automatically get it
I'll need to actually create a jar
And provide him a new version of the jar
So that he can get the new version of the business logic
We cannot consume
Got a lot of problems associated with
Getting a job and trying to reuse
52 application is able to provide output in a format that other application
Patients are able to understand then
Little problem that's where
Concept of absolute
What we're looking at right now
Where is the w3c that's
Turn off of that
It says
Support
Interoperable
Machine-to-machine interaction
Over a network
The three key words are interoperable
Machine-to-machine infraction
First thing is
Web services are designed
Application to application interaction
My to-do application is not a web service because it's not design for application to application interaction right
It's only designed for a human interact
If another application wants to talk to it
Little application has not ready yet
Should be
Interoperable
Any other kind of application should be able to
Talk to my application
It can be application is installed on dotnet application which is installed on Java
And application C may have been built using pH
They should be able to talk
To my to do service that's when my to-do application will become of absolutely
And the last one is
It should I love communication or network you were talking about this jar
Dejar is installed locally communication what happened
Within the boundaries of deceased
The communication will not happen over the knee
Indexing are you
This is not really a web service
Friend application to be a vet service
It should allow communication over a network
Are there application should be able to talk to it the applications Q2 have been deployed anywhere they might have been dipped
Floyd on the same system on a different system or somewhere on the internet
They should be allowed to talk to my application
Only then
What we have done
In this video
Try to understand
The most
Important things that affect service should support
We'll learn that website we should support application to application in traction it should be in
Operable
And it should I love communication or dinner
In the next video
Relocated
How to build
Web services light