Individualistic
Did you turn hard coded string bag
Get request
Do this you are right to this method which was threatening a simple strain
You would actually create an object
For hello world beans and
Turn that back and see what would happen
One of the things you need to understand its effect there's a lot of things that are happening in the background
Butte
Springboard to create the project
Through the spring boot starter project using frame looks like spring spring MVC and a lot of other things
So there is a lot of magic which is happening in the background
Before we get there
Food focus on getting a ticket request
Copy this
Method
Compilation errors let's not worry about it right now what I want to do is to create a get method to
Hello
World
This time
I want to create a beam
Return
8 back
Simple string are going to create a bean
And Brittany
Do you want the map
LOL Bean boots
Can you map indicate mapping request
How about interpreting a string do you want to return a bean bag how do we do that lets
Quickly
So if you want to do Hello World bean and
Make the change in the method name Nerf
UT the DNA testing companies
But instead
Creating hello world what I would need
Want to do is to create hello
One more thing I want to do is to make sure that this matter is between the hello world
Two interesting we won't return LOL
Halloween is not really there so let's go ahead and create that first
Class LL Bean
Heloise Bean
I think the default in Click finish
And
How do I want to create
If your teeth did a constrictor
Visiting here so let's go into a control one
And create Constructor hello world
I want to
Create
Hello with a messy
What I want to do is
This
Message
Is equal to
I'll get out of the compilation
Pest Control one and I'm going to create a message
We have a Halloween accepting that in deconstructed and sending it to itself
Create a
Gator
Quickly
Salicylic acid
Okay
The easiest way to do that is right click
You can go and select
Tinder
Tight
Obviously I would also want to generate
Trintellix gender to sing as well
Static source
Soviet rating of very simple peanut nothing complex in here so just stating a simple bean
Enough LOL control bootcamp
So what we have done until now
Very simple language
Define
Which exit send message
Deer activity things back in D
Control method let's start the application up
Godavari hello world
Dootsie
Bad Daddy's in address
This is one of the important things that you need to understand that lead is not really
Easier to debug and that's the reason why I listed this first step
Hellowell Bean does not
Have a good day
If you don't create a greater than the automatic conversion will not work so let's go ahead and create
Does it
Source
Select
Beautiful that
Enough Beauty
That Decatur is present in here
It's Quickly reset the application
And not if you launch the LOL Bean
Cutesy a Json message back you'd see that message
Hello world
Vehicle
You are right
Hello Venus sleeping return with
Hello hello
If you look at the structure it's actually reflecting
This structure in here Surrey
District attorney message
And hello world
The name of the film theorists message
So that's exactly what this year
Pictures of being set
2D
Message is being
Presented as its value
This coming back
Tucson
Adding one more simple method this is at listening a bean bag
Novi everything a bean bag
This being is being automatically converted into Json and return back
The first two steps
What a really simple driver
Just created couple of simple method
You look mixed
Will understand what's happening in the background
Altice two steps
How is
Dirac was being handled
Who is handling the request
And also
How's the Hollywood bean contest getting translated to Json