Welcome back
Dude want to create a simple controller
This is like your hello world restful web service
I can't really call this a restful web service
It just call it a service which concern takes
I'm going to create a new class
And I would want to create a new class I would want to call this
Hello world
Controller
Big finish
What you want to do in this hell over controller is I want to create a method
And I would want this method
Cookie 10
Hello world
Whenever we create a rest service Munich Define
Two things right when is
Method
I would want to use get method
And
I want to use
IQR
What do you want I do want to use I want to use that you are right
Hello what
Somebody goes into their browser
And since
Get request to Splash in the world
I want to send him some text
That's basically all that I would want to do
In this
What are the first things that you need to do
Eastern spring that disease a controller
Could use a controller
In the sense that this would be handling HD.
To dispense thing that is a controller
And next
You need to create a method
Limited
Would be public
It's dripping a string LOL so I'll call it
String
And let's call it
Hello world
What should this method do
Sympathy would want to return the string back
So I would you do that
Return
Do this method map
Agate
SeaQuest
Wri
Hello world
Better things now we have to do when it's
Call Lisa controller so we need to say this is a control
And then we would need to map a get you a Leo / hello world to this
How do we do that that's focus on the control of first
Cute want to tell spring MVC that this is going to handle stress
Request
How do we do that
The baby would do that is by using something called
Controller
The rest
Controller becomes
A controller which can handle
Rest
Request
The next thing is to
Create a mapping
But this method I would want to map a get
Request
Do this
You are right
Why don't the base of doing that is to creator
Request
Map
The annotation Access Control one and imported it in
And here
I can Define
What is the request method
Request method that we want to use
He's request method.
We want to use is get
And the soiree
How do we map the UI right
That's by using this
Is equal to
Hello
That's it
As simple as
Does Netflix
8080 /
Hello world
Cutesy
Displayed on the
Browser
What are you done
Put up very simple animation address controller
And then we map
Get request to this URL
Do this method and what it was
Which is returned by this particular
Method
It's displayed on the browser
We can improve this further instruction
Using at requestmapping
Is an annotated annotation called gate mapping
So I can take it
Mapping
Is equal to hello
Similar to this
Foot mapping and other mapping Zachary would use in the subsequent steps
I like the ad
Get mapping annotation because it's quite short
And it's pretty easy to eat a sweater mapping a get request
To hello world
Isn't that
A cool thing
Imports
Control shifter
And let's be stopped
About King
In this brief step
Creative assembly
Helloworld request