The last couple of videos
Introduced
To devote
And the how of
And this would you like to buy some of the
Key terminology
Request
Restaurants
Message exchange form
Look at what is a service provider what is a service
Definition
What is tram
Put request and response
Request is the input to a web service and response is the output from a web service
Message exchange format
Format of the request
And the rest
Are we using XML
Are we using Json
What is the format of the request and response
That's basically the message
Exchange
Fort Myers
Key terminology is
Service provider
Service cat
Application wants to consume a service
From the web service which is present
The vet service here is called a service
Provider
Service provider is the one
Who was
Dbap Solis
Stubby's consumer
Is the one which is
Consuming the web service application in this example
He's a consumer of the web service
In this example
The job application Department application application
Little bit
Service provider
The guy who's providing the service
Who is using the service
The next important terminology
Service
Definition
Descendants definition is
The contract between the service provider and the service consumers
Disservice definition Define
What is the format of the request and response XML or Json
What is the structural Theory
Quest
What is the structure of the response
And Viet easy service available.
These service consumer
Call
The service which is exposed by the service provider
The other key terminology
Transport
Define
How a service is
Call
Ac service
Pushed over internet
Easy service exposed
Order queue
2 popular for metal
HTTP and
HDPE is basically
Just like your type of URL in the browser in a similar way application
Call Deb cell
The other format is mq is to use
Communication over
The service request would place a message in the queue
The service provider would be listening on the Q
And as soon as this request on the Q
It would take the request
Do the processing of it
Create a response
And put it back in the queue
And the service requested would get the response
Transport which is used
Is mqa does not necessarily be websphere mq it can be any of the other accusers
But the fact is the communication happens over Q
Over the transport
Mq
Alaska terminal
Or whether it's exposed or Divide 13
Idea behind this
Video
Provide
Quick overview
All key terminology which is associated with web server
Discussed in the early videos
We wanted to make sure that there is no ambiguity
An understanding of these
Key terminology
Because we would be using this terminology
During the next
I'm in the next video