Video de vort
Related to web services
Redefine
What is a web service
Do a web service
Need to support an application to application
It should be platform
Independent
In this world you will shift our attention
To have
Answer some of the important have questions
Related to web service
Fitstar cunyfirst
How does data
Change between app
Application
I have an application which is consuming of episode
How does the data Exchange
Application
Just consuming a web service
Lit City web services
It's related to a to-do app
Education
Offers a list of
Tutus
The application needs to send some input
To develop service
I want to do is related to manga
The web service
And the vet service
Needs to send an output back Rhonda has this list of to do
Do you want to create a course on this.
He wants to learn this topic more
Boost list of Toulouse
Has to be sent back
Application a
By the web service
And there's a
The input to a web service
Output from a web service
It's called a response
So if application is need some data from the web series or needs to perform some action
Turn on the web service
It creates a request
Application will create a request
I want details of to dissolve ranga
Lip service
Would look at the request
Process
And it would create a response
With the list of tools
That ranga has and it returns them back to application
And response
Big bass
Concepts
Behind
Except
The important thing is web services should be platform
Independent
I want web service we should be able to call from a job application or Dartmouth application
Application as well how do we achieve that think about format
Play Taste of java specific form
Auto. Net basic format
Other applications in other platforms be able to send a request in that format
The important thing for
The web service to be platform-independent
He's at the request and the response
Also should be platform
Independent
They should be in format
Which apps support
All different kinds of platforms
Photo request
And respond
First one is
XML
XML stands for extensible markup
You can generate XML from a Java platform or platform or any other platform of your choice
You have ignored
A closing note
Another note
Another closing note
Which is best find the details of the code that we would want I would want to get the details
Off
Course
I'm creating an XML request
2x ml is one of the popular format
For request
Response
Amvets
The other data exchange format
Jason
Jason Spencer
JavaScript
Object notation
The language
JavaScript which is used typically on different enough
We are also using JavaScript in the back-end like nodejs and
Things like that
Dallas
Footlong while was a language of the
Ben 10
Angie Stone
2%
Objects
The gripping love
Just venting systems
But also Kansas
Java.net
End
Took to make the VIP service
Independent
What we do is
Big Dipper
And the response platforming
How does application
Notify format of request and response
Application needs to send
Quest
2D web service
And once it gets the response
Mitsubishi Evo
Process
And do whatever it wants to do with it
How does ignore
What request to send
Where to send it
And what is the format of the response
Service
Definition
Every web service
Office
A service definition
Disservice definition would specify
Request and response format okay what is the format
Which is used to request and response is it Jason
Is it eczema
Or is it any other format
That specified by US service definition
Pittsburgh
Structure of the request
How can a consumer
Create a request what is the format
Request
Also Define
Structure what is this
Brookshire
This response which is returned by the service
The last thing which is part of the visit
Definition
How to call the service what is the endpoint
Where is the service available
The application a wants to make use of the web service in this video
We looked at
Important house
Related to a VIP server
How does data exchange take
To request
Respond
Web services platform Independent by creating platform-independent
Request Android
Sponsors
How does
An application
Nota format of request and response
We do that by providing something called a service
In the next video we look at some of the key
Terminology