But you come back
When we talked about the resource mapping
He said some of the values would be passed
Indeed
So here
/ user
Flash ID
Heidi's
What we'll do is recreate our the simple hello will be in request
Meetup
What a loser
And what we want to do
We want to pass in
Is we created Hello World
Variable
How do I get to
Accept deposit variable
I would need to give a name to the variable psychology
So what would happen here is
Quizlet
Battery rebuild / in 28 minutes
Then in 28 minutes
3D map
Variable
So let's get available to take that to that's called string
Is that sufficient
Actually
How do you do adding an addition called at
Variable
And now it's important in
What would happen if somebody types in Aura in 28 minutes to get map
The name India
Would be what would be mad
Into name
Change the name of the metal it doesn't really matter
But let's change it
Hello world
I want to hear
I would want to use a formatted essay
Hello world
Percentage is a losing name in here
String.
Format
This is the format to use
And I say use the arguments
Name
Go to happen this percentage is
Wood busy place
And this hello world being
Who did it
So what do you think it is very simple. What do you want to do
Assortative path variable
And what are values coming back
Vacating a hello world in with
This drink template
And returning that
It's a simple example
To show the power of battery tables
In all our social media application resource mapping
Beetlejuice bar parametres extensively
Kevin Gates post ID
Restful applications
B make extensive use
Tweety Bird
Start the application and I'll copy this Hollowell Parkway Berlin
Nips
Downhill
And UFC now that it's coming back with a response
Hello world
What do I'm passing energy pathway is getting
LOL
This is getting us how to order run.
What do value your passing in is being picked up by the controller and it is being sent back
Indira
Battery cables are a critical part of creating rest resources will make extensive use of battery cables
Indus Pacific Coast
Interested
Ballon
And how to pick up the value from it
Music
Tina control method