Welcome to this day
Where you could set up a project
Using spring initializr
Who'd want to build a restful web service
What do you do use
Start. Spring.
Initialize our spring project would want to convey to Maven project
Languages
Java
Anything which is greater in 2.00 Snapchat
The other things we want to specify is it cool
I want to use the group ID come in pretty when it rest web services
And I would put an artifact
Stressful
Lip service
For any Maven project
You need to give your group ID and an artifact.
You can kind of compare this
Lake
Last name
Gage
We would also want to add a few dependencies the way you can select dependencies is by type
So I would want to sell it
Texas
Dependency
You can't build restful web services
You remember that spring boot starter web is the starter for developing restful web services
It is also the starter for developing web applications
I would want to also add in
Deftones Deftones mix it
Easy foot Galloping application to a lad devtools in
I want to use GPA point in this course
GPA
And I would want to use
Stu lasting memory database
It's a date
Once you do that
You can click
Generate project
And that's what this downloaded to your downloads folder
Visit fine
Do some folder on your heart
Zip file is downloaded
You can take this uncertified to some folder on your local hard
And lunch apocalypse
Once it gets launched ASAP
You can import
Project by using fi
Import
And you can browse through to the directly where you unzip
UFC Fight 2
This is the truth directly to which I unzipped my zip file to
And I can see your phone. XML coming up
Restful
Web services
You can also use
Browse
To browse through to your folder
Wednesday
Finish button
Actually download all the dependencies
Which are listed
Linda Palm.
And it would also set up the entire project for us
This might take a little while if this is the first time you're using this specific version of spring boot
Because this downloads
A lot of maven
Dependencies
What is happening in the background is the complete setup of our restful web services project
Once the project is set up duty of folders
Structure like
This is
Typical Maven project structure salesman job assessment resources Solstice Chihuahua
Swing Java contains
All I Java code
There's not a lot in here right now we have Swordsmen to sources with
The properties file
So this application to properties which is the springboard
Properties file
And we have the test
Which can be written down in service desk
We also have a bond election
Which contains
The dependencies which we have chosen
XML contains
Spider web
Devtools
These forty forceful defenses are what we have choosing
On this tablet sting. IO website
Fab
Devtools
TPA nh-2 that's what we choose
And those for the dependencies
And by default
Spring boot with adding
Initializer would adding a dependency on Spring boot starter test
You should see
Lord of
Dependency suja coming in
Because of the starters we are you
Know that we have an overview of the project.
We are looking at
Let's start up the springboard app
Applications
Crikey
Runess
We have not really written
Unicode
As of now
But that's fine we we like a lot of code
Steps for now
What do you wanted to check
If the application is launching up fine
UB application lunches at 5
Gambia Good2Go
You can see that there's a lot of love
Being generated
You would see by the end of the thing that the Tomcat server has started up
So you can see the cat has started on ports
Ada
There's a lot of magic which is happening in the background
We will uncover all that magic
Any subsequent steps
As we develop
More and more
Bad service
Until the next step