Welcome
Back
Let's look at an important
Deus Ex
The earliest it be defined
Glasses
For this specific
Things in a CSS file
You can also Define
Dcss
On the element itself to on the counter itself
Pekin actually Define CSS
Let's look at
And what are the consequences of doing that this specific
So I said
Wendy counter itself you can include the style so how can we do that
I'm going to the counter and over here you can say
Is equal to
And you can put the
Police work
Let's go
Oops
Skyproc expects a mapping sunstyle properties to values and not a string
What did sing
Is that don't give me a string give me a proper object
So what do you need to provide it is actually
Object you cannot provide a string so let's change that to an object
Will it work
It says
Fail to compile
Unexpected token expecting clothes based why is this failing the reason is because I'm saying JavaScript
I'm saying
Inside this that is Javascript code
That's what the open Grace means
But what I'm putting in here
Is
Text
I want to convert this into an object how can I do that
I can include it within
Another set of
Braces
To save this now
Will this work
It says
Unexpected token -
Inside a JavaScript
Object
You cannot use a-
So how can I do that
How did you say
Phone
Size
And if it's a string value
What I need to do is to
Put waiting
Haha finally after all I travel
Be able to define the style as
Enough
You can actually take the
Ping out from here
Let's see if it works
You can see
But enough different size Still Remains 50 pixels
Have you can also mean removing siding from here
Down here
It so I can take one size 50%
Bedding
Between double quotes
Enough
You see that it Remains the Same
One of the other things you can do is actually Define a variable for this so I can take this thing
Then actually create a
Variable so I can say variable
Actually
Beacon just elect
Sylectus
1 mm to 3 a.m.
Is that
Scoop of it is not blocks could take you have a number of blocks and you define a v
Table in the innermost block
Debatable is available for the entire function
Antimatter
How late is block scope
Select Health System create block scoped variables
And that's the reason why I typically
How do you select insert beer style is equal to this particular
Why don't you think it's time is a constant let you know do the daily change it
In that case you can also use another important feature which is constant constant Style
Is it going to descend now
I can taste a physical to style
And let's see what would happen
It means
I don't really want to have Style
Spite of
You were confident sex as much as possible you won't actually have
Quality styling present in your counter
CSS
The idea behind this dip was delisted problems that you would face
Benjamin styling JavaScript code
What you doing now is an uncommon actually comment
Specific thing every Moody Style
From here as well
Go here and do this
Table of court
Turn off the tee if it remains as it is cool
To save this as friends
That's perfect
Stop
Step
Quick dip steps interesting isn't it
As a JavaScript variable with stylosa JavaScript variable included used it in the
Deus Ex
And then we went back to using CSS Style
Isn't it fun I'll see you in the next step