Rakem
Previous step
We started with creating the counter component
This is the view we have right now
Intercept
Let's go ahead and add a button
And show up
Count
You sure that's all you need to do is set button
I just
I had code
Plus one to it right now let's see how it appears
Tibetan + 1
It's plasma
Important things to understand
56 is equal to. So if you use captive
It says device not Define
All history of elements
Should be small
Weather today
Any formal events
All of them should be
Small case
Olympic custom companies that we create
Can use the initial calculator
Let's focus on actually adding a counter as well
Define a Spanish
Just do
Differentiate
It's Sunday but until that we can started differently
Is evil
What do you want to do this when this button is clicked
One of the things that I don't really like
How about it right now because I don't like the styling of it
I want to add a little bit of styling CSS to this Pacific counter how can I do that
I can do that is by creating a CSS file for that specific
Counter
CSS
Took Outlet CSS and I can add Styles in here
Imported into the way I can import a CSS file
I just need to say import. /
Counter
.
CSS
Check weather
DCS is working with sticky button
And add a little bit of CS2 / tulips
Just say
Font size
100 PX
You can see it's fun size
100 pics
This is looking like we have to do with glitter and glue
Inside
Better
A lot of background
Color
It's pekid green let's keep it simple
How to make the font size
16 pixels
Allied
Batting
Let's have a fun color of white
End
Have
Elijah battle
100 pixels
Expert on CSS and trying to just
Get this thing a little better looking enough I have plus one
I've been a little better so this times that we are adding working fine to apple juice the button
Let's actually
Add a class
To this
Call
Comment
I'm thinking about sex as if you'd want to add a class-divided attribute to use is class
Name
Always suggested thing to use is class name and at the reason why you would see that
In all the gay sex with me. Auntie love you would be using class name
Took to add a class on to anything that you need to do is look last name is equal to count enough
To access to the account that we need to do is say. Count
Play whatever you want in here just to
Check if it's looking that safe and fun size
PX
I see what would happen
A little bit of padding to it as well
Turn off I have a button and I have account which is displayed along
What should we do next
What do you need to do next is benefits plus one button is clicked
Dude want to incriminate
The value of discount
How do we do that that's where an important concept comes into picture
I see you in the next day