Welcome
In the last step when you slide state
Indigent
Tractor
He said
Contact has a value of 0 and this is what it should be in this day
And when
User clicks on the command button
What we need
What's the coldest state method
And gave it
The new value of counter
Could you not really update the value of counted in the state directly we did not say this. State. Counter plus plus
What weed is deserted state
And gave it
The new value of counter
Why does react make this
So complex
To understand that you need to understand something called
What you looking at
English of the counter that we would develop
What did see is beneath that the HTML is complex you answer this simple counter
Biggest human penis
It's a really really complex
Miniclip kljestan
The counter is getting updated through
JavaScript
How does JavaScript know where to update the whole thing
The great books is Javascript has an internal representation of this page
Document
Mortal
To each of these elements
Is Norwood
Inside the Dome
And bent over
You need to make a change
What happened to Sam javascriptcore gets executed to update.
Pacific element
Thing about Dom is
Thomas very very complex
If you have work with jQuery if your work with any applications from 5 to 10 years back you know how difficult it
How does he act counterfeit
That's where
A very important
Quonset
Virtual Dom
What's wisdom is
Presentation of the dorm in memory
Because it's in them
Making changes to watch Oldham
What league does
If you have two versions of State
Create virtual Dom
Distortions
And then finds the diff between them
And then
You give that to update the dorm
Search up making hundred updates to the Dome what year does this
Find out what are the exact two things that are changing and only update those two things
But it's taking example essay the current state of the Countess is
Counter
Buddhist
So you don't already have Gilda virtual down with the estate value S5
And it would be the new what you're doing with this date value S6
If you do it this
Identifying
The fact that
Only
This Pacific
Needs to be happy
And then it would go ahead and
I understood what happening in the background have
The Oculus Virtual down to ensure that the applications are as efficient as possible
Next Step