Welcome
The previous steps
We started designing a counter when we did a plus one variable increment the counter
If you need to have multiple counters
With different values on them
Let's take
Indus Pacific step
We have a single counter on Tinder
It's going adding another account
Just I did encounter in here
What would happen now
I go to my location to see that there are two different counters with their own individual states
If I add one more counter
Is
All these three have their own individual counter States
That's cool right to know if you have
The ability to create energy components and
Include them in updating component
But what do you want to be able to do
Is
Number one
Who want to be able to Define
A different increment value for each of these
The best one I want to have classified as being human this one I would want have less than as the inclement this one
Probably + 1 as the increment
How can I do that
That's number one
Is venom
Take this long to update the same variable right now we have three different things
That's
Problem statement number two
Let's start with problem statement number one in the specific step
Do you want to be able to have different increment values for each of these buttons
What are the important things that you need to understand is the increment value is not going to change to once
I created button and I say this is increment value S5
You cannot change to something else
During the lifetime of that specific component
And that's weird
Property scams in order called
What you can do is stupid counter
You can add a property so how do I add a property
But you can do that is by saying counter
And say increment by
Is equal to
Something increment by is equal to one there's a small mistake in here don't worry about it we'll fix it a little later
I don't think you mean by fight
Increment by
I can go to the counter component
And I can use the increment by
Value how can I use that
How does it come in
Let's hear the way you can use the props
Is your plus one
Interveinal want to display
Deep value so how can I do that
It's a JavaScript value
And you can do that this this
Got trucks
.
The name of the property
Bike
Let's see what happens
Plus one
Best Buy
Blessed and Isn't that cool
+ 1 + 1 + 1 + 5
Listen
Let's fix that
Stop the step in here and try implementing that
As an exercise near me
Side note
I would recommend you to try that as an exercise
Okay I hope you had a chance to do it if you have not
This is how we would do that
What do you need to do
Drops.
Bite
Tonka lovable incrementing by what
We waiting too many things by one instead of one what do you want to do
If you don't even come in by
This. Thoughts.
What would happen
Let's to
What is happening
It's actually not incrementing is but a pending one to it
Think about it
It's actually doing this thing happened
Why the biggest thing happened
Because
We have defined a string value in here
Okay we need to actually Define a integer value
Books
Address
Oops
You can use Bluetooth
The only way you can
Assign a India value is actually creating a
Deus Ex explosion
I need to surround this with
{
Let's do that
And save this
+ 1 + 2 + 3 cool + 5 + 9 + 10 + 10 awesome
Isn't it cool
What we did enough this week
Having the ability
Customize
How much the increment of each of these counter should be
How is the increment should be does not change over the lifetime of this company this company will always increments
This company will always increment by 5
This component will always increment by one
And that's the reason why we made it a property
Bi using it
Set
The increment value of that specific component
Little bit
How we can use properties
You look at the fact that if I do bicycle to court
1 it becomes a string
Places
And all that we needed to do inside the counter class
Was
To start using this. Probz
But