Graco
A few steps
We talked about lot of different things about component you can Define of you using it
Baloubet how you can write
Logic
Basically how you combined events
What happens on the screen
Look at how you can stay
Little bit two options
We can believe that
Create Styles inside your JavaScript as well
A basic look at this state you stayed for the counter
And believe that the fact that the state has to be initialized
Inside
The Constructor and later when we would want updates if you'd call this set statement
Emerge to the set set method would always do a March of the
Allstate values
The existing state
Glockenspiel
What's props
To be bit
And have you considered default
Properties
Second space
Example of constraints
On a property
Let's look at
Important tool
Unplugging related to react
If you Google for react developer tools
Cute and up
WhatsApp login
Fendi website Chrome. Google.com
Zurich menu to use the Chrome browser so instantly Chrome plugin
They're going to put two salsa has
Firefox plugin
I've already installed it on my Chrome
Remove from chrome
If you have not insulted you would see I install battery in here
You go ahead
Instant and restart your Chrome browser
Launch OBD2 do application
When's your lunch ready to react location what you'd be able to do
Go to the reactor if you right click
Inspect
And then
What year
Go to react
So if you actually zoom out a little bit
UTI
Clytia
Or you can
Use this ad which is present in here and go to the reactor
Dragon drop the w212
So that I can see what's behind it
And you can see all the elements which are present
You can see the props
And you can see
The Deep
Affected this deep
Children
Property call
Class name
You can see
The fact that there are three counters
You can see the props and estate
So if I actually do class 1 you can see that the state changed
You can see that that's reflected by a yellow highlight
This is useful in debugging staff
Whatever you see something is not working
You want to see what is the thoughts of a specific react component
What is the state of the components you can use this plugin
Awesome plugin
When you highlight of component
Highlighter element
You can see the entire tree so they've
Hundred
Accounter Android SD card
You can also
Where is the code for that specific
Component is present
Is a very useful plugin
If you want to debug stuff or you don't understand more about how react works
Time to commute to Clarendon.
And I'll see you in the next step