Welcome back
In the previous step
Introduced the concept of
Thoughts
Let's look at a couple of important tips regarding products
A default value for the properties
As well as
You can check the type of the properties how can you do that
Let's start with the default value
The counter are going to make one the default value so it does not set by
At all
The default I would want give
Funny
How can I do that
I bet you can do that
Is by
Going outside the counter class
She's kind of a
What Quran provided
Yes it's working on / react to that is defining of property on the counter
So you can say
Counter. Default props
Create a JavaScript object in here so the JavaScript project is where you define
The default values
So I would say
Bite
If I want to add more stuff I can add it in this way
I just want to add
What's up counter default drops by
You can see my D phone it's 1
Add one more counter and save it
Between cat this week
Class 1 default value for counter
Increment would be
By adding default
Rocks
They made the mistake of actually assigning
Bye
Is equal to a string
And we saw that the counter company
Continue to work without giving a warning
How can you avoid that
The baby can avoid that it's by
Do it by check on the problem which is being passed
How can we do that
It's one of the property so you can say counter.
Prop
Type
Is equal to and Define another Jascha project and say bye
Proptypes
Oops
.
It's not getting imported automatically let's go important
So I can say
Import
Truck stops from
Drop -
Time in 1312 types of Memorial call prototypes
And I can say over here
Prototypes
Dark
You can see all the property types that can be
Bollywood
So you can see that
I can say proptypes.
Identity are rates a Boolean and you can also specify a list of values we keep it simple
You would want to check
Is that it
Number
How can you check data number
Which of these would be the better option
Number two
Bye
Proptypes
Number
India Burgess we have bicycle gas into a string one
Hooksett Kansas to work
Why don't things is if you look at
Dickinson days of warning which is being printed it says
Failed prototype
Hemolytic drop by off type string
Reply to counter expected number 13
It's an unexpected type you can go ahead and actually now
Gorgeous and fix it
Close this
And that's all
We have everything working
Expected music video do you get a few things related to props
How to add
Default values
The property's value is not specified what should be the default value for it
Have you been food constraints around the values that can be assigned to prototypes
We just needed to put profit and use that to specify the constraints
You saw that buddhaful flops and crop tops in 386 are added as properties
Saint Nicholas
I see you in the next step