Welcome back
Beirut start developing our counter component
What to do if you take a shortcut and we'll use the same application to develop the counter
20 + 2
Eating this piece of code what I'll do is actually Alex theater
You confident
Calculus class
Learning components
Extenze
Confident
Moody
Send a method interesting
Actually I copied intermittent in here
What did Nicholas enables us to do is whenever you want to
Go back to the learning components all that we need to do is
Do this
Learning components
Class learning components
And deleting the existing functionality that we had
The only thing I need to change this
Changing last name here to learning components
If I go back to the browser
It remains exactly the same
Isn't that cool
Go back to the incompetence whenever you want to
Guadalupe for enough
Please remove this app
What do you want to focus on is to start creating art counters
Lights ellipse start creating a counter component
We can create a class component or we can create a function component
What you have learned earlier is the need to create
Components in their own classes actually
In their own models
So let's go ahead and start creating a new folder
For all the stuff that would be creating for
Count to inside components counter
Can you hear a new fight I'll call this
Counter. Sex
Name of the
Component
Are the name of the file or the name of the module does not need to match
The name of the classes which are present in here
Indirect the name should really match
Howard
In JavaScript
The name of the module
Name of the file containing emoji
Does not need to match
Default exported class so you can actually name this playlist anything but as I mentioned
Kind of use
The company which is exported out of that specific model
The name of that component the name of the model
I haven't gotten.
Function company that you created
Card company entered into counter
Function
Counter
I'll take last name is equal to counter
And this is a counter
Make sure that you are replacing this as friends who created account
Component be exported out
You don't need to use a semicolon in a Burgess what would want to do if you don't want to import the contacts
Import
Counter
From
/
Counters
Let's include
Counter
The app Navia including Discounters component in now you can see us getting rendered
Is Quick-Step what we wanted to do is the basic setup for the counter component nextstep let's talk more about