Welcome
Indian music
VN hands. Counter
Have a better look it's really perfect yet but it's
Looking better than
What it was earlier
What do you want to do is when you click plus one who'd want inclement
The value of this and I said there's something called state
Involved
Before we get to State we need to be able to handle
Click event
This button is clicked and we will handle that
How do I do that
Let's see how to do that in the specific step
Eugene javascript-based donkey dong
The way you do that is by adding a on Kik event and adding a JavaScript
Method called so you say on click is equal to
Js
Metode
Call
Case of
Deus Ex
Do we need to do it is a little different
What are the important things
Is NJ six
All the attributes
So Auntie is an attribute on the bottom
Use
Camelcase
Tuan people would use
Bfcat
Tuan clicker Beyond C caps
Click
Define in here
You think that Lee braces
What function to call
So let's define a function calculus function increment
And
What I'll do is
Controller plug
Increment
I want to call
Increment method JavaScript
Hydraulic schematic call and that's why we're putting it between
{
Hindisax anything JavaScript to take Within
Let's see what would happen
Do right click inspect
Look at cancel
What are the things that I am observing right now is that they printed in Dickinson
The other side because I'm inputting logo
And also we have to find a technical competency
Used at all so that's okay
What do you focus on is really the increment stuff right
Increments
Is getting cold
Centipede is getting loaded and not one
Desmond is
Happening in that way
What are the important things about
Deus Ex
This venue Define the method you just
Bossa reference to the method of the matter you don't
Say okay this is the function to call this is the reference
And what did happen is that function would be called when the click event happened
Function call and I'm just passing
A function name to it
Let's see what happened
No you'll see that when a betta fishes
When I say plus one
Cool
You can see that
More and more improvements are being printed
We are able to handle
The increment
Click event Toronto click event
@dora increment
Question is what should we increment
Hated this dealership being committed to one and two three four and five
And to be able to do that we need to have something here
Representing
The state of this specific component
What do you have a state for this specific component
Want to take event you can do an
Adamant
How do you spell by state
Look at that in the next step
Boy