Welcome back
Section 8 the basics of components
Week forecast
On the j6 part and we talked about parent component child component
We talked about how you can create a new jail models for each of the components
And we talked about how you can create a number three components
In your app company
Do understand react we need to understand a lot more about components
You need to understand how you can write logic around company until you can take
Decisions based on actions
Are you going to style
Your component
And also talked about a couple of important things called States
And properties
To help us understand this
What do you do if you develop something called
Counter
A symptom
This would be up your friend encounter
Will you play any of these buttons
Specific increment decrement will happen
We have a reset button at the bottom
To reset the entire state
Liberty uses example
As a means to understand
The other important things about component logic
Styling
Create and Craft
I hope you're having an interesting time in the course
I'll see you in the next it would start with the counter component