Welcome
Back
Do previous steps
We created counters and each of these counters have individual state
That's cool with what we wanted to do is actually create something
Which has
Banh counter and multiple buttons
How do we really do that
The state is associated with each counter
Can we continue to associate state with each counter and have a single
Count
Which would be the single count
Be present
You are right have to move this state up
Yes
State with each of the counters
With each of the counter buttons
What do you want me to do
It's made me to Smoothie state
Little app
What are the things I would want to do is this
Counter class that I created
Lightning represents actually a counter button does not replace represent
Counter because we were going to have a single counter and a number of
Increment buttons
Cyclist counter
Button
Ann dancing class counter button
Extends component
And what we had including
Enough
Counter
Buttons
Time actually changing everything out
Counter button
Why
Because I need input converter
Send
Cool
It speaks that as well
You have everything looking so we have the counter button
Gift at associated with the counter
What do you want to do is actually create
A complementary presenting all the component buttons
Right
That's where you'd want to start creating a new component called
Counter
Which contains
All the counter buttons
Till I didn't have the app
Create account button salad want to have the
Counter beautycounter buttons right now
Colette's actually
Poppy Drayton
Third from here to coffee
Oh here
Class name is equal to
It's a counter
Handwritten this
Counter buttons
Define
And over here and stuff
Chili using the counter button sticks used account
To the app
Only includes
Counter does not worry about
Each of the counter buttons
Exodus elevators
I want to import contacts from contact component
Will it work
Nope not yet
Twerking
But it's only showing one counter
Because
What is happening is what is exported by default
Exported by default Discounters button
List on the button is being used as counter and that is what is being shown what do you want to do if you want export
Counter
Let's do that
Export default counter
No. 3 button switch
And everything is working as it is
Create
Counter button class and include
A number found two buttons inside the counter what we have is
Wenatchee
Started thinking about our problem we started to understand the fact that this battle
Delete account of itself
Accountant self
Then we can have single account in multiple buttons
And that's right we created account about in class and we created accounting class containing the
Multiple account buttons
One of the things that you can do as an exciting actually
Defected the counter button out into a
Gas off its own 2 into a module of it own
But for now I'll leave it as it is and in the next steps let's start actually moving this date
Sunday counter button
Could you count let's see what are the challenges moonface
Doing that
I hope you're having an interesting time
Doing this
The idea behind the entire course
What's the make it a very interesting experience and that's why we designed this country example so that
A lot of stuff
From animal places to other so that you have a deep understanding of what's Happening behind the screen
SLS
You have a deep understanding of how to design stuff with react
I'm sure you're having a wonderful experience and I'll see you in the next step