Alaikum
Back in the sentence let's look at a couple of tips
First one
Is that
With the current state what do they mean so if I have a state in here right or counter is
I would want to add
Pink
To Discount asset to this date I would want to add another value
How do you separate
Different values you do scum
M20
End
It's just a second counter
Android
Sodium sulfate is Countess England second counter hundred
Incrementing the counter and only sitting the value of
Counter
What happened to the second counter
Will it become zero what would happen is that the second counter value will not be modified at all.
What are adjectives of passing in here
And updated remains as he's
David want to see
The value of the second counter
What I lose count
II
Conceited second contest remains hundred
Setstate is actually emerge
That's number one
Tell if I would want to update the second counter as well I can say second counter
And say this.
.
Second
Counter
All of them get updated
That's
Number one
Let's get rid of tea
Second countdown
Cool
Checking account the result of the equation of
The second thing I would want to talk about
Arrow function
Typically
Vanderburgh
Videos functional programming in Java
We have a Lambda expression
And similar to that in JavaScript
We have something called Arrow function
All typing note aluminum command prompt or terminal
And typing note
Give Dallas zip code in here
And you can also type in the same code
Let's create a simple list and
How can you create a list where
List
Is equal to
One, two, three, four
This is how you Define exemplary
No
Whenever you would want to do something around this
Using functional programming
If that would want to look around this and print
Double D values in JavaScript is by saying list
.
But it is very similar to the first method which is present in Java functional programming
Do you think this bad footage
Eat
Value
40 text which is present in here
Cancel. Log
Into
So what do you defending here is X
This is equal to and greater sign this is called the arrow function
So X
Arrow
What should we do
Be very careful about decent exit list
. for each e caps
Closing (here in between.
OBX
And it prints to 4
Saddle function is what we are going to look at right now and look at how it simplifies
The need
To do a binding
This isn't normal function
Write how do I make it an arrow function
What did I need to do
Do a simple change in this
Go here
Give me set vendor
Is equal to
This indicates that this method no parameters
Then
Do this
What is the advantage of doing this let's save this
And actually
UK
Be cool to see if it's working fine yet it's running
Fine in the browser
The advantage of doing this is
Do not need to do this binding Arrow functions alone
You don't really need to do this blinding so if you see right now
I think at the air
Can you
Because I've actually change render method to an aromatic not the increment method isn't that funny
Dizzy kind of things which
Happens when you record a lot of stuff in a single day
Titanoboa
Can you be inclement weather
Arrow function
Let's see what happened
Cool enough
This works
The a dysfunction
Penguins
The need
Subaru of binding
Can you use an adverb function
You don't really need to bind the disagreeable because the disbanding happens automatically
After this course is concerned
He would continue using
Choose your baby cactuses have
Things I've done in react documentation as of today
So let's continue doing it
Deep traditional way witches
Defining normal class
Metal
So we continue doing that
And we continue doing bindings
Throughout this course so be careful with that
The idea behind this
Give you a couple of pics the first one
What's that
60 is a merge
With
The existing state second thing
Is it 55 in Arrow function then you don't really need to bind this variable to it
Disclaimer is in this course you would continue to use
Normal class
Es6 methods
I'm having a lot of fun creating the school and I'm sure you are having a lot of fun too
I'll see you in the next