Wake up
What's the click of this button will want to be able to increment the value for this
But that's beside the need
The other thing which we looked at is the fact that
Dysfunction is now outside
Function component
I've deep function component becomes more and more complex
It's better that we convert it into a normal component
What actually a class component
Let's start with creating a class component for counter and what do they do
Start adding
Let's get started right now
Something I would start doing is class counter
What do you want to do this extends component right at 50 what would want to be able to do
Extenze
Let's import the component from the eye
Stand over here
Beauty to add a render
Method
Integra no matter what you want to do
If you don't want to return
Isn't that cool
Let's
For my little little better
So that we can see everything which is happening in here
We created the counter component
We had Adventure mattered and we returned
Stuff
Etsy
It's in the same way is to + 1 increment is getting called
What do you want to do this we don't really want to have in common method outside the counter now
What do you want to do this we want to have the increment method inside
D
You want a method inside the class I will need to remove the function
Absolute dating
Let's see what will happen
Disney
Part of the class counter
Because if you want to call a local Lee Define this.
Enough
Increment is getting called that's cool right of enough
Converted
Counter from function components
Glass component
That's enough
Go ahead
And
Grandad
To this specific thing
What are the important things in
Best practices to follow our
Number one
Define
The initial state
In a constructive constructive
Is with you actually Define
Used shell state
In the specific methods
What do you need to do you need to update the state
What do you need to do
A deconstructor what would be the state of the component
We have a counter
Set the value of the euro
Each time interval method is called what you want to do is counter
Plus that's what we want to be able to do
Isn't it right
It starts with the first step is defining the initial state in a Constructor
Texarkana tractor
In JavaScript is very simple its Constructor
10 gallon acrylic last name
Scott's tractor
This you can Define the initial state
So how do you do
Initial state for a specific component
Anybody activity you can actually Define initial state is by saying this. State
Is equal to
You can define a JavaScript object in here
To the JavaScript object
Whatever you need to do is count
Lucille
Temple painting
Accounted
Initial value of
First step
Second step is I want to be able to use the state
Inside my
If you
Tonight novantrone zero in here
What I would need to do is what is the value of this date
So how do we do it
Save this
Oops
This. Stay. Counter
First ever
And also
This cannot set property state of undefined
Why is that coming in
Is because
In JavaScript
Unless you call this super method
You cannot use this
Celine Constructor
Before I use this I'll need to call
The super method
Remember once this is another a lot of
Notify
Didn't call Super and we would start using this
In the Constructor and this would result in an error
That's cool so it's coming up
Like what is that mean this birthday. Country soon as is
Is that what you want you want to show the value of this
So we want to execute JavaScript
No need to say
Teresa. Counter it's showing zero cool right now
What do you need to do you want to implement it
How to increment eclipse
Amindi increment
Stuff
Can I say
This
.
State
Not
Counter
Plus plus
Is that what we do typically
Isofresh
Jasmine
Which place
It says cannot read property state of undefined
Which is happening
Is that
It says I cannot find the value this
Instructor
What do you need to do if you called the super method to make sure that this is available
50 people react
Es6 classes
If you want to make this available
Inside the method
What do you need to do is move me to buy Indy method to the class
How to rebind a message to b class
Baby would do that typically
Is inside the Constructor
What do you do if you take this
Increment
Is equal to
This. Increment. Buying
Disturbia binding
This
Increment
What will happen now let's see
Cool arrows disappeared
There's a new era which is coming here because they do not mutate State directly but before that lets do + 1
Okay I think it's been good
But the most important thing is
Morning which is coming in here it seems to not mutate State directly
Don't try to change their directly
This is where I'm changing the state
Test to see what it's telling me
Siletz
Do that
React you didn't update
The state of the company directly
Metal
Idiot
Hell yeah
I'm going to update the state
What's the weather update is there you go and take it and a place to the components
Important things about deserted state
Is that
What do you need to pass to it is a
Object so I'm passing a object
Again
Passing an object
The updated
Value
To what I would need to do I need to say
That's basically the new value of State
Is actually
Counter
Plus one
It's for my Bissell little bit
Let's see what would happen
Cool
Plus one
Nothing is happening because I actually made a mistake down
It should be count as a counter inside the state
Is this that account of this one. Let's see what would happen
Amantadine treatment
If it goes on to become into that school
Let's do a plus one of you can see
That the state is getting incremented 7 + 1
This is getting implemented as well
Isn't that cool
What we have is a component to do a plasma to prevent a Duo plus when it gets implemented by
Is it
We started with converting d
Countif function company
Into what class component
The first thing we have to do what's the. In diameter
And had the counter Classics 10 components
We needed to remove the function key word before we move the increment method inside
The class
We started focusing on
Estate
Do this specific component we wanted to have a counter variable representing the state of this
Redefined a Constructor
Baby initialise this day and decided if I wanted to use this
I needed to call this super superclass Constructor
The difficulty considerably superclass and who you want this is called
We will be having this
Have this date set
You saw that the
Ikumen method
Did not have this available to enable.
We had to buy this
Do the increment method inside the glass
The last thing we did
What's
I did this date
We never updates did that icky that's a very bad please
All that we need to do is
I did this date by calling this set
Method
State State method
React would look at what is changing
And based on it
It would efficiently update
Deep component
Hip just started with State and there are a lot of things that you need to understand
About
You look at that and a lot more in the subsequent steps