In the last video we talked about subject
We saw how we design tables
Different from Hobbit
Design objects
Jtbc
Spring jdbc
And my bed is
Indus
Video
Rick Gates
Introduction to how
If you're already familiar with that you can keep this video and move on to the next video.
Sing about JP
The other approaches
In my bed
NJ DVC
Spring jdbc and my bed is what we do
We write creative
Once we die degrees
We need to do two things one is
Over here if you look at it the circle parameter
I need to do set user is equal to 7
These are all different parameter so I would need to populate
These parameters
When should I be quiet you need to set the values for this parameters other thing I would need to do is once Aquarius
Executed for example
I'm a few things
Grady
Big Topanga strain
The results are coming back
She's all set to take the values from the results
And story today
Kidney beans
It's to do with family values
You don't really have any results coming
But if you were doing when you have results back
So you need to take those results
And populate into your Java objects Aldi
How did jtbc do that did we just basically Java database connectivity
And the way you did it was through things like statement prepared statement results
So what we do is we write a query to write a query
And then we had to create a statement or a prepaid statement for it and send it back into the
Eat while you submitted the value here
Are you here
Tien Tuan
Equity
Then you need to get the results
Andrew need to map
Manually
What do you need to do
To do something like this
And then take the values represented and put into the bean so we are explicitly doing that
Yeah you can see that I'm actually taking
One by one
Into the dean
You can look at the code that we rode with jdbc
Just
Updates
Just to do a simple update at the light like
1520 lines of code and I'm not even talking about exceptionally coding
Alarm code that I would need to write in jdbc did
Try to provide a layer on top of JTV
He's refusing low-level things like statement prepared statement other things
Did he said he'll provide you a jdbctemplate you use a jdbc temp
If I wanted to do a update
I still have to ride equated
With what
You can call JBC update
With your pretty and all the parameters what I'll do
Take me first one
Duplicity
Take the second one
Everyplay City
Take the third one
And also it interviews a few simple Concepts
Rome apples
By default
If you are
Names match
Then you don't really need to create a map of that also then you can use something called Bean propertyroom Apple
Multiple queries
Oh here we are using this to do map
To map
The results from the query
2D being so what is this reasoning is it to do you can see that all the logic I would need to typically do in JTB
BC I don't need to do that when I'm using a jade
To what it's been getting busy to Simply provide a simple layer on top of jdbc
Can easily map parameters to queries
And easily take the results from the results
Add map to Java object
Not what the other framework which gaming
Mybatis
But I don't really think it's object relational mapping famous girl it's not really mapping or disc two tables
What it does
Max objects
My buddies provides a simple
Similar annotation based
What was mapping decorative earlier from new a parameter Skylanders to queries
End
What we can do with my bettas if you can do the same stuff using XML or
Sweeties like this
Juice to replace the
But what my bet is did
Is it provided a simple mapping
Framework
So? I would say
You was at and you what is using
You said is the name of the attribute in the bean
Craig sample over here you can see
Target
Target date is equal to Target date and what is Target date
Target date is the target date Sunday.
If I wanted to use
Really it's very simple I just need to say I want to update I want use this update gritty
And use this Bean
Because
You have a dream
The name of the field in here
I bet this would be able to recognize that
Security update statement for you a quick look at how things were done with
PC Whitaker
Jtbc
Also
Define something for all these three approaches with the fact that they're still pays don't query
Hypebeast in dried blood
Gravy's
Probably
Crazy
When relationships between tables
Then you have to modify all your queries
I've worked in a lot of applications where they were Lord of bigquery switch return like
And understanding these
And maintaining these
Is it really tough job you need to really have a great understanding of how things are done in
Database
To be able to type this
Grady's
Bacterial problem
The problem was
Equities were becoming so complex that it was
Difficult to really maintain the man
Tables
It was really becoming
Difficult to maintain these
Gravy
That's the world
Jeep
NBA stats
In the next video will look at house GPS price to salt