Spring data jpa makes it easy to manage
Once you have defined you are entities and Define the mapping to the database
That's it
Spring data repository would provide a lot of useful methods
To manage them
Any previous step images of this save method
Let's start with using a few more
One of the important methods which is present in the user deposit 3 user upholstery.
Fighting
If I want to find my ID I can use the method
Find a ID
And you can see that defined by ID uses a long so I say
How do I
And yes I need to a local radio
This actually didn't send optional so I'd say
You deserve it
I would say user is
Creative destruction
Gandhi user usbid1
Retrieved from the database
The other options user Repository
Kawaii
So let it
And I'll send this to
It's called users
And let's also log
All
Please a couple of methods from the use of deposit today
Actually use it positively has
Lord of adamant that so you would see that use a repository has a competitor that delete method
You can actually delete in badge
And you can check whether something exists
This or not you can do Viber idea searches using fine
And also
You have methods to save
Save method is used
Insert
And also to update and
Entity
What ideals methods that have Dayland user repository I would recommend you to try and see
What are the methods
I did and try to play around with them
Let's restrict ourselves for these two things
And let's talk
Running the application I'll stop this
And started again
Application will take it take a while to launch up because we have put it in debug mode
Tonight complete execution if you look at the log
Dootsie
A few things that are
To one of the things we just print it if user is a trip to be able to retrieve the user with ID 1
The name is Jack and received it illicit mean
And also we see all users printed in the logs all users
Restart how
User repositories very useful in simplifying interactions with the entities in managing entities
To know it
Spring data jpa
Makes it really really easy to manage to Santa
Next Step