We come to this video where we were trying to understand
Object relations
We were talking about is the fact that the application
Does the baby decide not to objects
So the baby design this employee to ask part-time employees retirement project is different from hell
Do things on the database
Stop
Employee employee
So how does GPS only problem
Jpa provides
Mapping
You can map application
Glasses
You can say
This class
Stable
Wikipedia
Mapping
Between your classes
And the tables
Using things like
Entities
Relations
To do something called identity manager
Mini
I want to save a task to the database I can use any
Entitymanager
DaVita Costco object
And it would be able to stay with today.
I would want to get the values of a certain amount of time
But I would want to get the values
Of all the tasks
Related to a person I can use the in
Entitymanager also has this features of criteria API
And jpql
Which provides
So I would want to find some data from the database
I want to do
Searches
You can also use
Jpql or criteria API
Querida
Jpql similar to SQL udb using
Entities
Instructables
In jpql
And criteria API depression survey where you can drive JPL using Java API
Before we can get
Idle Hands
Wednesday TV
GTA V look at a few examples of how you can map application
Classes to database
Example of a stable there was a mismatch of how things were
Class
Multitask object
Andy.
How do we solve that
GPA provider
Shinso here there's an annotation called
Table
The X table annotation
Helps you to map
Object
Do your table so here I'm saying
Okay this task
Is going to be
Store an instance of class task would be stored
The Entity cast
I'm good with an English accent
Beauty by putting in at entity annotation on top of
I'm saying
This description feel which is present in here should be stored in a column called
That's how we map
Soviet description Target data in the table is called Target data ugly map it
By putting add column name is equal to Target
Example of mapping
Feels
You can also establish relationships between
Different
Entities
Two employees and then
We already looked at the fact that they have a many-to-many relationship
You can use an annotation call at many too many so here I'm saying at many-to-many and add many to many
This establishes a many-to-many relationship between the
Employee and the task
Glass
And the third example which we looked at
Full-time employee and part-time employee this
Classes are all map
Just a single table in the database
Map to employee
One table
All the subclasses of employee
2 to 1
Table and we're also saying
We distinguish is using the employee title we're also seeing that in here so what are you saying
The discriminator column is
In the specific step aunt in love
Mapping
Between your object
And the tables
The most important thing that you need to understand is
Weird
Trying to highlight
If you're not able to understand these things at in depth
That's not a problem at all
You're going to do a lot of this stuff
Step by step
Future
InStep quick overview of the big
Objects
Two tables
We looked at how we can map
Table column
Examples of how to map
Relationship
And we look at how to map
Inheritance relationship
The idea behind this step is to
Give you a quick flavor of what you can do with j
EPA
We have not really got our hands
In the subsequent steps
We'll start getting our hands