Welcome to this video where we are going to discuss.
What do you want to understand
Is what is the problem that Java persistence API
He's trying to solve
What were the alternatives to Japan
And how does Java persistence API solve that problem that's basically what we would want to understand
Capitol steps will be little bit of theory if you are a handsome guy then it might be a little boring for you but I think it's
It's important to end
Sourpuss
What is the problem
Think about it
The programming language we are using his job to take data from java
What do you want to do it
Indy database
How are databases designed in databases are typically relational database
Right now it is there a lot of Big Data another step nosql stuffing
She's coming to pick you up
You know for the most part we use relational database
Tables
In Java side we have objects
Quantitative aside we have tables
How to restore data from objects to table
Is using auditory
WW2 tinted Concepts
Heather on the database
We use something called normalization oriented programming
Typically consists of corn
Encapsulation
Interfaces
Polymorphism and things like that
Hello baby talk about relational databases we're talking about things like tables
Foreign Keys primary keys
Villages of mismatched
Between this
Do there is a mismatch between how we design objects and how we design tables
But we would want to establish a relation
Let's consider a few examples
I have a very simple example here have employees
Slight so you have an employee who can have multiple tasks.
And what you would want to think about is what
Possible mismatches
When you are trying to map
This problem statement
Two objects
Tables
Let's look at the first example
Basic
Object is made up of field
Table is made up of
Columns
How to rename the
Different from how we name the columns
Example using VLC and getting the table to columnist
You recalling its Target date in the table
Target_date
Either
This is kind of a basic
Tibial example let's think about relationships between tables
Relationships
Employee can have multiple tasks
And it's asking have multiple employees associated with a child wasn't it in Java
Employee
We'll put a list of tasks to him
Play Casting have a list of tasks
This is how we put it
A task is associated with the list of employees this is how we
Recognize that
Indy
Java world
How do we do that in table typically irritable employee
Dusk
I'm sure the relationship in there
Classes on objects
How do you take data from here
Storage in the table
So here we have employees two kinds of employees full-time employees and part-time employees
Freedom employees have a salary part-time employees have
You can see that these accident employee
But when we talk about tables we just have one table
We have an employee type to distinguish between full-time employee and part-time employee
And restore the values of Department playing hourly rates
This is one of the attributes
The data from these three classes has to be stored
One table
We were looking at a few examples of fall
What we were talking about
Is the fact that how we
Design objects Is this different from how we design our table
And that
Really the problem
That all persistence
Free books
Have been trying to solve
Play framework Switch reviews
To solve
The persistence problem
What
Jtbc
Spring jdbc
And my back
We'll look at Hot Dogs flavors
Try to solve the problem of object relational in pee