In the last days
Redefine.
Beauty won't be able to save this
Entity to the database
What do you need to use sweetie to use an
Entity
Mayonnaise chips
Be able to save this user identity
Did the database how to create something called user
New user
New class
You want to call it
User Diego serve
Desert Toyota service
In the sense that
Set data access on
This is something which helps us
Access Data from the
I'm calling a user. Service
I'm taking finish one of the things I would want to move this to a package
I Would One Direction
Can be created
Package
DPN 10 steps service
So now we have this
And in this class we want to be able to manage user end
NDTV would one be able to save you this
And the trees users from the day
What are the first things that we would need to do to be able to get the values from the database is
Import Java Exposition Center
What is entity managers I would want to be able to save data
Thai Kratom scimitar
Publix long
Insert
This one
Accept a user
Save
D user down to the database
How do I
Save a taint
52b database user has an identity defined on it how do I save it
A method to entitymanager.
Buses
What is the method which can be used to make an instant managed
Persistent
And what we want to do is when the user has persisted we want to return the ID of the created one took
User.
This user.
It's something which helps restore things to do
We called that
That's kind of
Compliment as
Repository
Define in Spring framework so you can look at it
Did you type
Indicate something which interacts
The other thing is
When do you want to insert we want to modify something to the database
You need to be inside at
Transaction
What do you need to do is to need to be able to do something like open transaction here open transaction
Make the change
What about changes that you need to do and then close the transaction
Implementing transaction
Pain management in
Each method what GPA provide
Simple
Interface
Declarative transaction
Baby can do that is by saying
Fans action
So you can use this annotation
On the class as well as on the methods we are using javax. Transactional
That's the thing which is
Portage
This says
Each method would be in World in it
Transaction
Important thing that you need to understand
Concept of a
Persistence
And how it relates
With the entity men
If I say user Jack is going to new user Jack
Creator in
Monsters of the user
You're answering another distance
I'm saying entitymanager. Persist
Jack
Enough
Jack is something which is mayonnaise
By the entitymanager
Instant manager is actually a interface to the persistence corn
What is this something that post is Jack what it does
Is it safe to the database and also start
Tracking it in the persistence context
Jack Casino inside
Persistence context
So what do it changes I make 2D Jack
I now being tracked by the persistence context
Important thing to understand is entitymanager only attracts those objects
Which are persistent through it so here including something will Jill and Jill
And I'm thinking.
Change the role of
This would not be cracked
Only those things
Which art in the persistence context
Art
By The Entity manager
So we need to put an annotation
So that this is Oto Y2 what is The annotation its persistence
So I'm going to use an
Java X
Sanitation assistant Sanitation
This is cool right so I have a service
Which is
Having a simple method call insert to save the user know I would want to be able to
Call this and be able to save this data down to the database let's do that in the next