In the step
We would start looking at
Cynthia steffe I set up a simple project
There are things which we need to steal and
Understand about that project
Will understand them as we go
Let's focus on creating a scene
What we want to do is to create an entity
Call
User
Create a simple class
Name it to ask
User
I want to store it in a separate package I would want to just say
Entity
And safe
Guzzi that the user is created in a package called
That's cool so this is where we store all our kin
Disney package with put all identities in
And use it as an example
What do you want to have is
A few attributes in the user so I would say first thing is
And I did so I said
Private private
Long
And I would want to start a couple of
Private
Name
One thing you need to understand is
Deez Nuts lollipop
Design
Because a name might have first name last
Not that stuff so you might
Really need to actually have a class call name
Ideally you'd want to have enum defining that it's keeping simple for now
So let's just have
And I would also generally the
Ghettos and citizen
And stuff like that so what I'll do is
Likely
Source
And say
Generate
Get us insecticide only want
Greatest scientist Tailgators
And say okay
I'll also create a
Should I click source
Send it to stream
And say okay
Generator tostring method for Less
What are you trying to do is to
Genedata simple
Vector
Generate Constructor using
Ideally will not using ID field in the Constructor
Eid I'll just be at the field so we have a constructive in here it's constructed
Two parameters name and roll
One of the things that GPA expects
In every class is
Default
Constructive
So if we create a Constructor like this then we are overriding the default Constructor witches
GPX fix a default Constructor so let's go ahead and Define a simple
Default Constructor
Just like a simple being there is nothing JPS Pacific in it right now
It's a
Simple
Simple account
Specter accepting name in trolls
And it has a couple of Gators and the two string method this is very similar to any being that you did
Define there is nothing
JPS Pacific
To know I would want
Pick this user
And I would want to store it
Stupid table called user in the database
Take the data from user and be able to map it
Wood table
How do I do that
Then I would need to make this end
MDT
So if I want to be able to store this user to a table then what we need to do is we'll need to defer
Entity
As we discussed earlier we're going to use the Java X. Persistence
Daleks doctor disposition CC package with Jawa assistance APA invitations at present
Assistance
You can see that.
What we'll do is we'll also want to say this is a primary key how do I say this is a primary key
By using another annotation called
I d
User has a primary key
Call Adidas becomes the primary key one of the things I would want to do is I don't really want pasta in the primary
So I would want this to be generated
How do I make the stupid generator
By saying
It's a generated value
I'm adding an annotation sing this is
Generated
Simple entity call user
We added an invitation calendar
And we had a couple of invitation Sunday
Ayda field ID and generated
To say that this is something which is generated
Once we have created in
You would need to be able to save this to a database
How do we store entities to database and get
Dim sum the database
We will do that is by using something
Thing Called Love
Entity
In The Next Step could start defining a service
To get these values from the database