In the last few steps we getting it in
And we started managing 8 with
User.
Let's say I want to create another
What I would need to do in that kind of a
The situation is to manage it
Home Depot again going create another doll service
Let's say I would want to create an identity
Screen search
Here I would say some entity
This entity
DUI riding a user data service
It's very similar to some other entity Dell service
So here we are just insulting the data
Consider this scenario Vietnam inserting
I'm retrieving data I'm deleting updating updating and all that kind of stuff
So if I have a lot of methods here then those kind of methods are repeated again and a gain for
All the different entities
If I have 15 entities
I would have $15 so we says we should be having very similar logic to it expecting of The Entity
You have to interact with the entity manager to manage you tell you have tried to call a person's method
Or you would have to call something like a much metal or do you need to call a remove method
Or do you have to call one of the variations of Define
Spring data wants to solve that problem
What thing did I say
If you just Define your interfaces
You can find you a deposit 3 interfaces
And I will take care of implementing them
You should have that I can create a simple Repository
With a small method in the interface
It's been great all provide implementation for you
I'll be able to talk to be entity manager
And do what you would want to specific implementation orthostatic model GPA
Beta
Let's not use spring data jpa to create a Sim
If you do that it's already
S5
New
Interphase
The most important thing is we are creating just
Provide
Interface which is present
Inside the spring data jpa
Repository
Portage APL deposit
When we are extending the jpa repository we need to provide
What is the entity that you'd want to manage
Everyone manages Hughes
Cargo Advantage user
And the other thing I would need to provide
Primary
Radicchio fuse it is
I want to use this
Suppository
From command line when that's what I'll do is I'll go ahead and create another command line.
Cutting the user service user Dallas service
I would actually call this
User Repository
Because it uses the user Repository
I want to change this
I would not want to use user data service I would want to use
Use a repository now
What's up Jack
I would want to listen to Jill from here
A user user
Depository
You.
One important thing about
User repository is the fact that really want to update or in
You would use the same
This would actually return a user back
Will not need to worry about it so I'll say user deposit 3. See
That's enough
I'll stop this
Defecation
Utility Integrity Sapphire twice because we have to run.
We have one. Never just making use of the doubt service the other under which is making use of
Is a deposit
And you'd see that new user has created would be
Twice
You can see that
Jill is also enough
What we did in this step
Is actually
Used a simple
User Repository
Instead of a user douser
Did you deposit the kind of acts as a shortcut
To manage you
Instead of writing a lot of doll services
Very similar logic so you'd have the same insert purses
Stuff instead of using that kind of logic
Spring data jpa provide common abstraction
Call GPA Repository
If you extend
PJP repository and provide the entity you'd want to manage
You'd get all the different methods
Provided a varied range of methods that are provided for
Doing all kind of operations
With you
Interested
You look at one of the operations that closed
What we did from the
Use a repository command line
Is we made use of the safe
Method
That are Define
Spring data
What's the next step