And be creative audio service to manage
I would want to be able to call the dealer service at Sam
One of the things that we have already set up is a simple project which lunches Apple Springs
To this project because we created using spring Boot and uses used in Woodstock
What we can do at the launch of the spring context
We would want to insert a user
How do we do that
There's a concept called command line Runner
Quan text launch SR20 spin context lunges
John Daly need to worry about the Quan texture flight Nerf
I'll let you need to remember
With the fact that this command line Runner launches
When the application starts up so when will we start the application record in the command line for a nugget
Pick your dad's
Let's create a simple command line on alcohol this new class
Chooser cuz I'm talking to the service
User data service
This camera lens rental
I would want it to be managed by spring so I'll say at component
To make it a command line learner I need to
Implement an interface
As you can guess
I can import the camera lens rental in
All I have to give me
I want to implement a run method inside the command line Turner inside this run method I would want to be able to save
The user so I would want to be able to say
User user
Is equal to a new user
I would want to give him a troll off
Edmond
And I would want to be able to do
Opposites
Trellis we are going to be able to save him to the database
How do I save you
I need thee
How to set user data service after the single instance of the usual dealer service I would want spring to order wire
I'm thinking 4. What
That's cool
So how do I do that insert
One of the important things is the fact that desert Dau service also returns
Did back so I don't lose I would want to log
Decide
So I would want to save
To be able to log it I would need a logger so what I do and what I've done is have used the Logo Factory. Get lager
50 specific class
Dog service come in later another class and getting the logger I'm using it
I'm going to use a cell phone
Christopher J
We created a simple August so we can lock the stuff out so now I would say
Log.
Info
And
Hotel
New user
Let's take a quick look back at work
Command line interface
Coming late tonight because we would want this to be at the launch of the
Be added in a user Diego service because that's what allows us
To insert a
We created a user with call insert user and we're logging it that's basically what we have done
Let's launch the application and see what happens
Right-click run as
Job
If you get a port conflict what you need to make sure is that you kill the aliens
Kill. Instances started in you enough to let see what happens
It's starting up
And one of the things that you would see at the startup
In the Lord
Is the fact that it
Prince a new user as a new user is created
User IDs equal to
Is Pleasant in the log so what we are able to do now is we are able to
Boxes for you save something down to the database
Is it fact that we have not really
Created a database yet
How is this magic happening
Where is this data really getting
Where is the database
Do not worry about that
And more in the next
Like we have created a simple entity called user via freezer service call user data service
To be able to manage the user and they're calling their service in the command line Turner's at the launch of the application
Can we are calling disservice
To be able to store the user in NV saw the diesel was created fine. Of magic that is
What's the magic that is happening in the
That's basically what we would look at