In the previous steps we created
We created a command
I have to be able to save the date
Hello
Unanswered question
First one where is the database created
Vanity tables created
So on
So forth
Let's answer all those
The simple answer is only magic is happening
Because of
Spring boot
And
Doctor
Let's open up our pain.
When we created this
Project
Using spring in
Laser
Start. Sting.
Rituals
Important
Joseph Joseph static all started
Guichos hitch
To SD
Database
Let's focus on the
In memory
Database
Its 2
Bia used to databases like
Article
Put on those kind of databases
You need to First
Install them on your machines and create the tables and then
Should be able to save the data from the Apple
This would mean that there's a lot of
In wall
Other kind of database is called in memory database these databases are directly created
Inside the application this commercial Define
The tables are
The entire database is destroyed and removed from memory
The great thing about these databases is you don't really need to maintain them
I don't really need to install manually I don't need to install the tables in there and all that kind of stuff
Application. Property this is where
We can configure this spring boot application
And what I would want to do
Spring
Jpa
.
Show
Chewy
I'm making it
I want to show the SQL which is generated
I've been sitting I would want to turn on
Something about spring.
Hitch 2
Canton. Enabled
Is equal to
I want to see the astrologer 10 rated
And I would also want to enable something called H2O
Let's stop the application and start
You'd see that
Sequence being created and the table being
Creative
The other thing you would see
Is that insert into user
Name Blue Ivy
These are the queries which are being dicks
Executed I can see them now
Because I turned on login for queries I said Stinger jpho SQL to
We can see that the table saw table is created and data is in
Can I see the data in the database
Hey Stoopid
2 -
Cancel localhost 8080 has to concern
Test baby
It's too meme
Samurai Shogun 2
You can leave this as a default if you want to talk like to the agenda catch to embedded
This is DJ DB
Hello Kitty bch to Memphis TB
And I think
Enough
You can see the database you can see the user table
Do you hook a police created ID name and roll
Hindu a select * from its start from it and you can see the real witches
Inserted
What I would recommend you to do
Is to play around with this
We saw that
Is created in
Hitting it stupid
Besotted
Kima also is being created application status
And also
We saw the tables which were created
We saw the data in the database ass
Even then a couple of important questions remain
Creating the data source
How is the schema being generated
Spring boot
Saudi magic the entire magic is done by
Spring boot Auto configuration
To be able to understand spring boot auto-configuration much more
What we lose
Is will turn on
Debug.log
Logging.
String
Spring framework I'm turning on logging level to be
That they see what we're doing
If you look at the log now
Because we turn on debug logging
Deutzia lot more login
There is something called auto-configuration report which is
Ben 10
How do you extract a few things from here
Here's a quick preview of what we observed in
Spring boot is intelligent
H2O on the dependencies list
8 has configured in-memory database
Using hitch to in Murray databases spring boot knows that if you're using an in-memory database
Then you'd want to initialize the schema
He's able to understand whether your database is embedded or not
Okay yo use in a minute
Database uses hibernate property called teardrop
And drops this
Team event.
Number one
The other auto-configuration step that is enabled is
Hibernate jpa auto-configuration
Because we have hibernate on the classpath
Hibernate jpa auto-configuration history guide
Does Adidas switches Auto configured and entitymanager Quan factories Auto configured and the trends
Section manager is Otto Kahn
If you actually look through the log there are a lot of other stuff which is auto configured by
Spring boot what we are looking at some of the important things that auto Con tickets Sunday perspective Jeep
Hibernia
Auto-configuration is a very important
Feature of spring boot
Springboard
What does it
It took some classes which are available in the
Maspeth
It decides
What is the best configuration for you
I'm going to use hibernate with
GTA
So I'm going to
And it also decided that I would want to use H2 as a memory database
And it auto configure the schema for me
And also Auto configure
All this happened in the background
Easily execute
The greatest against the database and insert a user role in
We were trying to on Saturday
Important questions
Where is the database created what scheme
Uist what are the tables created
How can we see the data in the database
How are we getting hibernate data source and all others
Solid the answer to all of this
Spring boot
And the in-memory database
Hits 2
We had to do new project setup
No configuration at all
Using any memory database you don't really need to maintain anything I don't really need to install a database or something of this
This makes it a great combination
For Learning and for writing
The other important thing is with Lieutenant conjugation with some simple configuration in the application to properties
You can actually really connect to SQL database order
Watercolor
The only problem with using an in-memory database
Is the fact that the data is not persistent between restart to as soon as you tell me the application bien
Add schema and the data is lost
In this course at the start we would start using and
In memory database
Because of
Aldi flexibilities
It provides