Welcome to this quick start guide
Spring boot
Spring boot is the most popular framework to develop microservices
Indiscreet start guide
Which
Make spring boot popular
Give me start with creating a simple project using initializer
We'll talk about
Things like
Start the project
Images of various kinds of starter projects in a
Application and also
We'll talk about spring boot actuator to enable monitoring on your app
Application
And
We also we talked about
Have you can become productive
With spring boot
Devtools
Distance tips might not make you an egg
Expert on sting
It would definitely help you to get a
Looking
Let's get started