We will investigate much more
Traitor
How do I go spring boot actuator
Very simple
Just like everything else with
Spring boot
Is an actuator
He's also very very
Good form lyrics
And you have guessed it right so I just need to add
Actuator
And changing the starter
I didn't start of actuators what does the actuator bring
Actually that actually brings in a lot of monitoring
Around you
An actuator should be able to
A lot of metadata about the Epic
Little you want to see what are the beans that are comfy
You want to see
How many times has this week services
Do you want to see
All that kind of stuff
You can check
In your actuator and
Enable that
Something called an actuator
Spring boot starter actuator actually exposes a lot of
E-service services are compliant with the standard called hell
Chuze Cypress
So that we can
2D data
Provided by this
Pregnancy
Portal browser
Spring data rest
Help browser
You can save the project
Boston cream with data
Spring data rest
Albatraoz
Once we add the
Dependency for that
Caltrops
Would be configured among I depend on
Love you can see all day
Independence
What are the important things
To remember is that the actuator urls
Have been changing quite a lot
Across
Spring boot
Spring Boot Barn.
The URL was localhost 8080 / actuator
Later in the earlier versions of
Spring 2.0.0
Lick the Milestone reuses it was called localhost 8080 / application
No I didn't
Bia back to
Ss80 80
Actuator
Teresa turn
Launch of the actuator damages after 2.0.0. Release
The URL is localhost 8080
Flush actuator does not work
And probably you can do
Ss80 80 / application for cry
Once you're typing localhost 8080 / actuator this is what you'd be seeing if you're using anything greater than 2
22.00
UFC 3 URLs coming in
The right to decide be held and the info so if I click health
Dootsie the health of the applications up and running. Cool
Right
And
The other one
There's not a lot of info here right now
There's a lot of stuff that actuator provides
To enable that
You need to configure
Stop
How do I do that you can do that property management
Important
Bossier
Include
Is equal to
What you doing in here
Is Viet enabling / exposure
Exposure over HTTP of Aldi Management in points
What are the important things to remember
He's when you enable
A lot of
Tracking lot lot of auditing
What would
Happen if there would be a performance
Backpacks with
What are the recommendations is to identify which of the things that you'd want and only
Enable doze
But for now we are taking a shortcut.
What are the things you would have already noticed is the fact that if I
Typing control space documentaries
Duty a drop-down coming in
This is because of something called us
Bring tools
You can see that I can see what I do Valley Properties it also validates
Values of these properties and things like that
Be configured management at n Pointe Circle. Exposure. Include is coldest.
Please start
You are at
Application to make you make sure that you stop and start you at
Application
If I'm going to replace the actuator
You see that now
URL such a Pleasanton
TTL coming up in here
I'm thinking typing is localhost 8080
Olivia didn't the house browser
A little bit
The reality the hall brothers so if you type in localhost 8080 to go to the browser and we can use help
To browse through the actuator side actuator in here
Charlotte I need to do is tighten / actuator that you are in for the actuator India
And I can start looking through all the things related to actuator Direct
Look at a few of these things that deactivated is exposing
The audit events related to security
Additive in Food Show
Pictures of work properly validated how many people failed authentication and all that kind of stuff
Vince's and the interesting thing and picking beans
This would show all the spring beans that are cons
He got it right spring
He's a dependency management framework and
It manages all the beans
All the components for you and you can look at all the dean's that
Sting has created for you
You can also check the heads of the application it's a
Conditions is under the interesting thing
As we have discussed Santino spring booties all about
Auto-configuration there is a lot of stuff that the thing built out of containers
Conditions
Service exposes the positive matches
Aldi
Conditions that matched
SMS
If you search for negative matches
The conditions which
Did not match
Play Patrol list of beans which are configured which are not
You can also get the details of constellation properties the environment
Login to check on feet
So you can get a few metrics as well so
If you go to The Matrix
I can see a list of metrics
Which are valid
Tow
Let's say I would want to find out how much memory
Taken so I can copy this
Tavia memories
Dottie West
Tootsie
The value of
Amount of memory.
Same thing can be done with other mix
If I go back
You can see that data out of writing that idea of Netflix
Staying here
CPU usage and all that kind of stuff
But if I go back again to the actuator I can also see
Is stuff
It is an interesting thing called
Till it shows up as request which is coming in somebody
Play taxes the actuator this is the response which bean bag the time taken is so answer
So you can see all the details of the previous
Quest
Earthquake
Executed
The important thing is to remember that this would have
Performance
You cannot enable it in production is useful
A few requests
Obviously you would not want any belated
Place in production for all the requests
Last one standing here is mappings
Mapping
She was all the different
Star map
Do you RM
Play to win a world without creating a web application
Sobeys
Remapping a lot of URLs whenever we are adding dependents
We had a few URL
You can see all the mapping
This video was too quickly give you an overview
What are all the things you can do
Actuator
If some of the information you seen here is
Complex and you're finding it difficult to understand no problem at all the most important thing to understand is Future
If you need any such information
This one place you can go to that
Actuator