Previous step
Do it able to create
Rest service
Really
We will understand
What is auto configuration
How did all the things that are needed
For the rest of us to be up and running get configured automatic
Let's look at it in this step
We have the spring boot in 10 steps application
Wait we have the app
Spring boot application
The annotation at
Spring boot app
Application indicates that disease
Spring context file that's number one
Number to it enables
Something called auto-configuration
Number three
It enables something called
Components
Companies can is one of the important features of
The classes in this package
And this sap package
Any
Beans
Sobe have adenine and
Annotation at rest controller
One of the annotations
Which is
Stand
Portuguese would be registered as a components of the book controller
Would be registered as a bean and it would be managed by this
Spring frame
Three things that are essentially done
By The Edge spring boot application
15 kids
The second thing
Is the fact that
This enables auto-configuration
The third thing is that
It enables automatic scan orta specific
We want to look at
Auto-configuration in depth
Green contacts
As an input to it and it would be able to run that
Runmeter also return something so it returns
Application context
Actually
Deadly application count
Baxter
I'm getting verification contacts back
I'm outta application, I would want to look around itself for each
Control one
SpaceX
I would want to loop around
Application context
Get me
I want to get the names of all the
And I would call this
Name
And
I would want
Jesus is
Taking a shower curtain ideas
Amylase
If you guys I would go ahead and
All the beans with chocolate Center
Let's see what would happen
Jalopnik
I'm getting an interesting it
They just act because
ADT Zone videos let's see
It's already being used
And let's do
Did a lot of things that are printed right now so
There are a host of things that I getting configured first automatically
How are these being caught
That's basically the feature called Auto country
Spring Buddhist is a spider
Springboard
Green book
There is something called Spring boot Auto configure so if I look at
One of the dependencies
Spring boot
Auto configure
And this spring boot Auto configure
Has a lot of logic
Built into it so you can see that there is a lot of classes that are
Look at the auto-configuration
It's a very very very big
For all the things that we are looking at right now
I'm going in to the auto configure website
And you'd see something call dispatcher servlet auto-configuration
These auto-configuration classes are what are
Creating these
Start up
Is the spring boot
DreamWork would trigger the auto-configuration jar
So you could see that okay
Do I have a specific class on the class fat
Poopsie that have a spring web MVC framework on the glass
What does this mean
Put on concealer do
It says there is prepared NBC on the Quan
Casper
Then I would need to configure a dispatcherservlet
Spring Bourbon Whiskey on the glass part so I would need to configure View resolver
All those kind of things
Happen
And you'd be able to see
All
Beans which are
Creative
In here
Spring boot basically looks like two things one is free books available on the Grass Pad
Is a
Vertical spring boot tutorial. Com
May we have a lot of articles on Spring boot I'm referring to an of the eye
And also be it looks like the existing beans which are configured for the app
Application
Vision.
Provide
The configuration needed so for example if you're using a bad starter
Basic things that you would need would be a dispatcher servlet
You need a
Probably some internationalisation you need some messaging
All that kind of stuff would get Auto configured for you
We are looking at one of the auto-configuration beans which is datasource auto-configuration
If you see the code of datasource auto-configuration which is inside this thing pulled out of configure jar
Tootsie that it's conditional on class data social class and embedded database type. Class two people
Visit Dundee classpath
Then this Pacific Dean would be created being would be only created
Wendy's are on the class but you can see the code in here so they should be sourdough configuration is conditional
On
A specific class being available on the class
You can also see another example in the database configuration
This is
Only created when there is no data source
Weather is not being created with a data source RX8
If you want to find out more about what auto-configuration is
It's happening
What we can do is we can turn on
Debug logging
What I can do is good application. Properties
That's 25 weeks present in here
We talked about application properties
I'm turning onto login level I'll let you need to do is say login
Framework
Is equal to
This would start the application in a debug mode let me kill this application again
You can see a lot more blogging being printed right
Right now so a lot of things have been printed
Along with
Dude actually have a lot of logging about water conservation
Say all this stuff
And which was not a token ticket racing dispatcherservlet auto-configuration has
Because I found something
Of this kind Indica Hospital thing
I found a cervical dispatcherservlet on the glass part to have configured
Dispatcherservlet automatically
I've already considered
Default error controller
I've considered a cash debit cash configuration
AppBounty
Jackson for doing binding
And a autocon ticket validation as well
You can also see that there are things like glue dissolver and everything that we're Auto Contigo.
Not only that
The auto-configuration report also shows what are the things that were not Auto configured signature
Why the rest of the auto-configuration things
Did not match
Invite
They were not
White beans for Denver not
Auto-configuration is a very very important concept regarding spring boot
One of the most important things to end
Understand is
You are still a big Nowitzki
And auto-configuration is something which will grow on you
As you keep building more and more
Spring boot application
If the complete concept of order
Constellation did not fit in your mind right now that's not a problem at all
You would definitely learn
By the time you end this
One of the fundamental
Hawaii
Boot is
So famous
And so is
In this step
We looked at the basics of auto-configuration
We look at some of the beans which would automatically be created and also
Beluga
Where the code for Spring boot auto-configuration
I think the next step