And before we
Go any further I think it would be great
If you can
Beauty Supply
What are differences between spring
Spring MVC
And spring boot
I think having great clarity on that
Would be
Really wonderful
Spring MVC
How do they compare
That's basically what
Filled wontons
In this passage
Actually by the end of this
You would understand that
Spring spring MVC and spring boot
Have their own rules
They're not really competing for the same spot
Diesel
Really different problems
And they solve them really really well
Pink rainbow
Cool problem Springfield
Salt
Sweet
You don't Define property
Dependencies Danielle equations are not testable
The most important feature is
Dependency injection
Coral Spring framework is the ioc
Inversion of control
Spring framework
Takes control of
All the beans
And their dependents
That's basically what the spring frame bookcase about
Spring framework is all about
Defining your beans
Putting you at company putting your at service and things like that
And Ultra defining your dependencies at autowired and things like that and also
Defining
Basically
The core problem that spring framework Salt Spring framework solves the problem of
Dependency injection it healthier to build
Loosely coupled applications
Loosely coupled applications can be easily unit tested
If you look at this example
You see that welcome service instances directly
Created in here this tightly coupled welcome controller is not tightly coupled
Could you welcome service
Hollywood
If you do dependency injection properly
Then you would Auto wire it in
You can use Facebook's like macchiato
And Mark spring MVC
To replace the service with a Mach
The main problem that
Other than that spring framework also salts a few other problems like duplication
That's basically plumbing code
So if
Lips are you using
Jdbc then you needed to write a lot of boilerplate code
Try catch exception and all that kind of stuff
When you use any of the things that are based on the string trimmer spring jdbc order
Spring JMS you don't really need to do that kind of stuff at all
The other thing
Spring framework Saul was providing good ending
Vision without the frame box spring
Had good integration with hibernate for orm
Concerned with developing
Vibe app
Applications
Spring MVC
Provides
Great thing about spring MVC is the separation of concerns
Dispatcher servlet
Concerned with
The basic fan controller parts
There's a model in view
There's a Beauties on the way which is concerned just with resolving
Of you name
Physical View
With this kind of simple concept
Spring MVC makes it very very easy to develop your web applications
As well as you have a restful services
Whether you open web applications or web services with spring boot internally you are using
Spring MVC framework
That's disturbing web MVC
Why do we need spring boot
That we have talked a lot about in this
Pacific Coast
Play the last few steps be
Saw the need for spring boot right we don't want to be fun figuring things like that be a contributing bruises all over
We are configuring dispatcher servlet
If you're using
Hibernate jpa we need to configure data source entitymanager
Transaction manager and lot of that kind of stuff
Spring booties
Why do you need to do all this configuration can we delete things different
The thinking of springboard is
This guy has added a spring MVC jobs
Can I configure some of the beans automatically
Can I consider dispatcherservlet automatically for you
Can I contact automatically for you
How many points is a data source
If I hibernate jarasandha classpath
I know she put cabinet gas in the gas but because he wants to talk to a database
Why don't I automatically create a data source
The auto-configuration by Diplo
Glass pot
And provide automatic configuration
New starter projects are all built around well-known patterns
We we talk about
Spring boot starter web
And it's been good strategy. In the next
Other than status
Important goals of springboard
To provide a few monitoring
Starters like
Good starter actuator
Which is used for monitoring so it enables monitoring for your application and also
He does. Go stupid
Different embedded servlet container
Anita starters for
Logging so if you want to use log4j dessert
Separate login for it
I hope this
Spring MVC
In the next step
We would focus