Welcome back
In the steppe food look at
Does smooth look at a couple of examples.
Spring boot
Start a web
And spring boot
Strategy
If you open up the poem.
10 minutes of the project that we have
You would see that
Choosing spring boots
Taco Bell
How did its
You spin with Sarah Webb
That's because we configured a dependency on web
If I opened it up
And go to the pond or XML
Juicy.
Distinguished data web is configured
To distinguish staticweb is the preferred starter for spring boot to develop web applications
As well as
Restful web service
Command and
Open phone. XML first in good starter web
Cutesy
That it defines
Very
Kind of dependency
So what does it really Define
Wyndmere ND
Automatically using
That's because of this
Spring boots
Dr. Tomko
If you look at Springwood staticweb
It contains a d
Dependency on Spring boot starter Tomcat
And that's how
The application is automatically running
In Tomcat
The other things
You'd seen here at Spring and spring WebMD
Spring MVC sua
Spring MVC framework
Spring boot static web I automatically get spring MVC I automatically get validation validation
The default implementation for
Java validation API is hibernate
Data so I get that as well
And I get
Tomcat
And also
I get
Dr. Jason decided this more for restful web services
We saw that when we actually
Envogue be restful web service conversion to Json automatically happen
Elizabeth Cote
You just returned the bean bag
In the Box controller what we're doing is we're just returning a list of beans that
It done
Through this title
The start of Jason brings in Jason binding
Into the picture
Basically when you look at all starter projects
They have a set of dependencies that
Are already
And these dependencies
Automatically provided to our projects would start over
I get all this dependency so you'd see that
I'm getting Jackson for handling all the Jason stuff you'd see that I'm getting Tomcat
So if I can find the application in Tomcat I'm getting
Hibernate validator and validation API
For doing the evaluation and getting the spring framework because I have a
Dependency on Spring web and that would have a dependency on Spring framework
And also
Logging Frameworks as well because the logging Frameworks are
By default Define in the spring boots
Titus has been good Saturday is one of the dependencies in Spring boot starter web
This is the default starter
This is where everything inherits from so any started that you would use
In Spring boot
18 headed from Spring boot starter
And you see that decided dependency on Spring boot framework this as a dependency on Springwood autoconfigure
That's how we get our configuration
That's how we would get logging
And we have
Dependency on Spring
RSV
Yamill is one of the convocation languages that spring boot support
So we also have sneaky animal
Think about something good starter webos once
Abramson all this dependencies
What would kicking auto-configuration wood
Kicking because
Spring Grove MBC contains dispatcherservlet to automatically dispatcherservlet would be configured
That's done by
Spring boot Auto configure.
The auto-configuration which we talked about earlier
We would start a web is one of the starters
You can see him here is spring boot starter test
So if I go to the pond or XML in here
He would see
That it has a definition of spring boot test
Definition of the article
And it has dependencies on Jamie preamble
Sog
And also
You have monkey tomohito is the default
Mocking framework that comes along with
Spring boot
A combination of
SOG and ham Bristol
Awesome to light green
And you also have a dependency on this
Spring test
Framework which is useful in writing unit test for spring
Good couple of starters
Beaches
Good starter web
And spring boot
Other than that another important Charter which is frequently used spring boot starter JP
If you know GPS GPS kind of the interface
Hibernate so dep Define
How warm applications
At what time frame book
What time is object relational mapping
Let you know adding a dependency on Spring boot strategy
You would see now that there would be a lot on my mind dependency switch would come in
Transaction API hibernate
You have spring data spring data jpa
Dingle Ireland
Spring TX
And a lot of such dependence
That's because of the spring boot
Strategy
Hey if you open up the phone lyrics Milford spring boot strategy PA
Then you'd see all the
Get down to this as a dependency on Springwood Saturday Opie status jtbc
Spring data
All this Jazz you'd get
I'll get all this
For free
One of the things you need to remember
Is if you are a starting programmer or this is
The first time you are looking at Spring boot a lot of things my
Confusing to you
Especially because we are referring to
Problems for
Variety of Frameworks
So Perla
Terminologies that come into picture when we talk about springboard
So if you're not able to understand any of this terminal just do not worry at all
What's the cause of this
Course
And also over the course of your next few years
So that those don't know just become really
Ikea for you
The idea
For you is
To understand the big picture of what springboard does
Spring boot is now
One of the most
Popular Frameworks to develop microservices
The idea behind the whole set of these steps
Is it gives you a
Flavor of spring boot in wide variety of scenarios
If you're not able to understand a couple of scenarios. Not a problem at all
I look forward to see you in the next step