Let's look at my favorite feature running
And I'm making a change yes I'm changing the washing screen
5.0 to 5.1
Services
Build retaining 5.0
To pick up the change I don't need to stop the server
And
If he started again
And that's cumbersome isn't it
Starting episode
Take a few steps
It would take a few seconds and that would waste my time
How can I get
The whole thing to be loaded automatically
As soon as I make a cool change
How do I do that
That's weird
Spring boot developer tools come in
It's
An awesome dependency I love it
Put it below test
Spring boot
Call Spring boot
Dev
I just added a dependency on to Spring boot devtools
It's as simple as that
I'll read the whole
So you can see that it
It's downloading.
Dependencies
Dark history project
And now pay
Want to start this over
You can see that the seller is loaded
I'm so excited and now executed
Why do guys have
Decided decided
But the great thing from now on is any Java changes that you make
What would happen if I exclude this one of the things you would see in the log is that the application is
Restarting automatically
5.0
This time let's focus on what's happening in the log
I just
Clear of water log is there
And I'm making a change
Mastering spring 5.1 headset
At the time of creating this video
Having fun
You can see that this specific thing is also very efficient at David Lee stats
You can see that this actually started in
Who was second to change was picked up
In 2 seconds
Stop the application
Restart it
You would see that actually
The typical restart Van Nuys
Do a fresh restart
One Steamboat is about
8 to 10 seconds
So this is taking about 9 second 35
Stop and restart the application it's taking about nine seconds
Hello
If I just make a change directly here
What I do that
Turn this off
Also
Just look at how much time it takes
Turn off how much time did it take
You can see that this actually takes to win the second
Pretty cool isn't it so
What are the things that
Sting Buddhist Springwood Turtles that's very effectively
Is it knows that everything in the madman dependencies
Will not change at all
So you cannot load things which are dependent on these
It would only load those beans which of the which of the application beans again that's why I take slessor
Time when you make a change
Manually start December everything including water is in here is loaded
But when you reach
When you make a change in the application
Only that specific things which are applications related
RV loaded again and that's the reason why you see that it only takes
2 seconds
And imagine the amount of productivity you gain weight
Took this is almost 10 seconds saved
Food every change you make
If you are maintaining any kind of application
That's a big productivity booster if you're using a spring boot application and if you're not using
Dinglederper tools
Then go ahead and try it
Industry
We looked at Spring boot devtools which is one of my favorite additions to springboard
Next video