One of the best things to do
To understand the beauty of
Spring boot
Is to understand how things were done
Before spring
Beauty look at one of the projects which we developed in asking him
Before we start with any project we need to decide what Frameworks and dependencies
This was a bad project
So we would want to use spring MVC and things
Looks like that
So we needed to make
Decisions on what Frameworks
Questions of dental
We need it to decide
How do I use
Springboro BMV
Add Spring Security web Spring Security config
I want to use Jackson databind because I want to do some binding and validation
I would want to use jstl
End
I want to use hibernate validator
And also app for logging I would want to add a new outside
We have to decide what dependencies to add into our project
Not only that
We need to decide
Big portions of them as well
Sometimes
This 5.0.2. Final version might not be compatible with some other version of spring MVC
So you needed to decide what are the compatible versions
Using them
Choosing the Frameworks to use
And which potions to use is a major.
Decision that we needed to make when we were not using
We needed to implement
Default exception Handler
You can see that here
Which adjusting implementing simple
Default
Exception Handler
And
We need to create a
Complete
Spring configuration
Then we would need to
Quincy girl Abdul dissolver
Foodydirect abuse to a JSP
To implement internationalisation
Benedetto
Implement a message source
And also a local resolver
And in addition to that
We needed to configure our web. Xmls well
We need to configure the dispatcher servlet in web.xml so that it can handle all the requests
And act as a friend controller
We need to configure the context configuration location in here
End
And make sure that it intercepts all the requests
There's a lot of bug that you need to do to get a simple web application up and running
And a lot of others
All the stuff with
We looked at In this passage
Escape is the kind of stuff
You don't need
To do with
Spring boot would automatically provide all that stuff
So that you can really concentrate
On developing your business logic
All the infrastructure
Would come
Free
To give you an idea of
Duvall
Before spring
Directly jump into spring boot you might not really appreciate
Values at Springboro
All the stuff which we looked at in this specific example
Would be replaced
Beta simple starter project
Call Spring boot
Start a web
In combination with
Spring boot
Start the security
Just a combination of.
Starters
What element did lead for
A lot of configuration
That we looked at in this Pacific
You look at those charters
And a lot more about spring boot
Indosat
Until then