Understanding magical springboard further
Let's create a simple rest controller
Temperature
Service at 1 to create a recipes with
Spring Lake
Flash books
And I would want to return a few hard-coded books since
The Tomcat
Tran Thanh port 8080 by default
That's what we saw
Port 8080 DUI would be something like
HTP
://
Localhost
: 8081 to return if you had called it books
Before we go to rest controller let's create a simple beam so I create a new class
Anacondas
Mix margarita maker
Not complex I'll just say
Name of the book and string
Arthur
Lesbian copies and things like that but let's keep it simple let's just have
These options which are present in this group
In the book
It's on Socratic instructor
Quickly
Also I would want to create the Guitar Center.
I don't really want to create a status but I would want to add indicators
Sendera added in and Allied in a two string as well
You have a simple being defined right now so we have a bean with ID name
Best controller
So how do I create a best controllers on a Java class and I would want to call this
Books controller I would want this to be a rest controller I would want it to serve request address request sorry
Need to use annotation
Pallets in Portage in
I would want the map but you what I do it
Lake lytal D1 which I want a map is/
So I would want to match / books of an hour
I want eight
2D tennis set of hard-coded books
So how do I do that
That's by
Mac
I'm mapping a get URL so I'm not going to get URL for
Type of the request
You understand his City. Then you'd know that there are multiple types of HDPE methods right get
Delete
Get is typically used to retrieve data
So I would want to use get
Let's create a method soap public
And I would want to turn a list of books back
Guitar
Calimport
Java.
Enough
I can actually
Wheaton
A simple
How do I create a book so I sent you
Book
I'll use an idea of one
And I can use one of the recent books out of their tent so I'll say
Mastering spring
5.0
Is the name of the book
And
Authored by
Manga katana
Or liquid
Very very very simple things
A descontrolar method would handle a get request
But this specific URI what we're doing here is
We are actually returning a book
We can actually return multiple books if you would want to I was just wanted to keep it simple
And I just wanted to return
One book
I would actually go ahead and now started so
Underneath a job application spring boot
In 10 steps application
So what has started up
Send in the log you can see
That
I will mapping has also been picked up directly
So you would see
/books get method is mapped onto the method which we don't get all books
To let's see what would happen when I asked you the request
8080 /
Books
You can see the
Silver respond back
With a Json response is a Json response Heidi one name is Mustang 5.0 authorization.
To this
Request is actually returning back the details in a Json format rest service
Imagine a part of the whole thing is the fact that
We have directed Focus
On
Creating device service that's what
Spring boot aims to enable we have not focused on any of the introduction
Stuff we did not focus on
Some beans are
We did nothing
What
Magically
Disservice
Starts working
How does this happen
That's what we would learn
In the next few steps