They come back
Instead we'll get the big picture of
What are the goals
What's been good is not
What are the steps
Today
YouTube developing large moonlit applications
We are building a lot of
Centra billing one big
Application reopening 2025 maybe 50 smaller
Microservices
One of the important things with these microservices
Is you'd want to be able to build them quickly that's where
Spring boot comes in
Spring boot has gained a lot of ground
It has quickly become
Number one framework to develop microservices in the Java world
How did
Spring boot achieved
That's where we would discuss about the goals
And the importance
What are the most important goals us
The most important goal of spring boot is to
Enable building
Direction radio applications
Quickly
The other important goal is to provide all the common non-functional
Ambulette service
Mexico
Hand externalized
We've talked about this
Features a little
These are the two
Important goals of
To enable you to quickly build applications
And also provide common
Non function
Before we go
You also need to understand what spring booties
Some people call Spring boot as a cogeneration
Vito cogeneration
And that's what makes
This concept
Ghillieglade
The second thing is
Spring boot provide great integration with embedded servers
Lake Tomcat
By itself
Spring boot
Is not a web server
It's not an application so
These are two things that you need to remember there's no coordination with spring Boot and spring boot is neither an application server
North of that
So what
List of the goals and also understood what spring booties
Look at Hot Spring boot achieve
The most important
Spring boot
Is this concept called
Start up
It's lit say I want. The weather condition I would need spring MVC
How did Supreme Court
I would need some validation framework
I would need some logging framework
In addition to that
I would need to configure all the stuff that is needed
Example if I'm using spring MVC I will need to configure dispatcherservlet I'll need to configure View dissolver and
A lot of things like that
Spring boot starter project
It becomes very easy
Or that you need to do is to add a starter call Spring boot start a web into your project
And that's it
You get the embassy for free you get to drink coffees you get a validation framework for free
And also a logging framework for
4 GPA
Dentist article
Spring boot
Start a GPA
When we use the starter
You not only get GPS but also default implementation of jpa
Hibernate and also auto-configuration of.
So you would not need to worry about the flame
And you can directly start
Creating you
Are the important feature we already talked about is embedded server
I'm developing a web application
I would want to deploy it
Onto a Linux box
In the olden days the way it used to work is
I need to install the Linux box
Then I would install Giovanni and then I'll need to install a web server so I wouldn't eating chili the Tomcat
And then I will take my application what
And deployed
This is the usual baby used to deploy stuff
Which springboard comes a concept called embedded server what you can do is you can package USA
Package store
Along with your application jar
So I can include
The Tomcat
Silver
In my application jar
So I don't need to install it
On the Linux box
All that I need to do on the Linux box
Is if I have Java installed that sufficient I can go ahead and run my application
I don't need any other server installed on the Linux box
This makes a huge
Difference
And also
A number of production-ready
Springboard provides monitoring for you app
Application through something called Spring boot actuator
For example you can find out how many times a particular service
Is called
You can find out
How many things of ridiculous service
Failed
And also you can check whether the application is up and running or not
All these features
And important feature.
Spring boot what is externalized configuration
The consecration of applications varies between different environments
Spring boot provides these features
You can simply create property files
Matching a simple naming convention
End
That's it
You got to ready with
Externalized configuration
Spring boot also provide support for different profile
Important goals
Beaches of
The idea behind
Used to understand the big picture of spring boot
What it is
What is not
And what are the importance
In the next steps
Beauty
Deeper into each one of these
Until the next step