Welcome back
In the step will create
Spring boot project
And look at all the magic
A simple starter project can provide
If you can create a
Springboard project
East by going to start. Ping. IO it's very simple
Starbucks bingo
Guess what Google search for swinging flies are you forgiven
. spring. IO
Once you are here
Need to choose
How to use Maven as my Bluetooth
Jawas language
You can use any version of spring boot which is greater than 2.0 I use 2.000 Snapchat
They would be greater version of 2.0
You can choose any of those abortions
And I would need to configure it
A name for my project just like you give up
Last name and a package name to each class
You need to give a group ID and the artifact ID to each mail
Maven project
I'll go ahead and give that to call.
In 28 minutes
Spring boot
And icons
In
You can add
Start a project makes it very easy
22 Savage
Died that's who you need to use spring boot starter web
Sam adding a vet star that you can see that in here so you can see that there's a very bad it in in here
You can go ahead
And generate project
Once you keep gender project
A zip file would be downloaded to your downloads
What I would need you to do
It's addicted zip file
Unzip it
To any folder
On your heart
And no down
Cat folder
Ice Age ended project
This will download a zip file
I have
To a folder on my hard disk in 28 minutes get
Getting started in 5 Steps
Spring boot
10 steps
Actually invited to any folder or newer
Local
Hard drive
I was going to
Eclipse and inferred that project so what I do is fine Imports
Existing Maven project
And you can write a piece
Activate you
I'm addicted to or you can use the browse to browse to that specific data clean
Either of these things
Should be fine
Once you're able to successfully sell directly
Ipsy spring boot in 10 steps
So I'll go ahead and click
Condition of
What would happen in the background is now of eclipse would look at
The maven configuration and start downloading all the other stuff that
So you would see that
It would start to download
All the dependencies and all that kind of stuff
This is the first time using spring boot then this might take a little while might take a few minutes for the whole configuration
The creation of the project
The interesting has come
Enough
If you look at it right now
This is the project to testing
We have a full local Source Mandela where all our Java code is
Aziz
Resources folder
Application. Properties we talked about it a little later
Sisters Java House
Other than that
You should see a lot of Mammon dependencies to check coming in you can see
Had a wide variety of
Dependencies that are coming in right now
You look at
A little later
Enough
Let's see if you're able to start this application app
Try to open up
Spring boot
In 10 steps
Application
And I would
Right click
Coronavirus
Job application
Actually we have not really implemented Anacortes search
So there is nothing that
Is implemented right now
Olympia looking for is to see if the
So what has started fine
Tootsie something like this
Started
Springboard
Intensification in 8 Seconds
And if you looked at
The details
All the log you would see that there are a lot of things happening already
The most important part for the fact that you have Novell application
Up and running
You look at
Different things which are present in this log
And understand what is happening in the background
A lot more
In the future steps
Until then