Wake up
Quality Hello World Service
Start focusing on calling the helloworld beam
It's an easy thing to do
You can even tried as an exercise you can possibly do in here and give it a try
Let's go
We'll start with the Halliwell so he's what we need to do over here is actually start with a
XU helliwell service and
Nicholas acutiloba
Right
Edible paint that looks cool
I get the Halloween being serviced
Anybody comes compliments
That's not
Really
Create a new button and do that all stuff again
What is altezza three
Welcome message
How do you copy paste this
Coming to South
And what we lose over here
Exit Halloween beans
You get the response
And the response and we are also trying to set guessing welcome message as a sponsored data
I don't think I do is actually try and log into control
DOT log
Respond
Let's
What's happening is it
Yes it again object into welcome message why is it happening that way
Let's look at
Beacon Soul a little bit more
Let's look at the response which came back
The data if you look at it
Is actually
A message
Hello Buzz
So there is nothing but now a Json response response that comes back is
A Json response
And that's the reason why the heck is complaining
Olivia
You cannot
Call Jay
It's not really
A simple strain
So what we can do to get the value from it is actually do or. Message
So what
We can actually do now it's over here
Do response. Data.
Send data and data contains. Message
Select data that message would give you the thing and it would set the right messaging to this tape let's look at it right now.
Go to the night to do the application
If you check the network that we would see that
The appropriate Christian
If you want to be delicious
I can actually
LOL
Play funny going to restart pick it up or you can manually stop and decide if it's not being picked up
Go ahead
Empty that Tyler will be missed
Etsy Whitney change
Save this
What day did SV call Lee Hollowell be in service this evening or hello world into this
Blitzwinger proper Json response back and we saw that manages Investments comes back and we are displaying it as is
React start complaining it says you can understand object directly and that's why
Because
Structure of the Json message we know that invitation through something called message
So he picked it up and set it into this date
I see you in the next