In this video
Quickly evaluate a few best practices
Ingress full services
Andy last best
Practice
Consumer first
Always
How to clear idea about who you are consumers are is it a web application
You expect a mobile application coming in in a future and have a 2-year idea of what they want
Before you name your resources thing from the perspective of your customers
What do they think about those resources will they be able to understand the naming of your resources
The simpler it is for your consumer to understand your services
The better it is for you
Last
But not the least
Track is one of the most popular documentation standards for restful apis
What was standard you are using
Make sure that your consumers understand the documentation that you produce
Next important best practices
Make the best
Use of whatever
Slf services
Based on http
Make the best use of the request methods use the right request method appropriate
For us Pacific
Get post put and delete
And ensure that you're sending a proper response to text back
When did the bad request when did Isabel Edition
Not send send a bad request 400
When you create a resource
Do not send your faxes
Same created by
Think about what is the appropriate response status for your situation
Ensure that there is music info.
Sustained in your URI
Things like Assassin
Just don't go by
Distended definition
Think about what you're putting in the URI and make sure there's nothing
Secure
That's going in your eyes
Always
Plurals
Alicia / users
I need a suicide pact created was last year's / what not / user /
I'd really
Preferred using computers because more readable
Then using a singular
When you think resources
Pink nouns
User
Account
It's not delete it's not delete account
About nouns when you talk about resources think about nouns
Hello
Thinking about now is all not always possible right there are always exceptions search link on
How do you do that
All these exceptional scenarios
Have a consistent approach
You're searching through something
Then if you're searching through Jesus didn't say
/search
Tuan
The action define
For example
These heaux GitHub does a star on the gifts
So if I put a star on the gist
GitHub sensory Quest is today
Results of the gist
It's in the put request
And this evening and start something this is the request
Which goes out to approach of how you'd want to handle the exception scenarios things that don't fit into
What we do in this step
Some of the best
Most important thing
Consumer