Welcome
In the previous step we got our
Retrieve through service
Up and running so we have it running in the back end
And is it a Titans back
We have our friend trains
Hard-coded right now so what do you want to do this we would not want to show they had credit to dispute want
Picture Doodles which are coming from the back end
How do we do that
Little. In the step
Dislike the Halliwell Services responsible for getting all the helloworld details from the apis
APA components
What are Luzon College
Data
Who is Calista dataservice.org world one also
All that you need to do is do a class
To do data service
B12
Export
By default
Instance of this
Go to the Hollywood service
Copied import
And let's go PD
Ixigo Delaware Service as well
Do you want to visit 3 Vol 2 deuce
How tall is Method as retrieve
All
Toulouse
And what is the weather like we want to call
We wanted to be customizable for user so what do I do
Sac City
Bill pass in the name as a parameter
And it's a hard coating this in here let's use
Dollar
3 + 6
So let's use that as well
So we have to receive all tools method ready
Be happy to do that.
Being exported out
Let's use it in our
Where do we need to use it
Videos of indebtedness company Android
List of companies baby would want to use it
Data service
From
Little tricky import right we already did that before
Da.
Clash API
/
Accessories
Duck
React defines of predefined lifecycle
For each of these components
Savannah component is being initialized what is the person that is called
Constructor
Something easy continent changes when out-of-state into continent changes and Dubuque has to be updated
Because it would be called
Did Ender method would be called
There is one method which is called
Blind
Component
It's loaded for the first time and shown on the browser this process of actually putting the component
Browser is called mounting
Animated name is
Component
Mount
Componentdidmount
If you hold out this you see that
Call immediately after.
Component is mounted best practice
Suggested in react
When you're calling an API it's better not to do the initial API call directly in
Deconstructor what happens if you do the initial a vehicle in concert at the state will not be initialized until the APA code
Is completed and that's not a good state to be in what we can do is initially we can set it to some
Empty state
Take it to initially The To Do List is empty
So I can actually
Comment
This out commenting
The entire thing all you feel such a present in here all the hard coded stuff that they had
The business now is empty
So what happened nothing is showing the initial render will happen with an empty list
And once his confidence is rendered
What you want to do is actually make the call today
API
So It Begins Lord of De todos
We can make sure that the component is rendered and it's not really waiting for the data
From the API and once once the data is
Populated again component will be rendered
Let's look at what happens right now so incompetent did Mount
What not to do to do
Data service.
What do you want to do
Retrieve all todos
And do you want to pass
The name how can we get the name Salman to get the name of the user West login how can I do that
We can use the authentication Service
Important location service in
Import
Authentication Service
.
I can call
Username
Is equal to
Actually there is nothing which returns a username
San Carlos
Login
Yusuf
And
If username is not then I'll return empty back
Alton
Username
And I'll go here make use of that specific methods.
Get logged in user name
I can use the username of the logged in user
Tanfastic to retrieve all tools
What I need to do
What if it's successful
What do I want to be successful
Think about it when we did do a company
What to do now is replaying Define the methods right here
It's not trying to create a new method
It's fine Define the state update
Staticky
Down here
So what do you want to do
You want to take the response
And
Listen to respond
We would want to do something I'll put it quitting
This is because that's the method body
Let's just login
Let's see what happened to Agnes
It's 250 pages to make sure to write
Why
Because
We need to add this
Need to do Resource as well
April
Biloxi Beach
You can see that I'm getting the data back did is being printed in the console and
You can see that
That's good
So now we can use the data from the respondent it into the state
Now what I can do is come in this
And actually
This.
I need to Define an object
What's the name of the variables
Toulouse
Truth
Restaurants
.
Data
When you refresh the page you would see that the two details are properly populated
Stab and see details
You see that the request is tropical is coming back
What we have done in this basic steps
Is he created d
Through data service
350 to do data service veip limited a method in their called
Dixie wall to do
We went to the list of this company and in a lifecycle method called componentdidmount
Made a call to B3 service
Reset the data which came back into this date
Let's dig a little deeper into the lifecycle methods
So let's see what happens behind the screens when is Constructor called when is componentdidmount called
Look at that boy