Welcome back in the previous steps
We talked about this access scenarios what happens if there's an added what happens if the service comes back
Sienna response to repeat that what I'll do is actually
Make the service
MC
Something
What's wrong
Making
It return
Not sure what happened music video keyboard
Could you see that any Quality Service you get an exception back
What do we need to do
What we can do is actually sexist with a sponsor we can Define unethical
Handle
For now let's just do a
Cancel. Log
It's not really about the states right now
What time is it
Tedious
Honda letters
And the letters
911 to this we already know how to do that. Catch
Handle
At
Hand
This is how we can actually map the error
And let's see what would happen
It's going to be cancelled
Oops it says
Request failed with
Status code
I want to get a little bit more details about this address as I cancel. Log a Target response
Let's see what happens
I can see this picture
The error response which is coming back
I want to actually die
Message to the user
So what I can do
Go to data and take the message from it
Response. Data
. message would give me something went wrong right at the messages just coming back from the service I would want to show that to the
As an error message in here
So I can say this or text it
Actually not respond to any more attacks
Start response
Data
Is that right
Message which is better
As a message
When you came to get this message and you can see something went wrong in theaters
I'm actually showing it as if it's a response from the message what I recommend you to do is that you
Deep at the top of the page
I'm have a
Play some de Frontera messages and customize it as an adult
And over here
What you can do if you can actually set steak
Another message
As that specific thing so you can do that
What year did message using the same
We saw
How do you can handle Arabs
If you make igtv call Anderson
How you can handle it
Actually
I'm coming. Come in the exception
And
Go back to the earliest date
Tonight we have everything working
Cricket welcome message MSC
LOL in 20 minutes
Locksmith steps in focused on calling all the Hello World apis
And you are sexy to be able to do that
Any subsequent steps
What do you want to do this we would want them get to the two deuce
We want to get the refund stuff
I need to build abs and get the data for them
Restart do that in the subsequent steps