Welcome back let's get started with creating the update service
You can call the update service
Let's go to eclipse
We need to start with E to do hardcore at service to create the updated method
What is
Let's create a methadone here
It is public
And I'll Calista
Send
Say method is used
To do what the update and the inserts as well
I just need to do is minus one
Is -1
Vietnamese food want to insert it in letter
What do you want to do
Is
When did Ali have a good to do
With a different ID
What do we need to do you want to update it
This is just a static list to make it
Easy for us to be able to do the update is bicycling delete by ID
Get
True. Specificity and Ivan
Add new to-do in
I said to lose.
So what would happen
Delete today's deleted and the new to do is
So I'm kind of taking a shortcut in here
Good want to add
Peppa can you do with an ID - indictments
I want to admit to doing but before that
What city ID
Plus plus
Heidi Compton
And in all the cases what we'll do is we'll return
The updated to do is to
Add on YouTube when I'm adding you to do I'm just in committing the counter and adding 18
When
I have to update it then what I'm doing is supposed to eat and then adding it
Updating
Deleting it end up getting it in
Let go to the resorts and create Buddha methods will create one method to do the ad and one
Message to do the update
We already have the
Details parade
Through resource we decided this earlier
So let's go ahead and pasties into to edit we want to use a put
And to create a new to-do
Do you want to use a post and that's the standard which is used when it comes to restful services
Let's Taco update method
Two letter at
Update
Mapping
What's the URI
Is the clues update mappings I used to syntax as it is
So I just copy the stuff from here
Two Heroes
Could never have the mapping present in here they should be updated
Enter the Abbey back mapping at 2 that should have used foot mapping
Import mapping
We have the update to do
Body ready we're not really did anything yet
To be to get a username ID
And Patti LaBelle username ID that's cool
Along with the update to do will get a request body in
Request body so you have the updated content
That is sent as part of the request party
So let's add this in as well
Import
Because body
Free update request will typically send
Okay status
With
Discontent
So what I'll do is I'll
Do the quantity of to do central voice to do
Analytical d
To do service
Safe
I'm passing the values of
And this would return
Be updated to do
Let's take the updated value of The To Do List to do updated
Lexington
A new response entity
Containing to do
Republican d-22 and Beauty status
.
Okay
Actually the same thing can be done by just saying return to do and changing return type to to do as well
This gives us
More options in 235 won't extend this and be able to return status back then using the response
Give us more options
Now that we have created the foot mapping for this
Licks
Look at how to create the post mapping in the next step