Play come back and it has to be designed it to DuPage form
What do you do when you take the initial values from the state and actually show them in these fields
And also what we lose when we do this safe
Piedmont actually submitted details which are present in there we take our first step towards that
Pokemon on let's get started with the first one how do you show the initial values in this
We only have devalues populated.
Gan Cho them in here inside the Forum
Fort McMurray makes it very very easy all that I need to do this
Send something called initial values what are you doing here
Description
Is equal to
This. State
.
Description
Target date
Detox tea. Activate
Informant
I can add him
Property initial values
Initial values would want pasta in a JavaScript object to it
If you want that same as I was kicked object I need to put
First one and the second one
To say I'm cleaning an object right
In the initial values what we'll do is we'll put description
Description
Piercing I would want to have a key-value pair
The name of the key is description devalues description
What do we spell Cynthia
,
The syntax looks a little bus
We fix it very soon
So talkative
No would see that the default initial that you switch over your setting in to reform are appearing in here let's change
Landform
Landforms in the state are appearing in the Forum
This sexier looks a little one of the things that we can make use of is a shortcut notation
Get the key
And the name of the variable which contains the value is the same
In those kind of situations you can create JavaScript object just icing
Description
Let's go to the JavaScript console and play around to see exactly what we're doing
Name
Is equal to in 28 minutes
End
Let
Course
Is equal to
Transcend
Full stack
I Just Called It full stack
That's it I'm quitting a JavaScript object lips
Details
1 is equal to
Typically develops I would want to create
With the name of name
Quotes
If I win the details
You see that it contains
This structure name is included when its course is full stack
Steam structure can be created very easily
But not even needing to pass
Is the same
The name of the variable
Which has the value
Then you really need to do
Colon and put that into details to is equal to name and course and said details to now
You can see that details to also contains exactly the same values
Isn't this awesome
Okay now we have initial value ready
The other thing I would want to simplify
This thing tax is very similar to say
This
Within braces
And this Thursday.
Description actually distorted
Tootsie
This is exactly
Working as it is right now
Why is it working
Let's create a simple test subject test is one we used to insist
No I don't want to take
Best of zero
He's going to testify against he's going to test us to the other way I can do that by saying
Let
A comedy
Is equal to
Best
What would happen
Listen to
Tuan
B
See
So this is what it's called destructuring
This is one of these
Most useful features in JavaScript
You don't really need to say he's going to test. He's going to test a test.
Automatically for you
A little bit of Flexin on the border JavaScript for now we have the initial values populated
And it's working fine
Everything we want to do is handling this submit
We can handle submit this by defining on submit
Physical to this.
Define emphatically on a bit to do the ending of the submit to
Unsubmit
There's an attitude called values which is passed into this door control. Log
What are the values that are being submitted
Before we can use the unsubmit
What do we need to be to bind it
Just after this date let's buy this as will distort on submit
Difficult at this. On submit
This
If I go to the
Cancel let's clear everything just visiting here
And
Pick save
You can see
That this is being printed out
Play despacito
Then function one you can see continent one
68 to 10
Concessive
What are values which we are modifying our
Populated directly into values
What are Rickman you to do is to compare it against the login form that we created
To be able to get the values out from the fields
What we have to do was to create on change method on each of the elements
And we had to actually divide the body of the unchanged method as well but formic makes it all easy
What we did this week
Let me see the same but we were able to see that
You can take the latest values and submit them
I see you in the next step