Welcome back
With all the actors
What are the things that you want to do at 8:20 and it is being able to build
Different back and replace them two different front end Frameworks
There isn't need to standardize
What's between us
What do you use
Be standardized on port 8080
For the backing
Buddy's Renton
Let's use of different port which is called 4200
Running the application on localhost 3000 what you want to do if you would want to run the react applique
Jason on Local Host
I know you will look back and you need to tell
The request for it
Would be coming from
You need to tell
The exact you all right
Otherwise it would not accept requests
Befriending
Play Contigo 4200
Are we going to get it
It's easy
I'll let you need to do is go to work
You can specify a port to other food is equal to
And safe
And you can go back
This place we are running it
Stop it
And
Do a npm start again
You see that note for 4200 is being used
And have you can see that the Google application is being launched
Localhost
You can login
UT.
Your functionality what do you mean
Exactly as it was so there are no real changes except for the fact
2204 2200
Suppandi application
I see you in the next step