They come back into step we want to create the three altitudes for user get service
What are the things I observed when I went to the structure organized
Stuff is not really perfect
What I would want to start with that would want to start with me during these two specific packages to add one
This bean I would want to meet up package call Hollywood
I did. How do I control one or command one and I say moo hello world into that package
And I'll also do the similar thing with the Hollywood controller
What I would want to do is move this to
LOL controller
I want to move it to.
Hello world package and say move
And I would see that everything is very well organized
The beehive
Aldi Halliwell services in a single package and Rehab
Web service application in
Just make sure that everything is fine I just running the
Teresa said it looks cool
If you go to the home and just will get
Everything else is fine
Let's not focus on creating the retrieval tutus for a user service
What I'll do is I'll create a new class
Cyclist to do
Resource
Finish as usual at rest controller annotation
Pest control space
What do you want to do this we would want to create a get method to public
List of Toulouse
So you don't return a list of Toulouse
Get
All
Toulouse
And we're going to be able to get them for a specific
User
I don't want to be able to return
Back
OK Google
Is will not really talk to a database simple
In memory service
Athleta point in time in the cross will convert to using a jpa and hibernate based service
Very very simple things let's focus on one thing at a time
What I'll do is I create a new class country
Create class to do
Let's go ahead and created in
The.
To do and to finish
Moody's to Detroit. No package that's good
Public long ID
We want to start at night
Could it be public
Good want to store which you said that to do belongs to
Let's to private
String
Username
What is the description of that specific through correct string description
Date
Target date
End
Good want to store the
Completion status
Is it completed or not
Let's quickly indicator sunsetters for a little loose
Took I created Garrison Keillor Garrison centers and Elsa select all
Miniclip
As well as it's constructed
You got a new to this is Psychic Source
Kindergarten centers
And all your other methods as well so you can send it to string gender Constructor and all that stuff
I like someone
To all shipped and gender construct are using
Tourettes genetic instructor
It's created down here and really want it down here
How do I take down here so we could have created a being with a Constructor
And also did get us into desolate 4matic control shift Air Force command Chief death
Let's go to the Total Resource
And let's
Do I import a shout-out YouTube this is not really compelling because we are not yet back
I would want to do is I would want to create a service
To private
Let's start with a hard-coded service service
And College
Service
This so is that not exist yet
So this created control one
Creepiest to hardcore it service
Chris Gordon created in
Antique finish
What I would want to do we need to do hardcore at series is I would want to be able to have a static list of Toulouse
Private
Static
List of
Tutus
Is equal to
New arraylist
It's imported list at least until 1 and then put it in India
Let's Imports
Download YouTube.
Guess that's one
What do you do if this would act as our database to Google put all the things into this
Can we create methods around it
Let's initialize the data in this
Static
Can we create a static initializer block
And adding
Cruise
Add
It's great and you to do down here
So what else do we need to continue to do I need an ID
Eid what a loser created counter
But I wait
Ink
Heidi
Counter
Is equal to 0 and each time
For every to do let's do a
Tinnitus would start at 1
What's an experiment's username in 28 minutes
The next one is description let's say
We would want to learn
To dance
That's the first one
Next one is the date
You did
To start off
It's what country won an input Java. You think because it is what we want
;
Navi have this present
Decrease the font size a bit so that we can see a little bit more of this stuff.
Ipf acting in a lot of stuff in here
I want to add tea to lose in 28 minutes learn to dance
I want to learn about microservices
I want to learn
About
Angular
Is that good
Let's start with creating a very simple method to sit on this list of Toulouse right so what do we need beer
What is it called
Find all
The stuff user
Find
List of Clue
Trulicity and 11
Sheraton
Now we have the tools being returned back from here one of the things which we are doing in here is headed into Springdale
Divya Singh tax so that we can easily switch to it later for now let's go to
Let's make use of the hardcore to do service
You should be a spring component try to view the one we don't want to create instances
Who wants me to manage that
Component
This is
A business service so a better thing to do would be to say this isn't head service
Numbness go back to the to do research
Autowired
Dude want to auto service in here
Speak to manager dependencies and now I can say
To do service
.
Find all now what you got to do we want to map to this you want to map
The get request so get mapping
And what is it you want to let me want the map to this we already decided that
It's / users / to lose
Total result
Put it down here
_Nimble use username
And this
Change username is a battery
Variable
Import parts
Don't I can import to get mapping
Put it in
Septice
Localhost 8080 users / in 28 minutes to lose
Cute CDs to Deuce present
With your username you putting
He said we should return Aldi to do switch a present in there
We created a service we wanted to retrieve a list of tools and we wanted to connect it to defendant
We created a service and we are ready to connect to the back and let's see
How we can do that
Except