Welcome
Back
Vietnam have a friend running
So we have defended running at localhost 3000 to lose
And we also have our
Back-end API radius Pennsylvania 88 I get the response hello
Let's start the journey
To tie them up together
What do you want to do if you would want to start
With calling
Hello World Service
If you want to call me Hello World Service
Listen
The welcome page
Listen to message and we'll add a button and only clickable button do you want to call
Say Hello World Service
Let's start with the preparation in distant and a button in here
Let's go to our favorite ID Visual Studio code
And
Let's open up are welcome component this what we have in our welcome component right now
Let's
Here so that we can see everything with his cousin
Click here
To get
Customized
Welcome message
Send text
And over here everyone to add a button
Who'd want to call the Halliwell service
I just said
Welcome
Message
This is
Cuz it in this class so I can sadistically message
JavaScript code you need to put it in
Braces
That's what he'll do
And over here
Let's put the text
Welcome
Sage
Let's save this
Go to rui
This is about to get ready from this age
Class
Is equal to
Last name
Button
Elizabethton Texas
I'm having a problem with the CSS because whatever we put in the counter
It actually causing a problem here
Natalie
Disable some of the CSS which is presenting here I don't really want to worry about this thesis or not so what I do
Coming out all the CSS which is present inside the counter. CSS
What we had what we should have done when we did the counter.
Is your last name of the counter app before each of these CSS elements
Odysseus is only applicable
To be counted element
Netflix is coming to town
And let's go back to the page
That's all I need a little bit so that I can see all the text which is present in here
Define desultory welcome message method
Subjective welcome message and over here
Cancel.
Retrieve
I will think about this this is sufficient we need to actually have a Constructor writer
Instructor and
Doodie binding
The Constructor
Cops as usual
Equally Supra
Roblox
After that
We don't want to actually
Do this.
Etsy welcome message
Is equal to
This.
Retrieve milk message.
52 something which
We must be very proficient by nav
Now if I go there and
If I do T get welcome message
Ridiculous
What you did in the specific step until Love is Real chili
I did this message we had to do button
And we see this evening
What we actually want to do it would want to call
W switches expose from the back and you go to call localhost 8080 helloworld and they would want to
See
Respond back
And show it as a message down here
On things that I see here is a lot of warnings
So let's quickly get rid of all the warnings which are being highlighted in here how do I get to the volume set up component
Compound is defined but not used
Let's open up the other component
What is not used is component let's get rid of it
Connecting us to do app
Let's go to tutuapp
The j-6 what is Define but not lips
Removing ink from here
Six one is a little interesting it says online 59 users constructed I was actually coming here and looking at this
This concept is used it's talking what deconstructed in here
This is kind of the default Constructor which would be an eBay provided to even if I don't provide this this would be actually provided by counter
Earlier we had stayed in here so we needed a Constructor but we don't really need it right now to let commentator
Doubt
Felines
That's going to end after Jace
.
Let's coming.
And a good leader Jess
Don't you
I can actually
Come and get out completely
And we can come and get it
We want to come back but
Once we do that you get more letters about
Discomfort
So if I come in this out
Binais
Go to the pages
I see that I don't really have an
It's up to you whether you want to do this or not like
Having my control empty
Heart attack warnings so we can actually focus on
What would happen is bendy having a rough morning Cindy console you cannot see the real errors
And that's the reason why
You need to understand focus on the warnings look at the control and see Dara Runnings
And make sure that you address them
I know but you can
I see you in the next step