Today results from the delete button here
When did Titanic skit will find lead that specific to do
How do you do that
It's located right now
Alcatraz delete
And highlight a button inside
TTD India
So I'll add a button
Martin
Let's call it
Delete
Give me the class
Button
Send button working
It should be class name
So now we have a delete button
See what happens
Now we have a delete button which is being rendered in here
What do you need to do if you need to call the chili pepper in the API back-end
How do you do that
Let's go to the to do service and create a new API methods
And here
Altruist alcohols delete
You need two things to one is named
And the other one
He's
The idea of the to do
So which was it and what to do so
I can now sit
Daughter
I d
Very simple right so you had the same URL as this
What
Delete
The name of the user to lose
Enough to listen to this component what you want to do if you want to define a method which is to be called
What I'll do is I'll call this
Delete
We need to receive a parameter
I think we need to be able to get t
Idea of which was deleted so let's see if we can
Get the idea to do that ID
We already know how to get the username to username I can get it
From the authentication Service
I know I can call
Delete method
Do a simple contract log off
Heidi
, username just to make sure that we
Have everything
Carlos De Heidi Plus
Space
You send me
Get behind this matter quickly
Inside the Constructor on last night so divine
Click is equal to this. Delete to The Click Vine
Do you want to call that method
This is the way we do that
Braces
This. Delete
Text is it sufficient
Dd2 ID
So I cannot do justice what I need to do is I would need to actually do a arrow function in here
I need to say
How to function this. Delete it
I'm passing a parameter should I pass
True. ID
312 passing me to do. ID to it because we need to be able to do has to be deleted
Let's save this
Go to browser
Iclicker
Inspect go to console
Totally tidy one in 2022 in 2023
Disconsolate log I can directly call
Metal
What method should I call service
.
Delete to do
And I need to Boston
You love me
,
Make sure that you have the order of the family that's right it should be username, ID
What should you do once it's successful that's a good question by to watch Abby
What to do when it successful
What will do
This will set a message
Intestate
Lunch with successful message to the user so what I'll do is I'll say this.
Send a message
Alice
Dicks
MC
Delete
To do and say dollar
Heidi
Texas
Stop this is not really in the state yet so we need to put it in the state to Hollywood attempt this date
How long will it take to lose what we want
Eclipse actually the Moody's commented stuff because this makes it very difficult to understand
Ted Cruz initially would be empty after that we would have a
Message
It is initially empty and we would want to show it
10 below
Twinlets creator
Put the message in heater
It's not just message it should read this.
Message
And let's put a simple jazz on it s website
And alert
Weather resistant Bluetooth
Login page
So let's see what happens now
You can see that by default showing and that's not really good
Let's fix that what we lose
Reset the message to
Initially
And
Only
When
This. State. Message
See what happens now
Now it's not showing busy when it's not it's not shown
And let's delete one of these
It's getting deleted
Things you have to do is that the pages not getting refreshed
Tell if I go back to the to lose if I go to home and come back to the Jews would see that the Tudors deleted but
Meineke delete that list of taboos was not getting updated what do you want to do
If you would want actually refresh the to do this again
And vegetables logic is completely present in componentdidmount
And I don't really want to call componentdidmount and that's not a good practice
What to do to create a method for this as refresh to do
Let's do that first
Refresh
Toulouse
Moral logic
Refrigerator deuce in it
And then I would call
This.
Reference to losing hair
And over here the same refers to this candy called
In the delete
Event at 7
When
Did I respond to successful
Then there is an unsuccessful response right to
That's the reason I'm putting it in here so I'm putting it inside the method when
Little sexy lesbians I want to refresh the two deuce
Bind
Refresh to do
Save this
Go back to home come back to Toulouse
And delete one of these and now you can see delete have to do to be successful delete
Do you have the $2 a successful isn't it awesome and we have no way of cleaning to do
One of the things we can do is
Obviously please. Be back in
Light Aqua defense the entire list of to-dos completely
Reality feature to delete
D2 do we started with updating The View
And also
Simple call to do data service method
When we use axios
Call the delete method and we had to pass name and ideas
Send a message in to state
So that we can show it to the user when
Delete a successful we also have to be to lose once the whole thing was done
I'm sure you're having a lot of fun and I'll see you the next day