We not have the welcome page ready
Any cricket
Wake up message what do you want to do
We want to call the Halliwell
Let's take a quick look at the framework we are going to use
When to use
To make the HD
Call Scott askew's
If you were Google search fractious promise
Pacific mango Tax USA
This should be the first
It is
/axios
Class Act
You'll see that it's a promise best hits decline
30 browser
The whiskey Vault axios allows us to do is to make http
What are the most important things that
It does it's based on
Promises
So if you go further down and look at
The features
You can see
That it support
Something called
Promise API
He has a lot of other features where you can actually intercept
Requests and responses you can actually transform the data which comes back from the services you can cancel request and stuff like that
Let's start with looking at
Take this link
You go to the
Notify Mozilla site
What are the important things to understand is when I click this button and when we
Calling the service
Disabuse might take a long time to rest
And if you keep waiting
50 service to respond
This entire browser would be hanging
That's right we didn't want to make a synchronous call we want to make a synchronous call
The only city because that we make typically from a friend 10
Would be done using a
Synchronous fainberg
That means you just
All the service and continue doing the processing
And when the response comes back from the service
You don't keep me waiting
But the response to come back
And Promises
Help us to do
Simple synchronous operation
The promise
What you can do
Don't worry about the syntax
Due to creative promise in here.
Might look a little complex for somebody who's starting with the most important thing with the province's you can Define
1 Step promises completed once
I have the response back or once
Something is completed
What we can do
Then
Executive dysfunction based on this response
You can look at this promise
What two things this is doing is actually sitting a timeout synchronous operation
We're waiting for 300 seconds and then returning to back
What happens is defining
When food comes back what should be done
We are logging the value of food to become
And I forgot next line of code
I like but more line to decide to cancel. Log
You can see what is printed first
Done is printed first Den
This Promise object is printed then
Only then
This 300 milliseconds completed and this return fullback
And only then
Good garlic
Executed
So what we're doing in here
Is a synchronously
Call something
Can you sing
Making a synchronous call Envy Define here
What should be done when this occurs call comes back with a response
And after that be a synchronous operation computer execution
And then
Monthly response comes back
The act on it
Think this
Actual streambook helps us to take the same concept
And
Put it into
Footballing
ADP API
If this is a little confusing don't worry about it
When we make our first hits difficult most of these things will be ready
We look at the actual streambook
Which is basically a promise based
Tell us to make HTTP calls from a JavaScript code
Wilson Pickett
At what is a promise
We saw that promises he'll of us to Define asynchronous operation and also Define what
We talk more about this
In the subsequent
ICU