Play comeback be implemented the API for update and create YouTube
Let's connect our front end
70cc if you want to save this details back to dapi
How do we do that
Let's go to be to do service and let's start creating a couple of new services
Let's start with a gate to do details
What do you want to do for a date today
Read want to sending you details
Cyclist update to do
Can I have the name ID and in addition to that people have a to do or get
What are the details that need to be at
Submitted
How do we do the update
Which method do we use to do the update to do the update
Put method in addition
It accepts an additional parameter you can say
What is the value that needs to be updated or what should be part of the body of the request
We quickly
Put out the update through method institutional to data service
Go to the Google company what do you do what you want to do
Toronto
Data service
Got a bit
What are the parameters that needs to be passed
Name ID and to do
We know how to get the name and the ID right we have the name and daddy Done lyrics
Let's get to username
Did this. Stay.
You need to patent an object saying what details need to be updated
OK Google repeat that from devalues
Description
Gladius.
Values.
Target
This what's Bolero down here IDs Notting values to what we need to do this we need to put this from
List of state. ID
Exit 50 listings page and go and find a Big D
Learn to dance
Respective
It's go to the tools you can see that learn to dance 3 is now updated to update is working
We're not really redirecting the user back to get to do space let's do that right now
How do we do this
Google history. Bush
Unsubmit
Submitted successfully then what do we need to do
Easter Define
The method which needs to be done
Bush
Where do you want to go back to
Today
Kudos
HBO TV need this
Actually we don't even need it takes so we can even do it quotes
Is it is just one statement probably.
Beacon formatted in a very very simple way this way
Learn to dance for
And safe
Cuticles to be list of this page
It's to update
Activities today to 19th
NC safe
Then it about anglophone and it's 19
Are the things you can see in the list to do state the values are not really formatted to this is not really
Getting good
Let's format it right there
What we'll do is Google talking. Let's Tuesday
Woman function
The moment of truth
.
Format
Why why why
Excuse the same thing
Bye-bye bye-bye
One small thing is to make sure that we imported them
Import
Moment
Trump
Cool
Let's see if it's not the page looks good so you can go ahead and Save
You can play around with these the update feature is working with literature is working
Is to be able to add on YouTube and let's focus on that