Welcome
Any previous steps be made use of promise
Axios
Pics of you some of those Concepts
The specific step
A promise is nothing but
Promise
Elsa's Stroop
And Define
What should be done
Burnet Texas
What should we done
When it fades
Example
Discontinue synchronous Quan
Which returns a promise back
On the promise you can Define what should be done
When did
Restaurants
Is successful do what
Do what if there is an adverb
Big skibidi Hallowell service
Envy defined
What should be done in the case of a sax
Response
Subsequent step also Define what should be done if there is an error if there's another how do you handle it
If you do a Google actually ate a documentation on this page
Github.com axios
Axios
Off making a call using axios
Renee Daggett
SeaQuest
Call if you needed to do was do adjusted get
Something and
Beaverton de promise back
And once we return the promise back
Inside the component method
V Define
What should be done if it successfully
You can also perform
Alterations
Oh yeah you can see that the thing that you iron
Ants between the body of the request
If you scroll a little down you'd see that there are a lot of other requests methods that you can
Use from axios
Delete
Head
Options
It support all
The HTTP request methods
Scroll down you'll also City
Object
Some axios look like
What would you get
If request is successful
So this is the response schema
We already booked that response. Data and we actually got the message from that right we said the sponsored data
Distance also contain something called
Which is nothing but good of the response
State of Texas
Exactly the representation of this 200
Okay
Purple
Page not found
If there are any headers then they would come back as part of this
Request configuration Houston would also count as part of the response
And also you have a reference to the request
Safelite
Making a request
And you think you're not getting good response back then you can look at all this data
Inside the response
He took a quick look
EPA behind the axios
Stream work I'll see you in the next step