Welcome back
Let's add the feature to add a new to do to a friend
Let's
Go to the distance component cable
Let's give our class is equal to
Let's add a button let's have a class at Lee
Have a class name here as fake last name is equal to button
This would be my contacts SS.
End
Let's see how this looks
Could we have an add button down here
Let's focus on what needs to be done when the add button is clicked let's go to The Cruise Compass
This is why we have the add button
I think about it what should we show when a button is clicked you should show the true page with empty details
Dude want to show 220 similar to what we do on the update button right to what
On fleek
Is equal to
This.
Let's cook
Activate
Actually copy out
The update to The Clique
Change it
Submit
Add
Click if I got the names right
A triplet hooks I got it right
Accurate leak
What you need to do is first go to the top
And add
This finding
This. Actually keep this one. They start at 3.
This
Now that we have The Binding different
That's cool and see what's happening to what you want to do is not update you'd want to create
And
What are the important things is farad to do dinner did witches passed in because
You don't know the idea of things to do that is going to be created
And 32 Deuce page to identify that it isn't YouTube what we do is really give it
Heidi of -1
We need to do when a twist of fate
Use might as well as the ID
To see what happens
It's
Doesn't work
Acrylic
Inspect
Because
We made a mistake when designing this this should be
Good looks
I could go.
Let's
Kit Kat and
Videos that we are staying at diesel detail resetting to this date
Compass in componentdidmount only called it to do service
Eid Eid state
Is equal to is equal to
-1
I just say
What I'm doing here is if it's minus one then it's not retrieved to do I want to continue to do so I don't really know
If you can handle the save button is exactly the same as it is in the case of an update
Except for the fact that we need to call a different service
We service what you need to do call is a post service writer
Create to-do
I don't really need the idea of it
Heidi would be assigned at a later point
URL
User / name to deuce
You need to do a post
School today that would want to call
I'll go to Z to do component list see submit button
Cupping method
So on submit also we have to have a nice condition this condition that we had earlier
IDs one
Then
It's on YouTube it's an existing through
This is what we need to do
What you need to do
It's something similar
They threw me to do.
See it through
I would not need to stay. ID inside
Dometic kontokosta parameter is not needed to username
IDs desert Sato tidy description
And after that
This remains
Exactly the same
Let's see if this works out time
Lettuce
X-ray description my first
Created
Safe
B
It's created and when I do an update
I'm able to updated as well that's cool so we are now able to create a to-do as well
Really liking here is the duplication which is present between these two objects take this
Alex and create let
To do is equal to
Yes I can possibly to do it
And even here
I can use the same
Credit
Hand
Let's go ahead and try the update
16 * 5
The Titan YouTube
I am
Cool everything's working fine we are able to add you to lose where they will drop date them and do a lot of magic
Recommend you to play around with this and I'll see you in the next step