Welcome back
The previous steps we set up through component in the set builder perform for the tool
But sometime what to use instead of connecting to be back and we'll have a to-do form where the default values are.
Calculated into the phone
Let's put a few values into this state and we'll take those values and show them in the form
Put values into this date let's get started now
So I said let's create a default state
Al Lewis on 2nd Street
Text Duda default one
UPS
Super
Props
So distraught state
And a Target date
Is equal to
Tidy
Let's
Athena
Default ID and description
It's pretty to
Learn
What I would want to do
You started it start with new date
Will need to
Add to the Target date a little later recall moment to ferment
We don't really have a moment install yet
We have all the values that you would want to use
In this date
You want to take these values
And throw them in the form to Englander wood want to create a form
When we will login component
Normally seemed element V. All the events we don't handle change event
And we did all this stuff
And we don't really write a letter of validation rent stuff in Harrisburg
What we saw at that point was creating forms
Whitley Act was complex is not an easy task
And that's where we would want to use another Library
Call for me
But he is one of the most popular form libraries with more than 1 million downloads
The last few months so it's very very popular and used across the board
What we do now is move install for me and also another Library call movement which we will do
Stop the running application
End
Sonic
Partagas added text to Lee you can look up your package. Jason you'd see it in there and let's also add
India mad
Moment
Momentous install and for me also is installed
Formic and woman down here
It's stocked with using
Moment
One of the things is this particular date format we saw was not really good to what I'll start with doing is using moment
.
Let's let's important
How to say import moment
From
Monticello
Awesome JavaScript library which helps you to format dates and things like that so I'll say it.
Format
And
The format I would want to use is
Yyyy
This is a format in which
Stimulate circulation so let's use that as
Allstate
State is populated what do you want to do if you want to create the form
Let's start putting content in here
H1
Let's put to do in here
As usual its creator
Actually
Class is equal to container
Oh here in the state I can use the ID
So I'll just put that
Has
Heidi Klum and Alameda specific thing
Let's focus on the phone now
Create appointment for me the baby can start it is by
The singer tag called
4mc
So I just followed me
And I'm saying
Control fascia so you could Auto Imports Parma can say it's important for making hair
Formic
And close it out
So inside
Formic what do you need to do in here
Is actually Define a method which would return the entire form
I would start with putting JavaScript
Notation
For this method will receive the props
Which app fasting
Then we can Define what should be returned
India return a simple
Let's see what happens
The Indians that have real Indian stats to start the whole thing.
I get an address engagement is not defined
Because I'm using cast
Mistake
I see something in here that's cool so we have on a syntax right
Inside the formic defending is a method
Which active process input
Returns back
Exactly steel mill of the phone
Maybe we can define a form in form It Is by using a tag called for me to type in for
You can actually
AutoZone 14th from 460 Alva Center in here
You can also do a control space to import it in
You can see that it's adding form to the for making forts
Form-fitting Moody live
Oats
And safety phone we would want all the form elements
Put (around
Difs
So that we can easily formatted in a better way to now
One level
Inside
Just give us a little bit of space so that we can see more of the phone
Tonight inside the phone but do you want to do
We want to create elements
Exactly creating description
So we'll start with doing
Reset
Inside the field status for you define
Element pictured want to show
You would have a label
The actual input element
How to get using formic so what we would use is something called field again I said typing field you can see that it
Is an Auto Import which is being suggested let's do that
To cancel that
Phillies also imported from formic
So this is kind of descent X let's add a few classes to eat so
Basic bootstrap classes to format deform
Is equal to Cleo here let's do a class name as well
Platinum is equal to
And footsies
Casting
Palm
Coffee these two things again
Because you don't want to
First one
Feel what you want to have is it description
This is description
This is
Type is equal to
Text
And name is equal to
Description
This one
Lisa Talcott date
Type of this
And they won't fit is
I got date
Make sure that your flute closing all day
Elements
I know when you look at the screen
I see a pretty decent form
Present
It's a dove Button as well
What we want to do is have a button
And it's a type
Is equal to
Submit
It's a disabled
Let's add a class
Name
Is equal to button
Button
We have the same button Aspen
I think it happened when we actually
Do anything with it
Did a lot of things we need to do before we will be able to use this one
But the most important thing right now is we have the form design
It is just what we did is being voted in for me
And we also imported in woman
Heaviest woman to format a date which we want to show we have not actually used it yet
And we designed our
Basic form
Let's add much more features to the specific form
I see you in the next