Welcome back now that we completed the delete feature let's do our attention to it
What do you want to do this we would want to do an update
So you lied about them in here Khalid and
Goodwin the update
Go to the new page
3 create a new page call true
Arby's create a new component called through component and antique of the update button
Lecture digital component I'll start with adding for update
Iceland
This one I change it to success because I would want it to look green
And I would want to call
Not delete to do but I would want to say
Update
Let's go to the update through click method
Easy to do
Wake me up at
Psychologist
Update to do clickfunnels
Amanda Corbett is present in here
Is until 2:00
A date
Band
Lsid
There's one thing that we need to do
So it should be
End
A bit crooked
Exactly
Etsy
Hobby Lobby button
It's do what I click
Inspect
And
Let's see what's in the console
A bit
A big one
I did too
I bet
That's cool
What do you want to do Sunday pickup you updated want to redirect to be to do company where is it to component
What created Created to the Explorer create a new file
Component
.
Deus Ex
Let's use
Import react
Component
React
To do component
Extends component
Collecting Clementine animated
Let's
Just say
Now we have a basic through component I want redirected this
From the list reduce component
Triplet method
I need a route to it where do I find out it's go back
It's a long time since we've defined out so this is where we Define this out right
Define about to do complementary. Integrated route or Jesse route
It should be authenticated outside only authenticated users should be able to see us
So let's go
And I'll say the party Studio
/: idq12
Show us Pacific to do salsa deposit / 2 /: ID
End
In the welcome company saw how to pick up the wall that we needed to do
This. Probz. Match. Adams.
That's cool
So let's take that go back to the to do company
And I don't to
Display. India
Tapu component
Heidi
Steady idea of teaching
And actually should not be named it should be
Not the crew complement has it
Name
Actually a route
What's it out to eat to lose
Stash
Value of the idea so it's like an $10 a day
So the company has a trout
Seadek
This out
From the update to do click
How do I do that we did something similar in the log in component when we wanted to redirect
Some login component
Could've elchim component
You need to do exactly the same thing
The ID which is faster
Let's see what happens now it says into app through component is not defined obviously to go there
An imported through component in
Import
Through component
From
Chris
Stop it in
Little company.
Any more arrows through company does not contain a default expert
Why does it come
Put gas
Through
Complement
Actually I should take sport
Default to the complaint through confident judges extender should have a return method right
Sophia Loren
Address again
It's very important that you know how to solve this
Because you would face this address again and again
You'd see that they have the list reduce displayed
Let's kick update enough you can see that
Localhost 4202 do someone is displayed in the Ura
Obviously
Vanessa / 2 2 / 1
This route is matching
And
This confident is getting displayed what do you want
This route to have higher priority
2 / 2
Clash caller ID
That's cool stuff to do
Update to do something Friday 1
Through Friday 2
Update through Friday 3
We're bending the sex is being promoted the update feature
Paneer to add the update button in update method on the list reduce component
After that we created the two components
End on the kickoff update video directed
From the list to do component 2D to do component
Nextstep blitzstein design a good page for the to do component
I see you the next day bible