We saw that when we click the get welcome message
We got a car
How can we prevent that
That's what you look at
Indus
And once
Be able to solve that what we'll do is we'll try and get the welcome message and show it on the screen
Previous step we discussed the fact that
The backend is not allowing request from a different
He's actually one of the cool features which is provided by Spring boot
What do you want baby tell spring boot
His finger I know that I would be getting requests
From Local Host
4200 I would want to I love them
How can you tell that to Spring boot eBay we can tell that the spring boot is by using something called
Cross
But itching
Type in escrow surgeon
And you can see that you can specify
You'd want that love
I would hear you can specify a number of Origins for now
Let's just say
You composed
Save this
And wait for the server to pick up
The changes
Let's go back to defendant
Messenger game
You see that I'm getting data back
Time getting the data back it says hello world the status of the responses 200
State of Texas
Something insulting
And tofu
We have to respond back what we focus on not using this response and showing it on the screen
Message in here all that I would need to do is say this class is going to continue
I want to see some message
We're leaving
Call is successful
Where can I put a message in and how can I display it in here
Pink reactively
Thinking
The way you do that is by putting it in
What do you need to do is now we need to set
A messaging to this day to this.
We need to initialize it
What do Louisville put
Welcome
Message
And usually you value would be empty
What do you do
Use that
And
Display it down here
So we'll just say
Welcome message
I didn't want you can put it around it and make it
Much more stylish but for now let's just focus on putting like a message down here
When I go to the screen I see an address
93 Gateway Commerce it
We get data Hollywood so we need to get this data and show it
How do you do that
What do you need to do is actually over here we need to Define
The entire method
Handlery successful restaurant
What do you do for this time is to keep things simple let's create a new method cyclist hand
Successful
Response
Any sexual response
I'll have response
The parameter
I don't think that we need to quickly do is to bind it
This
.
I'm successful response is equal to Desert and successful response
Vine
This
And once this is available what I can do
I can
Restaurants
.
Data
The data from the response and that is what should go into
Which one is it
We should put it
Welcome message
Where's the welcome message Pleasant
Inside this day title what we need to do is this.
Set state
Bass
Let's
Get rid of all this stuff sold that we are doing
Response
You're picking something for later until you did well, so you can actually see the
Complete
Structure down here data
LOL
So that's what you would be able to see in here
It's still not showing
The welcome message
Right
Because he's not really call handle successful restaurants yet
So what are you doing it's called
I think any successful response is not defined because
I'm not said this.
Get ready to message UT hello world which is printed in here
1 things that you can do is go to the network so you go to the network
Simply this
Be able to see
Minimize this a little
Let me clear it out
Diddy quest which is going out and in
Request details
Let's maximizes a little
You can see the fact that it's
Yesenia requested this URL
Request method is this
OCD responsible switch are coming back to factory provided cross Edition
This actually coming back as a
Spontaneous
The actual response which is coming back which is hello world
Uses to debug stuff is something is not working what you can do is actually come over here
And look at this
To go to the network Tab and see what requests are going in and going out
This is one of the most useful things that you can do to debug stuff when something is not working
Do I know something is not working what you need to do
Is you need to come to the network that see whether the request is successful successful
Lagdi response
Which is coming back
I want to know the response which is coming back
You can see how they are handling.
What year did we got rid of the Cross of generic or the Corsair
Display
Message which is coming back from
On the screen
I see you in the next step