Welcome
Back
Let me kick it like a message we want to make a high city because using axios
Now how do I get the ideas for looking into our project
And how do we make that call that's what we'd be looking at in this physics.
First question how do we get back to us when we can do on Facebook
Think about it
You are right we need to add it
So I'm going to the middle on and I say npm
Axios
I downloaded
Package. Tucson
It's not really in here
If you wait for a little while.
He could be added
Now we have a graduation 0.18
That's added in
UT
Axios also added in in here so
Havoc Naveen our package. Jason as well
We want to start making
Use of actions to make its typical so what I do is I like chili start creating a few more things
API calls waterloo's insert a new folder
API
Mapa
I'll create a new folder game call to
And what I'll do is right click create a new file
And I would want to call this
Hello world
Service
.
Let's
Create a simple class in here so this would be a kick-ass
Hello World Service
Sovaldi helloworld apis
We would want to call them
From here
Lucky Lou's weekly instant traffic
Portage so that it's available for all other
Gases which depend on this so I'll say export default
New
Hello world
So if any of the package would
They would get the instance of the specific class
What would we need to do in here to want to retrieve
Hello world
Message
What do you want to do in here you don't execute
Hello World Service writer
Servicelocator simple
And for now
Executed service
But before he can put this in
We should we put it into into the welcome component lighter
LOL service
/
Da.
API
Flash
Duchess
Global Services defined in siletz important in first
Indicative message what we'll do is we'll remove this
Next legal LOL service
Execute
LOL service
Let's see what would happen.
Save this
Trying to get welcome message
Inspect
Goldie cartoon
Receive
Click
It is because
You're not really started the application back I can survive
Visited
Nothing will be there
Desmond tickets you need to be cautious about you need to make sure that the restart on browser instance
Great 8 minutes
Dummy
Logging
Decorate a message I click in
Fancy the console
You can see
Executed
Service
That's cool
How can you make you the sexiest to make the call it's very simple
I'll let you need to do is to do something call axios
Get
And
Passing the URL don't want to execute
Hello Google
Find
Do you want to let you two want to execute
This line
Down here is a promise
Sunset Imports
Axios
Axios axios
Birkenstock making u v
If you wait
Studio City documentation of the gate metal or actually Dakota forget method
Back
OK Google turn the promise that
To each of these methods in the allowable service building a promise that
And people leave the responsibility of
Defining what to do
If this poly successful or is the squad leaders resulting endeavor
Welcome component Indie confident which is making a call to the heart
India
So just kind of declined
Cody helliwell service right over here
Give me a promise.
Telephone service what did we do promise back
What do you do
Is you can Define what do we do when it's a successful response
What should we do when it's a unsuccessful dress
This
Request
Sexy eats what should I do
If this request fails
What can I do that's what I'll be able to Define on the promise that start with defining the successful
Take this exit scenario
DeQuincy successful
We need to define a method calling here we need to Define what should we do
What I'll do
Is Define
If I get a response
I'll take it
LLC
Cancel
DOT log
Sports
Let me do this
Response comes back
You're taking it and putting it down
Today cancel
Let's see what happens
Message
Oops
It's saying access to my Stephan HTTP request
Xmlhttprequest
Had this
Some origin
Has been blocked
Think about this
80eighty
So yes kind of making a call to one server
From another server
By the back end right now
And that's the reason why we are getting this error
Let's take a break in here and let's see what needs to be done to fix this
In the next step
We didn't you promise that
And on the promise we Define
What should be done
When there is a successful response
I see you in the next step