Welcome
Any previous steps
We added the features to show me the values and we were a we can see what's happening when we
The same button with Banga.
Add validation Goodman to add a little bit of validation around these fields we want to make sure that the distinction is
Populated client is at least 5
We would want to make sure that there is a target date
How do you clean windows
Let's get to that right now
What we can do this weekend
Add a prop call Daddy date
This.
Salad
Let's define valid method
Validate
Off
Values
Pretty similar to values in here I can do a cancel
The Claw Golf values
Should return the Arabs
Back
It should return address which happened during the validation
This address should be returned back to work
Address is equal to this and return address back this indicates that there are no address present
Rudy
Binding quickly
Validate
We had it in The Binding
Save it
No
Let's do it I click inspect
Cancel
Antique safe
You see that
It's been two times the value 72 times
Because first-ballot is called when you keep this applicable to bandage is called
Then do you want to make is called
Listen to hardcore band ever
How do you say
Description
Should
Have
At least
Characters what happened
The family crest
I'm giving safe
You can see that it's only happening once
It's not being printed the second time because this submit is not happening
Is it being printed from the validate method
Samsung messages not really printing it
Now you may be wondering where can I see the address
How can I see the weather
Publix
Make appointment Matrix makes it very easy
I want to see Adam message I need to do this
Is equal to
Diff
Alert
So let's make sure that they are closing the note
Put this to next line so that we can clearly see everything with your present in here
You think we want to show the address for the description field and this Saturday classes do you need to use
I'm depressed
And now I fix it
You can see it shows the other in here it says should have
5 characters and add them in
Saudi Arabia created in Hollywood
And it's stuck validating videos
If not
Fabulous. Description
Aladdin
Address. Description
Is equal to
Description
It is a description already entered I would want to check that it's Oakland 5
How can I do that
Else
If
But it's length. Length
Is less than fight
What do you want to do
Peppa
At least
5 characters
Let all to validate
Let's see how can we update field
Do any of the data values.
We can use the movement framework provides options to check if
Adidas parley Donuts I can see movement of values.
.
East
Rallied
The date is valid
If not then
How to say Arabs
.
Target date
Is Aquatica
Target
What we did was we just added the other message for description little tired
Let's see what would happen
Safe
Removing learn what is something you can see that I'm getting an error
Directly down there making this date invalid and deleting the Dead
You can see that immediately I like this and delete immediately
So you can see enough that as soon as I change the values the validation is speaking in
And evaluation is also active
As soon as I hear something so if I do a blood also the same thing would happen
What do you need to do is disable both of those for me by default enables validation on blood and wine
Is equal to
False
Validate
Is equal to
Let's save this
Go here
Enough
You'd see that even if I enter the added value
You can like braless non-blood you can leave it to cool Electronics my chance you can leave it to do as well for me
I like being Holly violation so I'll keep it simple
We implemented validation of the fields
We saw that
Disney's pass the forms get submitted
Submit button
You get up validation never enough
To go on to the next steps weather actually get the data from the APA and submit the data back
As an update I'll see you the next step