We created
Delete method
Did you do research
Let's sign execute it
What we do is we use
Call
So if you search for s Late client sat testing you should find a chrome plug-in of this guy
Go ahead and install this
I will install the Toyota
Remove from
But if you're not install it then you would be able to see the install button but you can do
Go ahead and install
And once you install it used Sienna
This and you should see an icon down
Change this blue color icon with you seeing here
And once you click this
It would open up the last leg
The first page
It's taking a while to load up the first page
This is not the first page
UFC then you'd be able to do it
You don't really need to create an ID to be using this
Tuan the previous speed you'd be able to skip
It and I come in
What do you want to do
Localhost 8080 user in 28 minutes
Loose
/
The idea of the tools that you would wanted
Middle School
And not actually good
Send request
You see that I'm getting a 403
When you look at the statuses
It says 403
Forbidden
Reason why this request failed
Is because
What do
Restless blinders is
It sends the origin at this specific URL so it seems that you organize this
Let's configure An Origin
So the baby can do that is by saying origin
We can specify d u r l s
Enough if you do send
UT
Adidas pants is 204 204
No content
And that's cool that means our request
Has executed successfully
Enough if you go to the truce
Application
Go to the homepage and come back to this
You would see
That
What are the important things that you need to remember is each time this application is restarted that means
Every time you make a change in this
Application it's restarted and every time it's restarted would see that dick data would refresh
The data from the hard coded service would be refreshed
So each time what will happen is when I go to the home and pillows
Complete
Except
We focused on executing the delete request in The Next Step let's enhance our
URI
To be able to execute delete request
I see you in the next step