Welcome
In the previous two steps
We created login functionality where we can actually go in
Enter the user ID and password and login
We can go to the Tudors page
Actually see the welcome page we can go to the previous page
Citistaff
Floozies hard-coded
What do you want to be able to do
Is there going to be able to get these from the back end
We want to be able to edit them delete them
And add you to do as well
To be able to do that we need a lot of apis
You need an API to add to do we need an API
Get all the tools for a specific user
Let's start designing
Duluth
Apis what should the URL what should be the method which should be you should we use a guest should we use a pool should be
Use up
It's located right now
I need one
I would want to be able to retrieve
All the truth
What are you
Second one I would want
Delete delete
Also you was
You'd want to be able to create a new
Which equals method to be used to retrieve all students per user typically get
And the baby will Design the service
Is to have a URL
/
Username
The Flash username to this username
Would be up at 11 and we're going to get
All the kudos for that specific
How do I delete a
Maybe I can do that is by using the delete method
Delete
Request mentor
And you want to pass in
Which to do you want to delete the to do_ID
How do you do that
You can do that
Is by using
I know you'd want to edit or updated it is nothing but an update whenever you update resorts
You want to use
Amazing stuff will remain exactly same as Italy to
What does particular
You won't update at 2
And the last one is a creating YouTube
Which method would you use to create a new
Using post method
Which one do you want supposed to
You'd want to post to be
URL
Creating a weekly to get results a delete without applesauce and apples
We start with
Creating
This results
Will it reduce per user
I see you in the next