Latham
Back
Any previous steps
Reconnected
Trustage
Deep doo-doo service from the back and we are not leaving or Little Deuce
From the back end
If you go to the backing and make a change
UTI
Tous
Beauty
The new data getting selected
Let's focus on adding more features to our page
Let's add delete update and add to do features
It starts with adding the delete
Feature
In the next few steps
To be able to delete something you don't have a service exposed what do you want
Delete
/ user / username
Truth and the idea of the to do
So let's just so let's make this something like this
Where do we need to create this you need to create it in the to do resource
Let's go to be to do the service
What time does
Is this in
What do you want to do if you would want to create a delete method before we created delete method in the desert
We need a delete method in D
Hardcore
Chubbies
We can call it and delete
Dtube
It's quickly create a to-do
Delete method
Public
Listen to return the deleted to do back
BD. Find that station
Chelsea
Delete
Eid into long ID
Pretty specific
Let it through to do is equal to
Find by ID
And I
Potato method qualifying biology very soon
What you can do
Produce
. remove
Need to do witches phone
We don't really have defined by any method yet and the other thing is to Desert remove uses the equals method
We don't really have a eclipse with a different on the closest gold and Define it
You can do it right click
Send it to us
Kindred hashcode and equals
Excuse
Just the ID
Caillou just the ID too competitive
You see that there are two methods regenerated hashcode and the equally important logic
I do that same only then
This would return to back
That's cool
Did you do hard Credit Service doing a fine by ID
And we are removing that to do
Create method find by ID let's make it up
Public method
Turtleback find all looks cool
It should be simple itracing right to f***
To do to do
It's I'd like to
Too early to deuce
If
True. ID
Is it cool to do
Student is equal to ID actually
You should have to do that
Get ID
That's his color ID
Pretended to do that
Send a message to this phone
It would return to go back
It finds my ID
And if
Today
Is equal is equal to
Let's return
If we are able to successfully return the
Delivery to.
Return digital back
Be safe then you can actually check
Determine if remote is it successful
Then return to do
Otherwise
At the end you can't a return
So what are you doing here is very simple checking at this point if we are able to find it to do
At this point we are checking if
Dalida to remove Italian store. Veritas access with moving it
It was successfully moving it
Then
We had a thing to do back otherwise
We have to go back
Let's focus on the delete method in the Total Resource
What should we do in here
Let's
Cuz this URL isn't in here user username
Cruise ID that looks good
Public
Typically what you do the response it is that we should return, delete method there are two options either we can return
Texas
Are we conditioned no content
Took to the no content option to respond
Without any content to return a specific status back
Texas teachers back so did not really need to use a response entity because that's a default
But no we want to return a specific status of no content back and that's the reason why
The response of delete
You need to have Tupac
Variable
String the first one is username
The second one
He's
It should be a long ID
Let's
Did a few compilation errors let's work on it after we
Maybe intercourse music
Control panel command when I put response entity that's cool
Did you leave to do method
It's not hurting anything.
It's called to do
Service
.
Delete by ID
Did you leave by I did method
I sent a statement to a new local variable
90 continents
Then it means
It sucks ass please delete it so I said it done
Responseentity
.
Status of new content
If you had sex feel deleted
It's eaten a response entity
. not found status
Actually we should attend responded.
So what we're doing here is Bo Kimble candy to do service delete matter
And in that situation we're returning on no content.
Otherwise meaning of northsound status back
What are the important parts of building restful Services is deciding what to use
Helps us to build
Specific request with the Six-Day Justice and that's the reason why we are making use of this month in in this place
Request
Goodwill
Research method
Ford Elite
The Next Step
It's fine eczema Des NC
If we're successful dating that I'll see you in the next