Using a specific kind of encoding for this specific
If you go to the web security concrete this is where we specified the algorithm which we use
Bcrypt password encoder at the encoders
What is alchemy
Today
Create a new Java class
And let's call this
Bcrypt
Encoder
Test
If you'd want to add animated
What I would want to do now is I would want to set up new user with specific password
Lucille's BBQ Concord open till 1
Exciting you be critical.
Youkilis encoder
And if you look at the encoder
It provides an code method which you can send a password out
Let's make it a little kitty 1password at 1 to
Say this is the password I would want to encode
Alison Eastwood
Encoded
String
I can do this in a loop
Pink eye
Tylosin equal to
Let's + let's initialize it to zero
Should be fine I think
And
Let's
Truthout the encoded string
Let's run this brightness Dry Creek
Sun as
Job application
You would see that there are a number of hash values which a printed in here let's take the last one
And
Let's configure a new user that uses as a hash
Did everything is this too long
Tonga
And let's add this is T
Hash value that we want to put in here
And
Let's leave the roll Astro user to that time
I'm sitting this
When I go to the Westlake light and when you see localhost 8080 authenticate and
You provide the username as ranga and password as whatever we have put in here to have put the password in.
5th and Cortez
As if you can remove the authorization header the only thing which you didn't want to
A request to this you would see that it would succeed fine so you get a 200 and you'd get a token
Things that you can add new users we looked at how to add a new user with the encoder
Password
Nxtstep let's look at a few other things