Welcome
Back
Is it step
Let's implement the server-side
Foot chart
What are the things about chart is a good free books available to create dechart tokens
Heller integrating chart into an application
These are very very tedious job
It's almost like 400 to 500 lines of code before you'd be able to integrate a chart into an athlete
Education
What I've done is a made a simple custom frame but available on the GitHub repository of the course
If you touch for JWT components
You should just search for gwp space component
You'd be able to get
To this specific part of the code
What I would recommend you to do is go to your
Eclipse start with
Stopping to server
What time do is I would start
With reflecting the
Basic authentication fact
And I would move it to a package
Something like
Call me in 28 minutes rest
Mesa Court
Idea is because
The idea is basically that
LED components
Which are Pleasant
Inside
So what we're doing is
Effectively disabling basic authentication configuration
Okay
So what happens now
Backpages
LED components in packages
First thing I would do is go to the GitHub repository and search for JWT components
And you can
Pick up D
Application. Properties configuration from there
What I'm doing
Copy a few things let's set this up first
And will understand what is involved in each of these
Pretty soon a jar cute in that we would need to import inside go to the pond
Import
Lake City
Dependency right beneath
Spring Security
And
The group ID for it
Is IO.
Jason Webb
Token
Artifact ID for it
Jjwd
And devotion between want to use on that specific component is
10.9.1
And as soon as we continue this
You can go to the ATM deposit Tri copy all the code make sure that you're cutting it from the top
2D bottom
Coffee'd interesting until the last class which is JWT token response
What you'll see when you could try and copy this in
Is UT a lot of compilation errors
Fixing very soon
Before that
Create a new package I want to see the package specifically for jot
Alkalisk.
JWT
NC
Finish
There's a package which has created here
Now I can go here
Cutesy.
Space would create a number of
Java Eclipse magic which you are seeing in here
And what we'll do is cyclic
Source
Organize Imports
So just do what I click Source organizing port on
That and Jessa continue when You Face edits we fix all that stuff very soon compilation
In some of the components of things which will do right now if you create a new package
Take me to new package
Can I call this
Ashley Stewart's
Sol Duc.
. resource
Topeka Avenue
Package
No I do not like it
Refresh problem when I don't really do it
No I see a chart
Resorts in here
There are a few resources that we are exposing
Get the jar.
What I would want to do is I want to move all those
2.2 the sea package
So let's start with the S controller
Betoken request
Betoken response and the authentication exception those are all the things
That I would want to move
Resource
These are related to the first resource
That's the reason why I would want to move them to this package
These
How did I get
Refactor
Move
And I'd move it to the package
JWT resource
Out go here
And like it
Source
Auglaize Imports
That's okay
Have problems
Cyclic
Defective
It's a continue
And let's open one off
Each one when they are organized Imports
And selective iTunes
Cytosol Gas telephone J logger I choose Argus elephant
Chocolate Factory
Enough you see that despite
Is
Somebody cool
Next one
Control shift
Are the Comanches to
Olympic wardrobe malfunction
How to use
JWT clock which is the first one
The most of the things I'm truly first when Java util map
This compiles this might be interesting exercise
How do I really get somebody to set up a project without really importing it completely
Open up this resource which is present in here JWT unauthorized respond to Temptation entry point
This is one of the important ones
What happens is
By default the authorization exception
Authentication exception that we have created in the application would be imported in
Actually what we want to do is we don't want to use this ordination exception that we would want to use the authentication exception
Spring framework
The thing is
Liquid import Eclipse directly pricing uses something which is inside the project Anarchy
Cobi don't want that
I do that and I will do a control shift
I know it's not just all the other ones
So this was
Imported earliest I would want to use
The one which is Dublin
Define which is used in
Security code authentication exception
Utilities code would compile
I think this was one of the TPS wants to import properly would all be pretty straightforward
You just need to make sure that you are importing the
First one
So just make Nordstrom fast Mix Cement
Safe
And the last one
Compulsive talking
Objects
That's it
Not we have the entire
GWT stuff
Set up
The Next Step
We'll try and execute this code will try and run this cold and sinus and what's happening in the background
And the step after that
Delete get to looking at Discord again
I see you in the next step