Welcome
Previous step
The enable JWT authentication on Earth Project
And this
Let's look at how to execute request
When I do a get request
Industrial Light
Localhost users in 28 minutes to deuce
What I get back is a 401 response it says
You're not authorized to get away
Get out of here
And if you go further
It says you need to provide a JWT token to access this resource
How do I get a JWT token
The baby have designed it
Is UT to send a
Get request
Forget request
Think about it
8080 / authenticate
You you need to send a
Request
And the post request needs to contain the following information
The first one is the username
The username
Plus
In 28 minutes
End
We need to have
Password
What this URL would help us to do
Get a JWT
Password
Dummy
End
So username in 28 minutes
Password. Me
Send
Let's see if this exceeded
Still give me a
I'm getting an error and when I go and look at it it says
But expecting it, that's the problem
Do you need to have a, here to separate diesel
And I kick send again
Enough beauty that there is something green at the bottom
You see that I'm getting a response back with etoken what a loser copy this token out
To copy the Coconuts I'm selecting everything and copy token out
Make sure that you're coughing the entire thing
And I put it into my
The reason I'm doing this
Cummins diesel control/
Then I'm doing this is because totokl
This every chance that you might make a mistake
It's better to pop it into a text editor and make sure that you're copying everything between between the double quotes
Is everything in between the double quotes
Forms
Dokkan
This is the token which is most important for us
You can find out what is present in this
Token
I'm placing it in here
And you can see what is present in this token
What is the biggest organ
Denver temperatures uses hatches 512
The subject is in 28 minutes there's an expiration time on the token as well what is expiration date
It says
Number 17
And today's November 10th zodiac fashion time of the token is of beak
From now one week from now
It says invalid signature
The reason why it says invalid signature is because
Gwtw does not know what my secret key is
My secret key is
My secret
Secret actually division secret if you're really using this in a production kind of application
Should at least be 64-bit in length this is a very small
Secret
Wedding dress tinting of astigmatism
Betty fired you can see that
This token contains all the information you would want to use
Let's go back to This Little Light enough I would want execute URL
The service which free were looking at earlier let's pick up in credit when it's
2 deuce
And I would want to send a get request to it
By default if I send it
What I would want to do is I would want to add a header
Devalue
Be careful with typing it should be better
So it's Barrett Bearer
Followed by the token
I know you'd be able to see that I'm able to execute the request response back
Viosk for a token
Once I get a token use it for
Continuous request
Egyptian token
Has an expiration time
Expiration time for application is coded in here
About two weeks time but if you don't refresh the token what you can do as you can send a gift request
To be
Clicklist ATT refresh
You can send the authorization in the same way
So just like any other requests you would send the authorization with the token to authorization
Andy token
And you'd see
Dokkan degenerated token
It's not us refreshed van so you are getting a new refreshed
Token out
Except
We looked at the entire floor Resort
How to get a token by Sonny request to the Authenticator
And then
How do we use the token to make requests to the server and after that
Below deck
Refresh URL Works how quick and efficient broken if it expired
The Next Step
Let's look at what's in the code
Behind the services that we have created