Back
As you can see
Beer making progress towards the end of the course what are the most important things that is remaining is
The subsequent steps
Data service
A few things that we can improve
Something is
Burn is repeating
A number of times if I would want to change, Dev server to a cube
Then I will need to change all this stuff if you create a constant
And use it everywhere you could make it easy
And to do that
We have the token names and things
I couldn't find a few places
Let's fix that
Let's do a small change in the distance component
One of the things I have observed just now is the fact that
Yeah actually reversing the target date and is completed
Actually diverse
Closest Target and then he's
Is completed
I just interchange these two columns
Is present in the retarded is completed shows
That's cool that's good
To the authentication Service
Avakin do that dispensing export
Constant
And give it a name
Tootsie user
Session
Attribute
What's what should we name for that it's authenticated user
I can use this token everywhere
Can also make use of this for making use of this in the specific
Galaxy place where we were using authenticated user with
Username
This would ensure that if you'd wanted change the attribute name is
Present at
Just one place
Let's do a quick
Search for authenticated user
And this is the only place which it's being
Stop this is a URL that we have been using until now
This specific thing is used in multiple places we are using it's a notification Service as well as
Did using it in the true data service
What are the best practices is to create a separate file
50 Constance
It starts with us call
Constance
.
And in here
I can say export
Constant
API
URS
Is equal to and Ice to localhost
Localhost
Enough what I would want to do is make use of this constant
Everywhere inside of the hard coded stuff
Debate I can do that
Eastbay
I'm putting it into here for API URL
From God.
Slashdot.org Constance
What we can do if we can replace this
Except this would want to use
APA urltv we can create a variable and use it in his passing dollar
Open please
And with that
I have to change this
Backtick
Taking out Tuesday quotes
Sufficient
Total
Do this
Everywhere
Turn up over here also what you want to do
Backtick
The API URL used inside the Authentication
Service
Data service as well
Cottages
Best it out here
Important that you are and this would be
Darling
API URL
We are already using so that's cool
Fully delete
Tactics
So that's cool
Do we just need to replace t
Video chats
Easy
Now let's see if samples
I think I'm files fine
Before we do anything let's do a lockout
And lips
Login
Let's do get one, cities works
True Lux
Contrite
I didn't delete as well almost everything
Would be working
As expected
What we did was
Fixed two important things one is the history of things to do
Which was not right for spite of this course and
We struck repeated multiple places and we created a constant for it and created a constant
38.
Have you started making use of the APA
Everywhere
I see you in the next