In the previous step
Be added in
The URLs for JWT Authentication
Let add JWT Authentication
2 hours
Sentence
What do you need to do is when a user tries to login
We need to send a request to authenticate
Ura
I'm trying to get the token back
Once we have the token
We can use the token
On all the subsequent HTTP request
Let's get started with the first part right now with you
When are you relaxing you should fall into basic authentication Service you'd want to call V JWT
Authenticate service
What time do I create a new service
Should be very easy
Execute
Alcala
Jot JWT authentication Service
Do you already
AT&T
What you need to send
What do you need to send
He's a
Post request
The username and password
That's what we did when we were executing the service
From the client sundress client
So we didn't need to do a post to this URL
Username and password inside the step number one
We completed the post receiver will use this
The case will be using it is indeed login component
Oh here
Copy this
AC down here
And
Comedy code
Milano using d
Basic authentication Service what we want to call is execute
JWT authentication Service
The thing about JWT authentication Service is where does it return the token back
150 service
You get a response with the token
Lights
When
We get the response back what we need to do
It's use that token
JWT the important thing is
We don't really need the username and the password anymore what is important
Is it token
Where does the token come from
Encrypted password we need to use the token
Fidelity token come from
Betoken comes from the restaurant
Hindu response data
You would have something called a token to response. Later
Dokkan
So you need to pick up this broken I create a new method actually it's not register successful login let's call it resistor successful
Login
JW
Because the other mother was accepting username and password I love this one will accept username and two
1 things successful login is registered we want to show the welcome page stuff remains exactly
It's not the gate D
Do you still successful login for GWT method
Let's go down here and let's call this
Username
Dokkan
Exactly do the same thing what we'll do is we'll
The item into
II storage
Set PS logged into
The next thing we want to do is
You need to set up the axios interceptors for that
What Windows desert interceptors
And instead of
Creating basic auth token what you need to do is create
JWT
And passed Jersey token in
The JWT token we don't know how to create Adidas created in the back in and given to us
Where is the method to create
Basic Atoka Nasir italics copy that
JWT token to create
JWT token
Ending to this is a token
And
How does a
JWT header look like
Nothing better
So we need to save data
Bless
The token which came back
That's it
Let me date until now
What are you doing this weekend
Calling Dee
JWT authentication Service
And if this accessory response comes back
BFG g-string a token
Ford Interceptor
Said this token is the used on every subsequent request
Let's see what happens right now
28 minutes
Dummy
Unlocking
Cyclic inspect
And go to the network and see what's happening in the background
So what I'll do is I'll do it.
Damien game
I can see the
Authenticate request to Trenton
I can see that it came back with the status of 200
You can see the request you can also see the request
Payload if you go down
And you can also see the response response contains the token
What do you need to do from now on if you don't use this token in every subsequent request how did we
YouTube that feature
Bay
Register successful login for JWT
What we did is we set up
Interceptors
Is no longer the basic whatever it can be any Heather Wright
To actually go control change the name of this to token
You can call us with any token and this token would be used
Every subsequent request is having the authorization token
Lyft logo
Make sure that login
Clear this cancel out
And
Etsy request to welcome
Successful
If you see the request
How's it Go consent
If you look at the request this is where the talk listen better
And the token that we got back
Trump
The authenticator Vesalius
In the last few steps we talked a lot about JWT
Heading to Bonita Beauty and defendant was very very simple all that we needed to do was Call of Duty WW2 authenticate service
Get the token back
And
Payday deceptor
Every subsequent HTP Quan will use this token
Weather
A simple as that
I see you in the next step