Welcome
Then come to the section on
JWT
Jason
Dokkan
GWT is also called
Chart
So that's what we would be using to refer to this
Trump
Before we start with jot
Start with
Indication we have been using basic authentication until enough
We saw that
Hispano basic authentication what we send is a
Base64 encoded
Username and password
Important thing about basic authentication is there is noise
Violation
What happens if there is no expiration time it's invisible to get access to the basic authentication token
Value
Then he can use it for a limited time
And the other thing is
Basic authentication token does not have any user details on them doesn't have any authorization.
User ID and password
And that's right
They were a number of atoms
And create custom
Token-based Authentication
The discussion token-based authentication systems Define
Output is a token
It's some kind of a hashed value
These tokens contain
The use of details
The user authorization
And any other details which
Temperature talking to each other
Custom structure
And because of it
There might be security floss
Order. Of time what happened was we evolved
Carmen
Token
Standard
Which is called
Jason
The awesome thing about chart
Is that it can contain user authorizations
And a number of other details
Standard part
Which is Define
Diddy's apart where you can extend and add your custom ink
If you go to the website
Jw.org
This is built by Dion
You see that Jason Republicans are an open industry standard method
40 Pleasanton claims
Between
Two parties talking to each other
And
You don't want to know
What are the claims
What are the authorizations
At a specific use of hats
You can use
You might be wondering what is present in the jail
Beauty what is present in the jar token
Look at it
So what do you think on the left hand side is the encoded the final token
On the right hand side what is present
Information which is present in that
Contains a header
A payload
Peak Nature Park
I think we should present in the Hayden are typically the algorithm bought algorithm are you using
Hashing
So if you look at
Here
Examples that will be will be using HS 512
And you see that this
The algorithm hsv-2
American pain Society
Spend it
Yout
Hdwt
Pandora contains
A few predefined elements
The name is
The name of the person
You can have additional things this admin to indicate that this guy is an admin
The I-80 here indicate
Creation time of the token
In addition to this you can add custom Define stuff as well
You might add what are the authorizations that a specific user has
The last part of the JWT
The verify signature
It contains
EBay 64
Encoded
And also
The last and also one of the most important parts of Girard
Is UEFI 12 bit
Secret
This kind of yogurt
Cream
What is providing the JWT
They can have a secret
Which should not be revealed to anyone
Make sure.
When you decode it only do guys who know the secret would be with decode
Properly
You can also do base64 encoding on
Secret
So what do you think in here
The most important parts
Off the chart
Typically what do you do in web applications
Example
Application what do you do
When user logs in with a user ID password
We would send a request
City Cellar
And you would get
JWT token back
And for all the subsequent request
We would be using jot
Body JWT token as part of the
There would be an expiration time also on the jar tokens
You have to send a request to something called a refresh token
Are you asking these key for the new token
Alexa set let's look at how to implement it
How to get defendant pill
I'll see you in the next step