Let's review
The code that is set up
Bjwt flameburger
We saw that there were a number of resources that are being
Exposed
When
You do app.
/authenticate
The expected request was
With a username and password and we got a response with the token JWT
Videos of MattyB
Wendy wanted to refresh
What do you need to do
You need to send a gift request
To this refresh
URL
That would help us in
Refreshing the token there is nothing that you need to send along with the gator request
He's
Authorization header
Baby
JWT token
The only other kind of request letter I want to request a resource
I want you to get requests or opposed to Auto put already
What do you need to do
You need to send a header
Dgwt
Dokkan you need to send authorization header
With bated
The JWT token
This is what we saw in
What are the important things to understand this
Twt
Tokens are very very complex to handle length
If you see this one
It's so huge like this
What are the tokens which we used in our own application and this is huge
Another reason right
Putting all token processing we have a file called JWT token UK
Diesel plus in creating tokens
Delta's in getting to find out what is the username what are the rules that
Allowed for hospice
He has
There are different claims
Helps you to get details from a token
As well as it helps you to create a token when
It also takes care of only
Expiration date in China
You need to calculate when in Spanish
When I go to token what is expiration date on it
Adhesive past expiry
The one that kind of logic
Built-in
JWT token YouTube
This is a fine and you'll see that there are a number of methods are present in here
Get username get expiration date
East token expired
Genedata token
Official token
Validated
Stuff is done inside
Is extensively used
Bjwt
Interesting thing
Is the JWT token you makes use of the JW
PS classic
This is from
The lottery that we had
Important
If I do a sink
UT.
She's coming from
DJ W
Which we added in
The mixed ones did resources themselves
He won't expose these two urls
The input for this order request for this
Username and password
This phone is stupid
So this is like any restful service that you would want
Toluca's 8080 / authenticate what would we typically do
EPL results
Same thing with a splash of fish
For this is the token and the output
Again is a new token value
I'm not really put the response in here but the refresh token
Would also return a response
Containing
How are these resources implemented
There are four
Important files
The code for this
Digital token request and response
Represent this request
And this response
Do you see that token request at the username and password and
As simple as that
And you'll see that the authentication rest controller
Contains
The important methods to be able to handle our resources
If you want to refresh
And the creator of vindication
Toyota
Request mappings for them
You can see that these are being picked up
From the property file so if you look at application. Properties
That's where this URL cycling
The authentic list what it does is it
First uses
Spring Security
To check if the username and password
And password is right
You go ahead and
What does the refresh do refresh plus 6 if token is valid if everything is fine then it gets
End
He takes expiration date and if it's all matching penetrate the token Android
We have a specific exception for authentication which isn't in here
These are the important files
Which are corresponding to the implementation of the gate open and the first token resources
Let's consider all the other requests
What should we do
Send any requests or get a post a foot or a delete
Do any of the resources
What do you want to do
Who wrote the check if there's
Light
Token on it
Authorization header token containing the JWT
And if the JWT token is invalid
U of L application experience how do we Implement such kind of requirements
I want to
Do something
For every request
What do we do is we use something color filter
So what we do is we Implement something called a token authorization request filter
2 for every request we want to authorize the JWT token and that's what this Pacific
Filter access to do
What's a Despicable do is check if the user is valid if the user is
The use of JWT token is valid
Token is valid
It would love to use the details
And it would set it
In Too Deep
Security context holder. Get count
This is one of the places which is most important to once a user is authenticated and notarized
You put his details
So that
All the others servlet
All the other resources controllers
Would be able to access to user
Lipsi
What did you the details
That the user ID password what are the rules of the user
I stayed in a database
Destiny name that poor bastard in
What Spring Security that says is I don't really want to worry about where your users details are
What do you need to do
Is I give you an interface
You implement interface
And make sure that you provide the flight implementation
I'll tell you what is the signature and what should be the return value
Implemented
Provide it to me and I take care of using these user details
To authenticate the user
2 hour rule
Ainsworth providing the user details
What is a Tervis
That service is the user details
Service
This is an interface which is defined inside
And what we're doing did the Endeavor user detail Services implementing the user Detail Service
Folding method in the use of detail services
Load music by username to give
Do any username or let you need to do is to provide
And implementation of this interface
User details
The implementation of the user details that we have created
JWT
User
So what do we do
Oh here in the specific user Detail Service is when swing security gives us a username
And it deleted back
Indy formatter
JWT user details
Tubidy
The big contract
It is provided by
Sting security people service
And return the user details.
What happens if Spring Security would start
Using this
Everywhere
Where to buy Springfield wants to find out
It's April 1st
Give us a username
Ask for the details
And what is the weather like details
Ring security would take care of getting the password
And all that kind of
The last part is actually to bring it all
Together
And I have lied but I do stuff that we are configured
Acquiesced
We want to consider our own custom user Detail Service which has a memory details
In addition to that be something called a password encoder
Get on Google Store password as it is we would want in Kuwait
End story
And that's why we use a beaker password in Kodi
One statelessness we don't want
Section
Creative photos
India application
Rest API we don't want to have any session on This Server Authentication
Entry point
Authentication entry point is all about handling on
Authenticated
Users
What should be the response that we send back
Because of a Bell application the authentication entry point you want to configure a form
A login page
In the case of the rest API or
In the case of a JWT authenticated Sapa what we would need to do
Is gluten a natural response response
Request. Not have a JWT
And that's what is implemented
RT
Best phones
Authentication
And you see that it wouldn't just
Unauthorized
Response
So give me the Quan figure that
The other thing you need to come to visit. Which we have created the equator Africa
Tied it up with distinct security
The flame book
The last thing is
At the end of the course will be using something called
Stu console
Prison inmate database and using his to cancel to look at it
Want to make sure that this URL
It's not secure
Psy.d
That is a default configuration which is already provided by Spring Security WEP security converter adapter
Be extended this even when we were including basic m
Basic Authentication
The extended footage
DWTS
The important but this is where the internal user Detail Service is configured and they're saying
YouTube Tuesday
Decrypt
Password
The next important piece of court is this
PSA authentication entry point
Justin Heyman
You want to create a stateless
Zaxby's is very a configuring in defeat
Every request
Should go through
JWT
Authentication token
If it's long video
Jeffrey McCarthy Johnson look
What are the important things is everything that you're saying is just one X adapter
For the most part you don't need to modify any or
Look real
Little bit
The different resources that are related to JWT are implemented
End the refresh token
Pizza Hut
We are filtering every request
To make sure that every request is
I see you in the next step