Welcome
Green want to help you get
Quickest started with the course
Something I would want to do is to congratulate you on making a great choice
Let's get down to getting started with the course
GitHub repository of the coast
You find a link to it in episode section of the video you're watching right now
You just have to hold over to the left top corner of the screen
And you should see resources
A link
Two digit positive
Just click it
943 and bookmark DUI
Triple Tree contains link
Do all installation guide views
Step-by-step details of the course
And
Also
The source code
What's a present
Is the source code at various
Intervals
OTA course
Examples of these files
You see that this complete backup is present as
Single file
Acts as a reference if you face a problem during this course
You're having a problem with the map method and you're
Unable to work out the syntax
What would you need to do
Is the good
Guwahati backups
And find out how it's done
You just need to search for tools. Map you'll be able to find
How it should be done
Perfections of the course
Focus extensively on react
Fanatics
Visual Studio code if you go to the homepage of the deposit and search for
Installation guide
YouTube Sia playlist
Between
Nodejs
This playlist contains three steps
Installing node.js and India
Direction to
Azules
Installing Visual Studio code Java
When we get to the spring boot section of the course
A little later
YouTube pausing video in here
And visual studio code
You can use this playlist
Watch it
Those two tools
If you have sex
You're ready to rock
React
If you have a job or developers looking at
Planting code for the first time the first few steps can be overwhelming
You'll be using a new language
You'll be using a new framework react
Will be using something called create-react-app
New tools
The first few steps
Contain a little bit of
Who interviews you
Did the various parts of developing modern JavaScript
What you get to the second section of the course
You'll be spending 95% of the time
Getting your hands
Recommended approach to follow the course
It'll take the steps
Vanessa
In the order they are Pleasant
Hindi quotes
We talked about the remaining sections of the course
When you get to them
Let's get started with understanding the application architecture