Welcome
BackBeat you just dip we saw that we had to do a lot of hard going to get the 11:00 service and the authentication Service
It's list
Start with removing the hard coating from the Hollywood service and then you'd want to remove the hardcore
From the setup axios interceptors
The get started with the Halliwell Service First
What do you think is
VR
Adding a header in word is exactly what
It's not being done by the interceptor
Saudi service does not really need this information at all like I'm so
It's coming this out
And I'll actually coming
Alpha Center
Coming these lines of code
Is coming out
The need
To send a header authorizations
This is already taken care of by the end of September. We have in here
Recycling Seymour let's see what would happen
28 minutes
Dummy
Logging
And let's
Can still working
Even after
Hardcore Nina Simone
Number one
Number to what do you want to do
Is
The axios interceptors
We don't really want to hardcore the username and password Andy base Accord headers
Louis Malle refactoring
So that we can actually create decider Sunday username and password that we pick up at
Login tagged
Total loser
Do you know this stuff on here and actually I'll start
Putting the same thing
Down here
What time we need to register Texas login
This get
Username and password as parameter that school so I the movie first one
The recreated Basic Auto
Haida
And what I do is I'll make it a parameter to this setup axios interceptors
What is the resistor
Successful login to
It creates the basic whatever
And since it out
Set up back to us interceptors
And this set of axes intersect at an accident
Basic water as an input
And set it into the header
To know you're not really hard coating anything in here we are just picking up the
Username and password whatever user interface using it to create a header
It's
Baby change
Drug enhancement
Dummy
Choose everything continues to work as it was earlier
Vietnamese hot coating it to places
Peter Moody from Hallowell service and authentication Service
In 28 minutes.
This is what we are using to authenticate a user
Act login time
We have basic authentication setup and we can use the backend to do this
Authentication
Next Step
What will start doing is creating an API
Kaaboo this validation
What do you want to do from here
We want to say
Hey API user ID and password and tell me if it's valid or not
And that's exactly what we would start implementing the API put it in the next step
I see you in the next