Welcome
Bearded configuration to allow
Options
Request
Important things that I would recommend you to do this
Make sure that you stop
Died
Your back and compete
To make sure that you are resetting the entire
Restful web services web application
This would ensure that the entire security configuration is refreshed
Enough
You can go over to the front end
Antique
Nick welcome message
Uxie
That the
Request is now succeeding
Thank you. Cancel completely
Close the browser
Came back again to the screen
And now thank you to get ready
I saw that they were to request that were being sent
First one is the options request
And the second one
Is a get request
Authorization request
The first time the authorization request is sent
What happens is a
Pre-flight request
STD is called the options request
And that's what we enable in the previous step
And once we decided
The next request was also successfully get request went through fine and we got the response that the expected
Baby shooting the screen right now
That's cool
If you go to police
Address
Visors that are coming up
You know why it's coming up right let's go to tadoussac
Let's go to home and Toulouse
What is happening music with his failing
Heather's
It is 4 / 1
Not authorized
Why
Why am I getting this
It's because the only fixed
The Welcome Facebook
Specific method to send a header in
Is that good
Yep it's good in the sense that
Let's play secret Quest is working but
It's not letting genderly across the board
How do we make sure that whatever we are doing here happens for
Every
Request
What you can do is Instagram
Adding bahadur
Every request
Please try and intercept request and add the header
How do you define a interceptor
What do you want to do if you would want to intercept the request
And every request would want to add a authentication header
How do we do that with that videos
If you go to the APA documentation of axios
You would see that it's very very easy to intercept request
Our sponsors
So what do we disagree
Create
Would be executed
Before
Behind
Bite then
Any specific instance what we are interested in
Is intercepting the request
So what we can do is we can define a
Function
So we can define a function which defines
What should be done
So inside the Quan Viet I want to add a header so we can define a function saying I would want to add
Syndication head that I would want to pick that data
That request. Use and Define a function
Defining what needs to be done
On this request
As you can see in here you can also intercept the response
And Define what needs to be done
We did that spawns
Set up
Axios
Interceptor
It's not
Created in Hallowell service because then this would
Be completely to be hella Well Service what we'll do is we'll go to the office
Butt isolation
So we already have an authentication Service
Let's go there
Chocolate syrup
Axios
Interceptor
What do you want to do you would want to set up an
Does a pepper axios
Before I'm able to use axios in here I'd need to do it in Port right let's do an import
Axios
From
Oh yeah I can sit axios
.
Interceptors
You can see that there is something called interceptors where you can actually
Set up a few things
So what do you want to do this we want to set an Interceptor on this request
Friend request comes in
What do you want to do
Used to use my third and
Set up
What we should do in the specific method
What do you need to send to the youth
He's an amateur amateur definition
You can see that
Sensores de config as a
Input
You can just go and fix whatever it is the existing config of the request is the input
If you look at
Axios. Get request
We stand this configuration earlier
That's exactly what we're doing in here with the candy
Old country
And you would want to add a header to this what he'll do you want to add whatever values we have Spotify
Find
Let's copy these three things from here
And over here what do you want to do this we would want to use this basic
How do we do that
.
The.
Authorization
So you want to set the authorization header
Do you have what
Use
This
Basic water.
One of the things we should be careful about
Is B12 do this
Only when user is logged in
If user is not loading I don't really want to
So I say this. Is user login
Then
Do this
Adding in a intercept US Weekly the simple method
Which ads
Authorization header
Request
I took this actual thing would intercept every request
I need to add this authorization header
This matter once it's updated the convict should return the country back so they should be
Return back to lips
Return Decon feedback from
Hiiraan
Do you want to call this method
Set up axios interceptors when you want to call this
You want to call it typically
Login X of Wands
You have successfully logs in then what I would want to do is set up the axios interceptor
Interceptors
What is happening in time
BFF
Axios interceptors
And the address interceptors
Simple interest
Seat in action
Let's go
Home
It's not really working
I'm still seeing
Empty listing here
Why
USAA login
So in 28 minutes
Dummy
Jogging
And now if you go to the truth
UTD to do Seacrest
Succeeds
We are able to now see all the two deuce
And
We can also try to add data to do and try and save the details
Suntrans 3 for example
You can also try and create
And delete
And the previous step
Now created an Interceptor but still it's kind of
Hard-coded because the user ID and password are hard coded in
Next two steps
Let's look at how to eliminate
Hardcore Henry don't really want to hardcore the username and password in here
Where do you want to pick it up from think about it what would be the best place to pick the username and password from best place to
The username and password from would be
When are user logs in right when the user logs in his entering the username and password
Beacon big.
Wendia sending the request
See how we can do that in the next few steps