In the previous step be added Spring Security in
And we saw
That you were able to check for 4 multiplication and basic
Password
Being used is a generated password I would want to have a stable user ID and password
That you'd want to use a crossbow
Easiest ways you can configure user ID and password
He's bite going in here in typing in security to speak. Security. Username
Is equal to use it
Music
To typing
The property value in the application. Properties
What you can do is install an eclipse plugin
Call
Spring ID
So go ahead and search for something ID Eclipse plug-in and it should start back
Sting. Security
And finger security. Username
Is a. Password is
To save this
The application reset stupid
That app
You can use this user ID and password
I would prefer to call them
In 28 minutes
If you close the Chrome browser
Relaunch it
It's typing the URL
28 minutes
I'm picking up one of the you Islands
Zocalos
And then you'll be going to the
Login Facebook
ID and password that unit interest in 28 minutes
You can see that the password
And the user ID combination have been changed
Nobody would have more control over
Launch of deep sleep can't you see that big basic authentication also the same password would be used to
Same user ID password combination with the
What year did SV standardized has radiant pass
Even accept let's start focusing on different things
I see you in the next step