Welcome
Welcome to this new section
Securing
The application that we have.
What do we mean by security
Education.com
Things you would have answered
When we execute any request
We are not really needed to passing any user ID and password
Which we are executing Auntie love
Executed without user ID and password I can just go in
And type in a URL
And get the details of the to do or I can go in type in the URL
Aldi to do speech app
Present in here
And that's what we mean by unsecured
Applications
You don't really need to
To be able to access this service so if somebody knows
Do you like it
Then that's sufficient for them they'll be able to break into the application and use the information which is present in
And that's not good
So in the next few steps
We would start our journey
Towards securing the entire application
Woodstock with using a basic approach called basic Authentication
Along with
Every request
Do you need to send a user ID and password
So if I have to agree with this request
Tell me to send another user ID and password
Music of the fact that sending a user ID and password with every request
It's not safe because it's a mitigating user ID and password
Then they can do anything with it
And that's where we create a temporary token called
JWT
Jason
Dokkan
We discussed about what is the difference between basic security in JWT
And how DWTS more secure
Enhance
With Authentication
And have a front-end application connect to it
There a wide variety of things that you need to do
Get set for all of them
And I see you in the next step