Welcome
We discussed the fact that address services are not really secure
And we would want to make them very secular how do we start with making something secure in the spring world
The easiest way you can make something say
Securities by adding a very simple dependency
Spring boot
Security
Steamboat status security is
Spring boot starter
Implementing Security in
Applications
As well as
Let's
Save this one of the important things is not in the application and restart it
Because we are adding a new dependency
You need to download the new jazz
Man does that for us
And you need to restart and you need to really stop and restart the application
So that the changes would be
Localhost users in 28 minutes to lose one in the URL browser
Have you see that it's taking me
Login page
Login page USA
If you type in any URL to the services that we created a deer
Login
And provider username and password
And the default password
Do you work until you see a string like this in the logs
Just look at it and find it and that's the password
This into that in here
And from here on
To be able to
Any number of other requests so you can open up a new tab and also Execute order request
Put all these requests
You'd be able to see the details
The ones you Entergy
Is ID and password with form based Authentication
Ascension cookie is set
So there's a station for you which is created on the server side
And that cookies along with every request
As long as I'm in the same browser
And keep opening tabs
Call request bootcamp
This is what is called form based authentication and desist
Enable by default
Buy screen security
Let's close the browser browser and come back
So I'm opening up the Chrome browser again
No I wouldn't want to execute the same thing
Truthdig
Sounds like lunch the slip joint
Launch app without an account please
Okay David Essex
We will just end up getting dressed
Put this user in 28 minutes to lose
Origin
I've already put it at
Looking who's calling
Not if I try to send
Request
UTC
Apapa
Make sure that you actually started the entire browser
Now he's asking me to enter the user ID and password
I enter a username password to this day's it becomes form based Authentication
What I would want to do is I would want to send something called basic Authentication
Ikea cancel here and you'll see that I'm getting a phone call and response back for
Not authorized
No I don't want to add authorization and I'm the one to choose
Basic
Authentication approach
And username is user and the password is again
The same thing
Make sure that you are taking the latest password from log
If you show password
Password
Fix it
No
I would again click Send
Love you. See that there is 200 response coming back and I can see the details of the response as well
What we are using in this specific circumstances something called a basic or 20
What
Founders authentication is based on a session which is created on the server
End of cookie beaches in your browser
That would be used
As d
Authentication mechanism
I found a certification needs
Additional session which is created on the server side setbacks and
The case of a basic authentication what we do is we keep sending something called a basic authorization header
As part of the request
Basic authorization header it is little different than the user ID and password that we entered
Is this an encoded form of the user ID and password that be hacked
You talk about it a little later
Important thing is to understand that there is a small head
Which represents the user ID and password and it needs to be send along with
Every request
To each and every rest call you may
Gas station
Created for you
Being able Spring Security will look at what basic authentication is really bad word form
And in the next step to look at more details