Welcome
Back in the bridge we created an API for checking if a user is authenticated
Let's start with using axios
Who actually
Create a simple method
Inside the authentication Service so that we can call that
Accreta simple method execute
Basic authentication Service
Crossword
We need to do in here if you need to do actually us
. get and call the API
Where's the APA president
HDPE
Localhost
8080 /
Basic art
What do you know what you would want to do it would want to send a header
So what do you want to do now if you want to send the header just like what we did in the Hello World Service
We want to send ahead and check
Do users login is good if that means that user entered.
Reading chairs are not right what about user is entering into the login and password field
Are not really right
Hey this
What do you want to do is send headers
Let's call it basic or
One of the things I can actually do is actually
Copy this logic which is present in here
Basic authentication header
Calculation
Drop down here
I think it's a bad practice to duplicate the same logic at multiple places so let's not do
What I'll do is
It's coming disconsolate log and create a simple method so what I'll do is
Alcohol is
Create
Basic
Token
Odyssey token which is being created
Andy tactics to input
Username
And Oxford
And what I'll do is over here
Wilderness
Let
Back that is equal to
Do this and return this actually
Interrupting this acting silly
Staticky
The basic headed back from
What I'll do is interrupt
Having a temporary variable for having the basic called Heather
Alcohol
Create basic auth token
End
Boxing
The two parameters username
,
What we have in here is actually answered yet and we have any authorization header
Rename this
So I don't really need to use this
Coming this out
And use the same Medical
Connecticut
Token
Username password
What we have done is created execute basic authentication Service
Is it poly basic what and it'll send Behavior based on the username and password that we have set
Have you gone to call this on the login screen how can we do that
When you go to the login component
And we should we do the call
Over here
So what we're doing here is hot getting the authentication right so we don't want to do that call
What do you want to do is make a call to
Authorization service
Execute
Basic authentication Service
I'm passing
What do you need to passing the username and a password what's the username and password
This is the username and password list
Okay. Username and this. Stay.
Password
Saudi Saudi username and password
And what do we want to do after that
If this request is successful what should we do
We'll find out in a den method right
Catchment
Earlier
When will be hardcore. Indication vedodi logic
In the East condition actually causing a service then we have to actually write the rajic in the den and
Nevada service cuales taxes Uber do I need to do you need to do these two things let's create a simple method to do
Create a automatic down here
What do you want to do
B12
Do exactly what you just been done
You want to login
And move to the next stage
And the same thing over here let's actually
For my disability so I don't really need to
This big
Happy catch down here
I can push this code one level out
Let's define Arrow function again
Cats
Do exactly
What's being done in theaters
Let's
Comment this piece of good is actually be created the executive basic authentication Service
Method
Fitbit listen to the username in token which is entered on the screen that's because from the screen meme added to this
And
Trump said we are getting it and passing to the eggs get basic authentication Service
Requested successful successful login
Request fails
Show authentication error
Let's see if
All this type of well and everything is working fine
It says create
Basic authentication token is not defined
Why is it not defined
Think about it
This in front of this
Let's do it this here
Here as well
And try and login
Enough to get Wrentham Sage perfect
Cruise
Awesome you can update delete an attitude and you would see that although that stuff is working.
What we did is we started using the service which we created in the back in to start doing
Validation
We saw that it was very simple and that we needed to do is create a simple method to call that person betokening
As a basic authentication header
And then we have to change a little bit on our login component we just had to
Call Dad API method and when it's successful do whatever we were doing
When we have the high school did logic and it was successful
Also added in
Logic
2 handed the unsuccessful scenario now you can go here and actually trying to do an invalid
Ignited password and you will see that you get
Invalid credentials
Sabine of have proper Authentication
Implemented Vietnam using the backend to do the authentication defendant does not store any of this
Details
Right now
I see you the next