Welcome
Restart that Wendy added authorization headers
To request
What is happening
What's something Colin
Options
Method request
4D results happened
What happens if Venable you
What happens is a
PreFlight
Request
The before sending the complete request
What happens
He's a request call options request is sent to check
If you have the right permissions
And what is happening
Is that options request
Is being denied
Right now
What we do in the step is will fix this
The other thing which will be working on in this Pacific
It's something called CS
Cross-eyed
Request
Forgery
Focusing
On how to connect with sling security
Open up control safety
350 Hotel Elvis to open up any
Class which is already defined as part of
Send typing WS
CA
Configurator
Which contains the default security configuration
Spring Security
Did I divide variety of methods which are present in here
Helpers configure only security
That the
Insecurities providing by the
The specific method which we are interested in is configure HTTP security
This is the method which
He's president
You can see that
You can order this method to configure specific
HTTP security
You can see the default implementation of the specific method as well
So what I do is I'll start with copying the default implementation of this method and let's override is to
Solve problems with
Options
SLS
Disable something called csrf
OK Google create a new class
Nucleus
And I cleaned it in the package
.
Basic
Cited dogmatic. That's a package in which I'm creating it
And
Spring Security
Configuration
Basic
LA Fitness
What do you want to do if you would want to ask
Staind
WS
CMM security configure
Confederate control space
Is the method which we copied from
It's the Moody
Let's maximize this so that we can see the entire screen
It's the movies line of code
Consecration contains
Spring configuration title answers
Echo integration
Let's enable
Spring Security
And it will
Actually enable
Web security
This is defined in
Insecurities
Enable
Spring Security configuration
So this is to enable spring configuration sadistic and a spring configuration that's what we're telling
By adding a configuration and network security configuration enable web security
It's okay Daddy
Configuration file
Spring Security configuration
Let's do that enable Spring Security
Enough
You can go ahead and customize this
Aladdin
Override
Annotation to set
That we are actually or I do
The method
His mode of a convention is not really needed
What are the things I would start doing
I don't really want to allow form login
Disable form login
The other thing I would want to disable
Thesaurus
Csrf Woodforest
Opposed
Put request
They want me to start having something called a csrf token
I can later point in time we'll be using JWT Json web token so the option to choose to prevent cross-site
Pooja dataquest
You still use
JWT token tobillo use the csrf token so I disabled it
The other thing I would want to do is I would want I love Dupree
Flight request I would want to allow pre-flight request to all the URL
Pre-flight request
Is an options request
How to say
Mattress
To any options method
Any URL how do you spell any URL
What I would want to do is
Put anything matching this
When any options request comes to any URL
What do you want to do you want to meet everybody
So we would want to enable all the options requests
Without authentication and all the other request I love them to use
Https important
This might look complex but actually it's very simple be disabled
Thesaurus
Basically
I didn't a little bit of Spring Security configuration
Toby disable csrf V alarm
We just wanted to use HTTP basic
I thought you was my next