Welcome
In the beaver state
The added in basic Authentication
And be confident user ID and password for our back and everything
Authenticated using basic authentication let's see how different than reacts to it
I'm entering the password clicking login
And oh yeah I'm taking to get welcome message
And you'd see that I'm getting an error
Visited States
Edit response. Data. Message
This is not really working out
I guess I go to right click inspect
TV console
You can see that there is something on Define which is being printed in here let's go to the awakened component and see what's happening
Component
Access line
56 so let's go there
This is the thing which is being printed out as
Undefined
We're going to pick up
Delete data from the error message
And that's
Not happening because a. Restaurants
It's not easy Define
One of the important things to realize is
Sometimes you might not even get a response back
When did you send Everett
What do you do is improve the baby at Highland theater in here
Aaliyah
Reset the error message using this
Directions
So what are you do is not
Create a video
Error message
Is equal to
What we'll do is we'll check
If
.
Message
If there is something called message on there
What is Louisville happened at
Gutierrez message
Error message
Plus is equal to
End
Wheel offset check
The rest of the stuff
So what do you lose when you check if there is a response
If there is a response. Data save this response and Investments That is data
Only then
What we do is win
Do
Set response. Data.
And over here
Instruct the air. Responded later. Message lets you stay at
What do I basically doing is
There two kinds of parasite
Maybe you are not authorized it allowed you having a network problem in this kind of situations you don't get a response back
It all
I'm in that kind of situation ever. Response is null
So you're not going to get the message out of it
What are you doing
What's happening it
Next
What is BHA
If it is anything in the response
And if they're East India picking yet
Up and shooting
Deep Friend lyrics to this change
Outlets
Get ready, and not Beauty
Being displayed
When you look at
The error on the screen you would see that
Why we getting the setup
Elastic VN table basic authentication and what we're trying to do
If you have time to execute
Request
Submitting the authentication details for it
Our request
It's stocked with enhancing the executor Hollowell Parkway will service
What do you want to do in here is who would want to send the basic authorization header Alpha Center here
And over here what do you want to do is really want to send a text additional header
Take a look at the gate method of axios
Actually any of the actress
HDPE methods
Disappoint
Sending in a config as in neck
So what we'll do is we'll use that
What you can send
Object
And in the object
You can send
Hey Dad
So you can send
Hey this
And you can configure what you need to send in the headers
India
What do you want to send it would want to send the authorization header how do we send the authorization
But I'll let you need to do say authorization
You can stay where you at
Aw India
Let's take a quick review again to a parameter
To ask yourself
How do we
Play the basic authentication header we know that the user than B12 uses
Password
What is it
To do that user ID and password that you'd want to make
Use up
To make the basic authentication call
The authorization header from the username and
That's what you need to do a simple encoding
So what else is left
Basic
Is equal to how do we create a header
Something like this
Basic
Followed by a space
Followed by the actual headed to this is basic followed by space
And to this
You need to offend or encoded value of
Username
Let's go
Please password
What do you need to do if you need to encode this
Combination to username: password and then opened it to the string basic
That makes me how you can send a basic authentication header
This encoding can be easily done in
Dallas are using that method called windows
What we're doing here
Creating a basic hot headed this is kind of a standard
Basic authentication header
I mean just picked up the language you using this is how you structure your basic authentication header
The encoding which
Video a performance is called
Encoding
So getting the username opening of colon and password
Adding a prefix called basic to say we are using
Basic Authentication
A simple as that
Hello
Add use
So what do you think is enough when you're making the request
Use this header
Subsequent careful about the syntax
Tate's, here and here inside the object PSN Hindi
Basic Authentication
See how different in reacts
Message
Haha
You'd see that other has changed
It says
Response to PreFlight request
Doesn't pass
Access Control check
He does not have
HTTP okay status
Interesting isn't it
When I did not have this authentication header so let's actually just come in this specific thing so that
Tradition Hillary's not send
Alex
Get welcome message
Existing decided is not present no access-control-allow-origin header is present
But as soon as I add in the authorization
What is happening now
What is happening in Uganda
Request is being sent
Options request and it says
Pre-flight request
Doesn't pass
Access Control check
What does this all about
What's happening in the background
In the next step
And it looks to be
Enhanced our adolescence method
To be able to handle scenarios
Where you going to get a response back
When something big goes wrong you don't get a response back at all
Toby and Heather Handler
And
The added in the basic auth header
We see that
Ven
May I didn't see basic auth header do something for the pre-flight request which is being sent
And you saw that
Begin Again