Welcome back
I don't think she would have already observed login page
What we do in the status let's critic service in the back end
The idea behind that service is trying to login
B-52 Hindi service
Otherwise
Let's move
And it quickly create a service what time does our copy the Halliwell controller and hello world Bean
YouTube basic package
UT a few errors coming in in this
Cancel
Because
So let's remove the other two methods
Quickly
How to change this
Basic
Saudi
You have nothing to this is a get request to a basic Court
And the other thing I do
This is using
Which one so let me check
Rename this all shift r
Psychically Factory name
Adidas
Two Authentication
Send a message saying you are authenticated
At a later point in time you can actually send a lot more
Details as part of the response maybe these roles the user has
And things like that
It's just you are not indicated message back
So this is the bean
That's cool
It's Quickly to Katie packages so we have an authentication beans
And it's T-Pain Halloween controller this is not lol controller select
Basic
Authentication
Controller
Nike Factory name
Book
Enough you see that the application
Everything is fine we have a new service created
It's all right click service
And all them using putlocker.con
Now we have a clean
Basic authentication controller the ideas very simple
Only if you send the basic authentication header
And if what we want to do if you want to hear
ABCya
And if he's having the proper authentication details then it would rain
Open this phone's back
Most of the authentication is actually done
These specific configuration that we provided
I'm having a lot of fun and I'm sure you're having a lot of fun to Securities a lot of fun topic
And there was a lot of fog look in considering all this stuff and getting them to work together
I'm sure you'll enjoy it for the I'll see you in the next