Alaikum
If we must have launched up our first react app
In the browser
Isn't that cool
Let's take a step further in this particular
It's time to make a small change to this year
And see how to get that change lenders in the browser
What is we use Visual Studio code as the ID
And let's not launch the application in Visual Studio code
Jamie installation guide section of disgust
When did launch a picture Studio code this is what you would see
What's see that we have actually lived on a number of projects recently
To make sure that discourse is perfect
Yellow things that you would see in here I help and learn stuff
How do I command you to spend some time with you learn stuff too
Familiarize yourself with the visual studio code
Heidi
There are a lot of things that you can customize
We're going to open up a project in Visual Studio code
The two ways you can do that
When is open folder
So once you click open folder you can navigate
Did the folder where your project is
And you can open it
The other option
East Dragon drops
I created to do app in the specific folder
I can drag it
Can directly draw it
In here
Once you drop the folder in there
We just video called would open up that particular project you can see the different folders from that specific project
And other files which are present in the
Let's pick up one of these files package. Jason let's not worry about what the content of this file is for Nerf
I would want to see this
How can I do that
Doodlebops
Or
But using a control viore command
Is very important because whenever you are working on a file you don't actually work in full screen mode
And I didn't even know you wanted to cover it up at the first thing that we teach as part of a tidy
Adobe or command is the shortcut to maximize window
The other things you can do is also to toggle.
Explorer
Whatever you think in here is called Explorer bar where you can actually
Navigate to Aldi
Files folders and everything related to your project
A lot of other features which are present in
You can search for a file
You can look at your Source control Avenue
We actually put it in a git repository or something
You can actually check which files are committed which are not all that stuff into is controlling
Youkandy bug
As well as
Delano number of extensions you can add
On top
Visual Studio code you can check all that stuff
Let's not worry about all of them let's focus on
Actually learning react
Let me have the application open up in the ID
Changes
I'll open the public folder
Public folder has something called index. HTML
Which is actually
The page which is loaded up
When we type in localhost 3000
This index. HTML contains
The title element
You can see that the Titleist react app India let's make a small change
To-do application
Even
You can call this my to do application
You see that the changes immediately reflected on
That's what we understood right
The averages is where on the list of the content of the page
It's coming from
And this contains
All
Stop you are staying in here so you can see
The Disney logo which is being put
And it says
Safe to reload
The movie headed witches present India
650 change reflux
Decatur fix immediately
Stuff to make it
Easy
Beauty that the changes
Reflective
What's the magic that is happening
How's that the change in Indigo decimal is getting reflected after Jesse's getting reflected
All that magic is happening
Because of the
Create react
When
Beat build application with create-react-app and we started using npm start
Automatically
Keep scanning your code for changes
Change happens
And it is rendered
Important project
Into our IDs Visual Studio code modifications to it and saw that they were immediately
Next Step
It would start looking at
The individual folders
And the different files which I present
I see you in the next step