Welcome
Alaikum to this last step
I'll dispense with section
Intersection of a focusing on introducing components to you
He created a number of components
We also
Created a couple of class components the first company go to class components incompetent was a class component
This one was a function component
We saw that the function component was Sinclair to create
We included only companies that we have created
Inside the app component by using jsx
React terminology
Is the parent company
First component is child comprehend same is the case with second and third component
Is Tukwila called apparent component the first component will be called the child component
What are the best practices that is typically followed in New York
Is that each component is defined in its own file
Intelliscope terminology
Each component is defined in its
Model
A lot of Java developers who come into JavaScript
It is a fact that
JavaScript
Any Javascript file
He's called a model
Is apple juice is not a module and
These are all the classes which are present inside that particular model
If I create a new file
This Pacific
Glass in it
Then
That would become emoji and it would contain the class
First component
Start doing.
In this specific step
I want to take this company
And move it to you
Folder
I would like it and create a new folder
To all the continents would go into this Pacific. Components
And inside components
I would want to create a new folder and call this
Learning
Examples
Related rate of falafel
Counter because countries are not examples that could create will also create a folder for to do
Tarik store all the counter companies in one folder Ristorante through component another folder
Create this component in a fight
How did you create a new file
I need this fight
First
Component
Darth
Js
Xdt any component which contains
Gay sex can be defined
Return extension first company.
And I'm going to
Books
I copied something let's go to the Savages
Do I crack
And
Best
In here
Let's say booty files
Ballico taxied Deceiver
Eric Thompson
Cysteplus component is not defined
Uncle Jesse saying first component is not defined I have no idea where this first component is
What do you need to do
Give me to imported in
So if you're using
A class from a different model what do you need to do
Give me the first import that specific thing in so I would know need to say
Import
First component
What is that sign
.
Flash
Components
Learning examples
Flash
First components
You put this in
Imports I think does not contain a default
Expert
Once you define the module if you want something from this model to be available to us
You need to export
You can export It Is by saying expert
And do this let's see what would happen
When you
Look at this
It says now
There are two NFC this company does not define Recovery Act must be in scope than using GSX right
Community important stuff in
Copy this stuff in
Importing react component from react
No
You would see that the application load Stein
What are the questions that you might be having
Is why is it like this Vice
Component in
Places
Why I'm not
Why does it not work
Rent
You do this
Why
Let's look at it right now
How to open a birthdays
Let's say I would want to
Second take the second component and put it in here
Bus company in here
This can be exported
So I can explode
Any number of classes
From a single model to this model elected into classes
Second component also
What would happen if I put second component
Adding Patilla
ReadWorks
Nope
If I put it in
Braces
And wait for the ride
Google
It works
What's happening in here
Daddy
Is the default export
Set the default exposed alone you can directly use it
All of the recruits but you have from that specific class
You need to put them
{
Deactivate default export from the react
Package component is exported
But it's not really DD4L so if you want to use compliment
{
We were playing around with modules what we did is we could be first component
Andy created a new folder structure for the first component what we did as we created
Be exported this
And the imported D created module
In the ad.
We saw that
Import
The components name
Baht to the module
Guisado de Vaca
Because missing in decompensated Seltzer be added the Imports in
And I said we have to export
Default divorce company
So I could get the first component working
Biggest simple example of moving II export
To understand why Curlew bases are needed
What are all of the stuff is exported from Memorial
You wouldn't need
Godley Texas
Harley Quinn YouTuber exercise
When you actually move the second component
And also the third component
Today on models
What do you need to do is create car company. J6 and second company. J6
And move
The second and the third components to those files
And I'll see you the next step