Welcome
Back
The court at 10000 feet overview of what is a component
And let's talk about something called a
Component
What we're doing in here in the app. Is extending the ACT class
You can see that it's imported from react
To create a component
One of the options is to extend something called component and Implement render
It's movie Extenze company see what happens
My Google application has an address it says cannot call a class as a function
Cuz there's a tie pattern
Because
It does not extend
Component
Let's send out one
Does it work
He said something that is not a function that has no function vendor in the app component how do I show it
Write create a component extending the component class you need to Define.
Send a message to create a simple new component right so let's create her
Coffee tasting decaf component
Calling this
First component
In here
First company
Andy
I want to see it first
Component
I'm saving this
Country browser
Where is the first component is it shown here
Nope
Being shown why is the first complaint not being shown
Because I've not asked
The app to show it to a PC root anything that you would want to show you need to include in the app calm
And what the bay you can include the first component is by saying first component
And I'm closing it right here you can also Define it in this way / first components
Which of these best woodwork
Enough
You see my Hello World
First component being shown in here
Repeating in here by extending component is called
Glass component recall of class components
But the most important thing for now to focus on is the creator
Include the component as part of this food component
Using in here is called jsx
Who look at GSX in-depth medicine exercise you can pause the video in here
Complete Home component College second component
And included in the hello world example how do you do that
I want to see
A second component light beneath how can I do that
Okay I hope you haven't got a chance to do it it's very simple write-up
Glass
Second component
This would be second
And
Even this would be second will it show up
Alicia up
What you need to do if you need to include the second component
Dj6 of the root component
Let's do that
When you come up now
My hello world first component
Second component
Except we looked at how we can create component how we can create
Class components
The extent of yak classical component Define render method will attend ej6 with needs to be
Sean
And that's it
It gets indicted on the page
I see you in the next day