Welcome
Previous step
Resort at the Lakes rjs
Strength to endure the app component
Into the root element
What does this app pumpling contain
What is a component
Why do you create components into your
Let's look at that
Applications are complex right this
Bail application has a header or footer
The pH here it is to do it might be welcome page login page logout page
Stuffy tablets
Baby born to develop applications we won't develop them in a modularized
And that's weird
Components come in
Components
Design and develop each of these
Individual elements
Independent
Reusable peace
What we can do if we can create a menu company we can create a header component
We can create a footer component
And we can create a to-do component as well
Reusable
Pieces of cord
When it comes to Viet
Component East
Typically call
The app component
And that's what people looking at in here earlier
Because this is the first one which we are loading
Into
Root element
Where we talked about a number of things
Depressing is the view
Oh yeah
Guessing this is how
The device should be
Structure
We said we should have text call my helloworld inside
So this is basically the view information to Trieste spring inside the component
Hear you using something called
Jsx
Day6 is an extension of JavaScript
Adidas in the Javascript file including something which looks like a HTML
And this is what it's called
Js
YouTube G6 you can also write JavaScript code to do exactly the same.
We have a view which can I didn't using j6
Do we have logic
A company might have buttons
Might have
Empty boxes
Checkboxes a lot of form elements and stuff like that
So what should happen when you change something when you click a button and all that stuff
I don't have any component you will also have this Dialing for the company and all that goes into
Component.
CSS
File
Which color should something be shown what size
Could it be Center aligned and all that
The other two important things
About a company that something called state
We talked about this extensively
When we develop our next examples
Counterexample in application
Hindi we'll see how State and props play a very important role
As part of your company
We learned that react applications built as a group of components
Each of these components is independent
And reusable on it
The other thing that we have learned is each of these components contained of you
A little bit of JavaScript logic
Dining
And also a couple of things called State and property
It would start playing with each
And the next day