Welcome back
Don't forget that we created a couple of class components first company
The second component
What are the things in react
Is that you can also create something called
Function components
Let's try and understand what a function component
Lakes at Woodmont to wind up at third component
How do you do that
Just get introduced to the concept of
Components and stuff we are creating all the components in the same fight
Actually create a page JavaScript files for each of these
Let's keep it simple. I keep them in the ass
At a later point in the schools will actually move them out to separate files
How to say class
Third component
Extends component
Kohler Company
Intercompany
Reproduced afraid there's nothing new that you're doing in here
Is exactly what we were doing
In the previous step
Superior glass company
Seedeater component India
What paper company that the function component the baby can do that
Is by simply saying function
Third component
To the name of the function is third component
Open up a closed Basin open dress
When inside that
You can see return
What do I do everything from this render glass
Acting classes return
Pacific thing
Removed
Gas company which we created for third component
When you refresh the thing you'd see that the third component would work as well
We can see that creating a function compound is much much more simpler
Diamond Glass Company new glass company and you have to extend something create a specific method
When you create a function component all that you need to do is Define a function with a specific name
Do a return Norfolk that's all
What will you do in this course is very very activating simple components will try and use function components
Glass components
Have a few additional features on top of the function components one of them is something called
We talked about State a little later
What is Lewisville
Try and keep using function components
To keep things
I recommend you to try creating a food components
As a functional component
Included in the display of the page
What is a function
Components
We saw that
Define the function component was much simpler than a class component