Spring boot
And I'm sure
You are as excited as I am
Let's discuss the high-level architecture of the application you're going to build
In this course
Let's start
With understanding the basic function
Turn LED off the app
Application. We are going to build
We're going to build a to-do management application
Everybody has things that they want to do what they want to learn
You want to learn how to develop a full stack application
You can manage all of them in this to do management
You can add it to do you can delete it to do and also updated to do as well
We also have the authentication features typically the login and logout capable
Listing of shipped out at the ancient architecture of the application that we're going to develop
What is a full stack application when you talk about it. Application
You're talking about a friend application
Which is talking to a back-end API
Auto rest web service
React
The building Fenton Park
React is a friend in
Framework and it makes it easy to develop send an application
Would be using modern JavaScript
That's not a problem at all
Root make sure that
You are exceptionally introduced to the modern JavaScript quantity
Before
We would use them
Will be using
Spring boot framework
People using Java at the programming
Reboot is the number one Java framework
How to build restful API and microservices
We create multiple restful services for authentication as well as to do management
As far as authentication is concerned
Restart with basic Authentication
And also
Because about how you can use
Json web tokens for autumn
Spring Security framework to build Authentication
Around all the API
That we're going to bed
Onto the next step
Let's discuss an important question
You talking about building full stack application
Why should you really build a full stack app
There's a lot of complexity associated with this
Do you need multiple languages you need multiple framework like spring boot react you need to learn all of that
Why should you really do that
The answer to that question
Is that you don't want
Flexibility
Architecture
And architecture which can be extended to meet your future needs
Let's imagine you'd want to develop and Native mobile application in future letter and
IPhone app
Maybe you want to connect your application to Internet of Things
Devices iot
Devices
In such kind of situations
We can reuse
The ex
Backing
API
Outback application with the Saturday back-end API order restful API
Give us more options
To extend our architecture
And create different applications
Different device
Quick-Step
We looked at the architecture of the application that we are going to create
Weekly
Fenton app talking to a restful
Back and EPA built on top of
We also discussed
Full stack app
I see you in the next step