Welcome
What are they
And where are they used
Let's start with the most important file of everything
. Jason
If you are a Java developer
UB family
Quan. XML
The maven pom.xml dependencies of java project
JavaScript project
Yeah you specify
The dependencies
You'd need to run a project
Interesting thing
Hypochondriac
Is that
Diaken be used to develop both
That applications
As well as
Native applications
Applications we use react
Dumb
Native
So the core of the react framework
Is the same for both
Browser-based and Native applications and that's what is present in this
And the Egg Dome helps us to run the react framework and
Jet's Pizza basically the ones which provide all the features when you said npm start
All the work was done by
In package. Jason in p.m.
Installs them for you
If you set the folder
Nord
Modules
If you're coming from the job
You can kind of think of the node modules
Similar to
Local Maven Repository
Even as the target foldable you have all the jobs president
So what do we do we have
Presiding here dependencies of Dem
I downloaded Into Thin dude models
Indian
Greenify contains
Documentation about this project what are the commands that we can
Execute
Where you can find more information and all the others
Let's get to the two others
Important philosophers in India public
Insource
The most important file is index. HTML
Index HTML
Sd5 which is launched up when we typing
Localhost
: 3000 into the browser view page source
Why don't you see is actually the content of indexer Testament
Addition with bundling
On top
Aldi
Cold which is present in the source folder
The software that contains all the react
Quartz bright as part of this course when we were talking about JavaScript and react
He was attending to the source folder
Oldest code
Will be bundled as single file or a couple of JavaScript files
Use them along with index artist email to run our application all this work is being done in the background Forest
We talked about it a little later
Important thing to understand is
An integral test email is the one which is launched up into the browser
Episodes in death
A place
So abruptly uses averages aftertaste. CJ's
Decertified which are related to app component
These contain
Code for the app component
Deciding for the app component and the unit test
For the app component
Opposite might be interesting.
We are actually having the unit this
Right beside
The source code
And that's how
Typical Eastern in different world
Incredible we don't really have separate folders for Unitus
And production code
Do you like this
Live right alongside
Yale production code
That's something we might take time getting used to
What's the weather in Port in Fallujah present in Tierra Linux dirtiest and index. J's
Deciding which is best
Only specific to the app component
Pixark CSS on the other hand is
Application
Tualatin resources that we would want to include food included in index rtss
Electric jazz
And index artist you are the most important files
To focus on right now
Indexer decimal
Define
Route
What happens if an index. GS is baby safe
Element
Which is present in the HTML
Haines
Rain Bird DV act application in it
Which continent you didn't delete
Zendaya the app
Component
Look a little new4you do not worry about it the most important thing to understand is what happening
What does that mean here
Nid call Drew
What happens
Dival depopulated
This is the utility method which helps us to do that react Dom
.
Surrender
All Imports and stuff looks
Very very complex for you do not worry
This is all part of modern JavaScript which we get familiar
In the next few steps
The important thing to understand is the fact that
Bia populating
Using the react
Dumb
And that work is done from
Index.
If you go ahead and change something they say I say route one in here
Closest beauty that is Target container is not there is no dominant call Route 1
It's a go to apple juice
Add Kleenex artist ML and change this Route 1
Continuous working
Go back to who
Andrew tinius
Quick video
What's the different folder different files water importance
And things like that
I see you in the next step