Lake
Repeat the steps we use of jsx
We learned
That you can return the j-6 from component and that is displayed as the view a few simple
Let's van understand j6 a little more
You know that we are including jsx in a JavaScript file
I sodi so jealous when I'm actually writing some kind of HTML which we are calling it as they say
Extension of JavaScript
How does this code get converted to JavaScript code
Isn't that a good question to ask
Music creator
React app
Comes bundled something called Babel
Ba
Bpel
So if you do a Google search
For Babel Js
So Babel J's
This is the thing which converts
Justice Court into JavaScript code
Actually
The purpose of Babel is much much much bigger
Define
Browsers
Have different kind of support for all the JavaScript new features
So as a programmer it is very difficult for me to write code which works on all the browsers
What I can do is I can write code using the latest JavaScript standard
And you would be able to compile it to lower version of JavaScript
That's what
Baby labels as to do code in the latest version of JavaScript
And compile it or convert it
Earlier versions of JavaScript
A brother does not support the latest version of JavaScript we can use the earlier version of JavaScript to Randy cold in there
You can go here and keep Detroit out link
What do you want to eat right now
Translate a little bit of jsx Courts
Heading
You can see
Getting converted into
JavaScript code
What is happening here is a method called
Create an event
Indeed react
If yeah it's getting cold
The first attribute which is passed in H1
He's actually the name
What the Note II that tribute is actually the attribute so if I say hi to one
Class name is equal to
Something
It's not really what you want what it is
Then you can see
An object with all the attributes of is basically JavaScript object which is present in Calibre
First parameter is the name of the element the second parameter
Attribute an object with all the attributes which are defined in here letterhead and the Rocky Butte at Butte
Is equal to
Your teeth at that also
In
As part of the specific object
And the last one is it child Elementary what are the child that message a present in
Let's create a little bit more
Complex structure so let's say there is a parent company
Inside that
Let's say there is a
Child
Component
And let's kill the child component out in here
There's some text in the X component
You can see have the JavaScript code for that is I2
The entire child component
Is it cold
Parameter which is passed in here
Create element
Building component,
I don't have any accidents if I have an attitude friend in here let's have parents
Attribute
Is equal to
Who's won
Something it doesn't really matter what it is
Passing the second one as the object
Then you can see
The third one is the element the entire child and Mary just passed in here
Let's add another child element in here what would happen
Another
Element
Time
What would happen
You can see that the enter this particular element
Beacons
The third attribute
Epic react element for parent component
Create an event for the child component the third parameter is
Including the under component
Mickey what we're looking at is a Buick GSX
Gets converted into JavaScript code
I would recommend you to play around with this
Netflix look at a few tips and tricks regarding gay sex
Important
About j6 let's remove this
Disinclude H1
Heading
/ H1
And let sit
Including another
Its 2
What happens
You can see that is giving me an error
You think I just ingested sediment must be involved in Iran clothing tag
You can only have
Parent element you cannot return
2 elements
Together if you want to return to Elvis you have to create
Apparent element around them so I have to do something like this
Today
Active
Hook sleeping in this index light
And then
I can actually
Use
Number one you can look at them two elements from a single j66 like an expression
You can only just returned one thing
Little motions of
You can also use
Empty no time limit
Within the
Not so this is
Kind of open note empty open note this is empty case note
And you can see that this would still work so this creates something called a react fragment
Within that you can have two child elements
The other important thing about
Jsx is the fact that
All notes should be
Close
Even though HTML allows you to have something like this
Well if you'll get this
This is valid HTML and this is also valid HTML
But this is not valid
Deus Ex
MK6 all loads should be closed
So if I say
And inside that little Heaven would be
Can I close a first
It would give you an addict it should be properly close as well
All the mods should be properly closed
Switchback
Dua app component
What are the things you would have absorbed in here and returning it
Inside
(
If you remove the (let's just quit
Incline save it
You can see
Adidas address
Cannot actually do something like this if you want to return a jsx expression from
You should start the gay sex
Expression right on that specific length
You can see that it works but you cannot do this
So you cannot have an empty line and then Define ddj-sx expression
We put (around the return value this would help us
To have events structured
This isn't here is very very important without that the code will not compile
Turn off Beauty. Everything is fine
The next important thing is that first custom Define component
You have to use
Capital letter starting letter
Sexy
And I'm taking the third component also too small what would happen
Save this
3rd companies not at all displayed and if you do where I clicked users
Psychic in state
Go to console
The actor component is unrecognized in this browser if you meant it today then.
Component
Start
With a capital letter start with an uppercase letter
So you cannot do that so you have to have a capital letter
What a function component
The name of the component should start
Aldi small letters are reserved
Put all the stuff which comes from HTML we have hitch one hits to live
A lot of things that are present in HTML and all of them are what
Beetlejuice small letters
The last important thing that you don't understand
Is that when we use Deus Ex
You need to have react
India Import
Glass making use of react at all so if you say sexually active
This import is not at all used at all
It's finally move this
Important
Let's see what would happen
Oops
Lights
You happy Berkeley acting
If you would want to make use of j6
In your components to make sure that you are importing reacting whenever you are using
It looks like when you started with you. Babel Js
Which is the one which converts
Gay sex
JavaScript finally runs on the browser
Tobago
Disick's it converts it into
Dallas
Baghdad
All bags must be closed
In Deus Ex
Define that
We cannot return to tags
If you want to return to tax you have to enclose them in appearance tag
We start at if you have complex fractions to be returned as part of your G6
Better than Kodi
We start at
Custom component should always start with a
Capital letter
Beside that
React should always be in school
I see you in the next step