Welcome back
Let's solve exercises from the previous step
We wanted to create
Separate components for the second component and the third component
I hope you got a chance to solve them if you haven't then this is how you do it to all that you need to do is actually take the shot
And I will call this second component
Kadir sex
The second continental G6
Ramadi first complaint from here
And I call
Default export class II company that extends component
Remove the second component
From here
You are complaining fine now let's go to the apple juice
This importance to change right to let's go to this
Looking for Trinity import bus company from
This
Component from
Second contact
Let's see if it works cool continues to work
Isn't it awesome so now we have the first component the second component both of them in their own files
I'll take the lazy approach again ctrl-c ctrl-v
Did the third component
Function third component
Leave this poor default and copying the function to component
Save
School
Dear I'm not using the company because I'm not extending the component class because there's a function component
Alameda import
Go to the app.
What do you want me to do not I need to import
Incompetent
This continues to work
We have we have import bus company from first, and second confidence on 2nd, 3rd company from Turkey
Components
Each of these files is creating that spicy Classics doing export default
Intervene
XpertThief all along with the class you can also do Expo default
First component
Good thing that I can use to practice which is followed
If you have multiple components it's very clear which is the default component which is exported so you can
Can just search flexible default in the class and find out which component is the default this is kind of people followed in Dallas
Salads
Do that as well explore default third component
Collectible on
Till expert default can be a statement on its own
It could be the last statement
What are the other things you can see his tinikling is not really required to I'm trying to avoid using semicolons as much as pause
Like because of the habit of working in Java I kind of used to Nicholas a lot
Semicolons are not required in 99% of the cases in
Secret Emoji second component and third component into their own models and then put them in the app and beaver
We could quickly use them as well
I hope you're having an interesting time I'll see you in the next