Welcome
2D focusing on the react app
Application
You would want to understand the basic concepts of
Most importantly how do you build components with
In the step that start with creating a simple react application
How do you create a react application
Create react
Uline depandi create-react-app
Is it going to be positive
And you'd see
Let's create react app
By running one command
Ricky wanted us to do is to create a simple react application
Just by running one
Simple
Command
What is the command
Scroll down a little
Securities
If you execute a command which is similar to this
Create react app
What create the basic setup of a react application
Actually it would create an application which is good enough
To take the production
To be able to use create react app
Node and npm
Next Launcher parts
Terminal command prompt if you're on Mac it's terminal if you are on any other operating system
Like Windows for example you have to launch up the command prompt
Just type in terminal and you'd be able to launch at the terminal window
Going to lunch at the command prompt
Type in CMD
Take the command prompt
And it will open up for you
Your terminal or command from this opened
I'll let you need to do is type in notes
- -
Important to high fence in here right so it's not - -
Russian
So once you have
Abortion which is greater than 10
You can also type in in p.m. - version to find out which Indian version
If item doesn't work for you or Liam Payne doesn't work for you
Make sure that you check the installation guide which will bitterly ridiculous
68 - 3x - app
The name of the app
To debate we can do that is npx
Create react
Bass
The name of the
The name of the application I would want to use it
To-do app
But you need to move to the folder
We want to create this particular Apple
CD to the folder where you'd want to create that application
I want to create it in this folder so I'm doing a CD to
In 28 minutes good.
Full stack with the reactants being good friend
And or here
I can excuse the NBA
MPX
React
Space
What is Exodus command Duty that this will take a little bit of time because this would create the project
And also
Titus created now it's trying to
Billy
It's trying to install a few dependencies react react Dom
Angry eclipse and also their transitive dependencies only things that react Dom needs to work on the things that
React needs to work
And all the things that react
If you have a problem at this stage and if you are not seeing
Project being built
Like this or if you get a permission server
One of the things you can do is you can try and launch of the command prompt
As an administrator so if you press Ctrl Escape launch of the command prompt and
Open up
Stop in front
Organic you right click on the command from you can do it on acid
If you are on Mac or Linux you can try sudo
Please reply npx create-react-app to-do app you can try doing
Subaru
Space
MPX create react app tutuapp
Useful thing to do is to Google for create react app troubleshooting this will take you to a GitHub page
Facebook GitHub.
Once you click that
You can see
A few other things
You can cry
That the installation is going on right now
It might take a few minutes
Especially Fahrenheit for the first time
And I've been counting is done
Ipsy
That's it
List the different commands that you can plan
The good thing is Nuff
The entire application is set up so if you open up that specific.
If I do present working directory
Is the polar bear Detroit has created
There is a to-do app folder where all the content
He's created the entire project
Created in the space
Did a member of command speech
Create
React app enables
You can do NTN test
You can do npm run build
Create
A production Deployable
Battery died
Dallas zip code
In modern JavaScript applications will create
Hundreds of JavaScript files
And it's not efficient introduction to have hundreds of JavaScript files
Indian Grand builders
Is it merges everything
Into
Compressed
State of JavaScript files
Which you can then use for protection
What is peaches are actually built in
YouTube application
Is created by using the create react
What you want to do now is lunch at the application let's do that right now to deliver you can block
Take me to Pleasanton near npm start
When you press npm start
There's an error it says I cannot find a package. Json file
Okay cool let me check the present working directory ndls
Hardy AR
In Windows you see that
Indeed
Sentence folder to be able to run
Indians.com and I'll need to CD into the to do
And now let's go ahead and run npm start
And this would kick off
The launch of the
Project
So you can see that the project starts up and launch S8
Indie browser as well
It might take a little while
Bee Gees still loading
You see that
It's showing the URL
On the console
Second one
Launch
It in Chrome you can take this
You are intelligent
Most probably it would have been automatically launched up in your default
Browser
What if it has not planted in your default browser then you can take this year and executed
In this course
Congratulations
We created a react application
Create react app
And give the name of the application to do in team start
Launch that application app
And you able to see the application in the browser
You don't really understand what's happening tobacco
And that's what we would be looking at
Subsequent steps