Welcome
Created a number of resources and all these resources web-based
This data is stored as a static
To do list
And it's time to change that
Let's take this
And put all the data
In the database
You would be using H to as the in-memory database
Spring data
If you knew
2 GPA
Spring data jpa
I would really recommend you to look at the section
Introduction to GPS
We have a section in the appendix
Introducing you to JPS spring data jpa
What is H2 what are the advantages of H2 and all that fun stuff
That section is a prerequisite
To be able to understand what's happening in the background with this
Specific step
And the subsequent steps
Where we use GPS to connect
The To Do List
Or database
What are the things that we would do is first let's start this over
Do you need to make a few changes
Stop the server
Create a to-do jpa resource
So we would let this
Resort
GPA results
And you would happen GPA to each of the URL
That's the approach that we would be
Taking wheel creator
Batman
GPS or exposing a new set of URS
Do the new set of uri's
Let's focus
On getting the database up and running
Populating database with some initial set of data
The awesome thing
With
Jpa hibernate spring data jpa and springboard combination with H2
Is it bad that
As soon as you create an entity
Create
Database in memory
Automatically
Let's see that in action
In the specific step
Let's get started
Irritation I would need to add is at entity
Control space
And this would become
Entity which should be stored into the database needs to have a primary
I need to add
IID annotation control space
Hugo
This becomes did
What are the other important things is ID fields
It's not adjusted to have a primitive
Because
Typically indicates
That's an entity
Is naughty attitude to the database
And when you use that entity and save it to the database that means it has to be inserted
So what are you doing this weekend making this long
I thought you wait this long you should see a few compilation errors
Text exam
We'll start with
Can you get ID to Long
State ID
Utility to hardcore and service has an error
Let's go there
Exactly this is Daddy's giving the competition
Lucid change the account
Oolong
Once you change your contact log everything should come by
No I go back to t22 service now
Wakulla focus on it will add a fact that
It could be auto-generated I don't want to set the value of the ID
Whatever on YouTube is created you won't make it auto generated
The way you can do that is by
Adding an addition
Call
Generators
Value
What happens if
A sequence would be created and the sequence would be used
To set values into the I know you add a new ID
Insecta value for it
Beehive
The entire entity
Straight up
If you're wondering how did we get all these annotations identity at idea generated value
The answer is when we were creating this project
We already added in a couple of dependencies
Data jpa and that's how we get this
NBA also directed hitch to
That's how we have all different books
Teepee
Hibernate and spring data jpa
Always seemed like a lot of bad words are really recommend you to check out the section on jpa
Indy appendix
And what I want to do is I would want to add in a few more things
Whatever you want to do is I want to be able to see the sequel which is being generated to what I lose
GPS that shows equal is equal to 2
The other thing I would want anybody something call H2 control
Sprint outage to consult. Enable is equal to
To make sure that you have Buddha settings enabled
The application to start the application now and you'd see
And there's some new information which would be printed
In
Start a blog
UT
Data table is being created to do
And a sequence is being created called hibernate sequence
Now you might be wondering how can I check the data in this table
This is a in memory database
You can do that is by going to URI
SATA d h 2 - console
So if you go to that specific URI
You see your page like this what are the important things to make sure is the
Database URL that's too meme
This is a common mistake sometimes the default value which concept is a little different from this
Make sure that you edited and have a hitch to
UCD to do table
And you can text a friend to do you see that there is no daytime
Let's quickly population data in here
But you can populate data
He's
Adding a new musical five
Coming up the other approach would be controlling
Create a new text document and you can save it
Dortmund results
Today's click finish
Good dick to do
The Java class
Cleveland enter data into the specific table
Insert
And this Friday column names
Let's
Calamansi set ID
Username description target-date username
Description
Target date with Target
_
If you have something in common
Music apps
Any database
Typically
What we would do is
Use_
Did you understand that
The bean
You would have to have a good date
End
Set the table would be created
Easy undercut
What values do I want to populate into this
Use the ID
I'm going to start with a large ID value
And I don't want to conflict with it
That's the reason why I would use a large
Ibis
Between 13
The username is in 28 minutes are not really allowed in
And I said
Jpa
Easton
What does n equal in in here
15 suit
And you can insert
Multiple
To do list
Need to change the ideas typically one of the six
Any good show
Username would remain the same on GPS
Test
Data GPS
End
Makeup services
Now we have the
Data
Let's save this
And let's wait for
Application to start and pick it up
If you go today
Pancake run
Actually take you back because it still has to be started
Are you safe through again antique run
Enough you'll see that the data is populated
We made it to do object and entity
JP
And we populated some data for it
Andy was able to see all this stuff
In H2 console
Academy questions about
What's happening how is this working so easily
To check out the section in the appendix on GPS
I see you in the next