Like them back in the previous step
We need to do an entity and inserted some data into the today table
Let's start creating the resources to be able to access to data
What I do. Decide what I want to do is to create a copy of this to do research
Copy this
Is it right to hear ctrl-c ctrl-v and you can call this to do
PA results
And one of the things I would do over here
Is this JP Resorts all the urls
Add in something called GPA and this.
Do you have Beauty services available all the time
Tune-up I would / EPA
This is still talking to the hard coded service but that's okay
Class GPA
India electricity five
Research methods that got exposed from the
GPS has me create a new
Repository
When do have an entity in GPS where you can talk to the entities
The save data
And get information from It Is by using a depository
And finger GTA provides an awesome thing
Which provides
All the features to be able to delete update and get the details of an entity
Pretty easy
Select start with creating that results in here
Translate control in theater new class
And this class over here what do you want to call it
You want to call it
Jpa
Suppository
And inside this
Public interface
Jpa Repository
Alta implement
Expense
Because
You have to extend a repository
And you'll be able to say
And the first thing I would need to send a G+ switch entity
And what is the primary key
Long
That's
You can stop dating instances of this specific thing
I'll say this is a repository class
Thai Dishes
Should I be at repository on this
And let's go over here and now I can add
On djp repositories to do
TPA
And I call this
So what we had enough is be happy to do jpa repository in here
Wwz to do jpa Repository
To talk
2D jpa entity to do
How many votes are present in that specific entity
Delete method to delete
Delete all to delete everything which is present inside
To do table
And so on and so forth if you look at
Hit that a wide variety of methods
Which at exposed by the to deposit 3 by default
We love focus on just the two basic methods
To do the ghetto
Get through
Get to do should be easy
Get to responding direct method related to this
I'll let you need to do was stay
Repository
.
Find by ID
Define the ID in passenger ID
Interesting about the
Find my idgp Repository
Is it would return up optional.
And if you want to get the actual value from.
Get
So that's the first better than
So no you'd be able to get the data based on an ID
From
The database table
How do I do a final
Over here you want to get all the tools for a specific
Username
So you need to do a search
On this to do entity so
Titusville KD data
Wanted a nice present for in 28 minutes
Typically this data would contain data for more number of people
I want to search by the username
End
Only get the tools for that username
You better can create a search method is very simply
By saying
Find
Bye
Nickel element don't search for is
Username
Find my username actually have to make the first letter
Define
Parameter what you want search for
I need a username
List of to-dos which are associated
Music
Would see that the deposit we not expensive fine by username method
If you go to the
BJP episode I can use return
Through
Jpa Repository
Dog
Find by username and pass the username in
And I can come in this off
What you have done is the just implemented these two
Method
There are still other stuff that you would want to do
Before we go any further with the rest of the stuff
How to command you to test different with these two methods
The population of the Duluth should work and also I should be able to click edit
And see the details of the
Steve and the update of the truth will not really work
Enough
Start this again
I already have different and running in the background
TV console out
Connect
Run
Okay cool have three to do switch up resenting here if I go to buy logging out and logging in
What do you see
Exact definition is little different from what is in the database data from the database
Why
Because you have not made the changes yet
Get started with the changes right now
As you can see you still connected to the API URL sold it to do data services are still
Best API urls
You're not talking to the GPS stuff
How can we stop talking to the JPS Steph what I'll do is
How to create another constant
Another College
GPA plural
Jpa to this
What happened
Is
Where would I go to use this URL
This would be offended into DJ.
Beat you up
If you started with the first one which is the retrieve all Toulouse 23 volt
Is I'm saying GPA API URL
And saving this
Before that
We should import it in as well
Toilet in Portage APA
Let's go
It's logout and login again
Dummy
Go to those
It's enough that I get the JPL and data JPL and microservices that's exactly what we have
Indy database
Hello
If I eat Ryan Beauty to do
You might see a little bit of a different stuff
Light
The reason is because we are not really connected
Retrieve to do service yet
It's change that right now
It stains The Retreat to do
USD JPY
I logout
Go to
It would see
That I
I'm able to get the
Do they still use as well as when you say update
You be able to see the details safe
And delete will not work for a little while
Because the rest of the services are not yet connected
But the thing is really created the services for these as well
Any subsequent steps we will create the services for these and also
Quickly try and connect to these services
We connected the retrieve all to do Sunday retrieve to do
To BJ Papa
How are the three method to check remaining in here which needs to be connected to the jba
Not yet available
What will be the next step is creating a place
And
I see you in the next step