Welcome
Back
Reconnected get all tutus
And
Adorable to also connect defendant to these and get everything working together
No let's Aveda services
Delete
And also the update to do
As well as
Creative activities have been
Create to-do Matagorda Zappos via trying to create a to-do in here
All these three
You want to start using two JBL pulse 3
Let's get started with the first one right now
Set the first one let signal delete one
Let's see interruptible service we want to use it to do JP deposit
Activity terms of void
So what are you doing
Remove the assignment and
Lucky Louisville return
By default
No content. Which we can actually remove these pieces of cod
Guadalupe
Peloton no content
That's cool so that's simple change on the delete now let's go to the update through
On the update to do
Yeah picking up
Did username from the parkway
What do you want to do over here is calling this evening
Capacity
Call DCF method Honda to do that's cool and you get the
I did it to do back
Will keep ticks
That's going to be created it was called
Identity by mistake
Excuse the blue JBL pulse 3
Ciara
Getting to jkt forestry. Safe to do
What important things is when you are safety to Derby Days
Did you do details contain
Username as well
Independent you're not really populating the username
Belongs to that specific user
What do you need to do in the Bracken
He'll actually use this username and set it into the to do
What we do in here is to do
Username
Entity to username
We can do this
Update
If you're not go today
Recipe eggplant and you execute all these requests you would see that all these services
What
What do you mean the next step is actually connect defendant to the easy 80s
I see you in the next