Welcome back
Let's connect different a33 jpa repository methods that you have created
Last step
How do you connected them
Should be easy right
Let's talk with connecting the delete
Just Betty blessing
Logout and login again
Delete
You can see that
It's deleted successfully and I'm able to see the updated data so if you look at the
Network that you would see that the request is going to take us and
If you go to the office to cancel and Uber select * from to do
Connect again
Flagstaff
Coyote
The first to do was actually deleted
Let's do something similar on the update
And as well so I'm doing both of them let's go to
Application log out and come back whenever we make a change and come back
Dummy
Toulouse
Update
I can see the change on the front
On the back end that's awesome
It's added you to do
I want
Learn
To dance again
I can see learn to dance
Present in
It's raining again
You can see that learn to dance story that idea of one
And username is stored as
If you're able to add it to do but you don't see the to do in the sentence
Go to
Database and check the record which I presented here
Then make sure that in the back end
You are actually setting the username
Properly
So this to do that username username is an important piece of code
What is sequence of last few steps
It connected the entire application
Do a GTA back and you saw how easy it was
Music combination of spring data jpa and hibernate
And we saw that it was very very simple to connect the entire thing together
I'm sure you had a lot of fun doing all this
I'll see you in the next step