Welcome back
We implemented the logging component with a username and a password and login
But you're not really Implement a lot of functionality in there
Is it
Let's focus on making this login page a little bit more
Functional
I'm like no label printer value Cindy
Username and password and let's say I would want it give a default value
The username search I would say input name
This value is equal to
All small 28 minutes as the user ID
For a major part in this course
Could be all small
In 28 minutes
And
Save this
Enough ingredients
I'm not really able to edit
And if I do psychic
Inspect
It says
You blowing it up value proper form field
This will render a read-only field
Beautiful beautiful
Use default value
Let's take a step back and think a little bit more about this
Reddit change the value of a password in here
Password
Where is this value being stored
Value is being stored as part of the HTML form
All the formed elements typically maintain their own state
This password element or any other element we add to a form maintains its own state
And it is updated directly based on user input other chain something in here
The state of this specific thing gets updated
When it comes to react
People want to hold estate
Inside the specific components to example of username and pass
Hi state
Inside the login component
Two possibilities which are present in here
Deep form
Is the source of Truth
Deposit value
Used estate of the components
As a source of cloth
And have a single
Source of Truth is it difficult to understand all this year
That's good
Pants on right now
What did he wants to do is to have a state inside the login component
For these two things
I have a phone so I'll have the cash money state in the login component Teresa constructed
I'm going to be doing this Constructor and over here we called super
The best practice is also to accept drops
Props to the superclass this will ensure that any properties
I passed on to the superclass Constructor
Coming to the state how do we set up the seat this. State
Is equal to
What release date
Username
:
I don't have
The initial value as in 28 minutes
Password
What I'm doing is creating initial state in here
How can I tie this date
Who dis
Formal event
You back inside estate to deform element
Sky saying value
Not as in 28 minutes
But see
This
State
.
Username
This is a JavaScript variable to win it put it within {
Let's see what would happen
In 28 minutes I'm still a
So what does that mean now
What is present in this state
Is being picked up in soon as devalue
So what is the source of truth right now it's this state
Wendy's value changes what do we need to do
We need to update this state how do we do that
Before we do that let's actually add the value
Today
Desert State.
What do you want to do
Is
When are values of username changes you going to update the state
How to do that
This.
Hand
Username
I want to create a method call handle username
Change
He said his Handler would want it to be handled
Henry username change let's go into your dad and username change
One of the things is
This and username change get something called event
As in Portal
If you're talking to himself
Any action that you perform in the button when you click on it with genetically different
Reactants actually this is something called a synthetic event
We look at what in it
Very soon translate controller clock
Event
This event so
This.
Is equal to this.
Duck Vine
So not even taste bound let's see what would happen on the phone
But you'd still see the error on deposit that fine
Pink excited later
I want to do to see it even though I'm trying to update the value here I would see that events have been generated the synthetic event is
LOL you would see that the value of the username is not getting updated why is it not getting updated
Dating yet
So
Consulate login into Target. Value gives the value which is being changed
So if I
Tried to change light know you can see
What do I value on tithing in that value comes up in here
What do you need to do is actually use that and set this date
How do we update the state
This.
Said state
End
50 Cent State we need to pass a
Subject
Object containing
The new value
Username username
Good lunch set it to
Event
Target.
This can be written in the shower
Get confused with the syntax actually school is very similar to
The formatted version that we saw a little earlier
The biggest at set username
Bradley changes estate
Let's see what would happen though
Oops you can see
You can see that we are able got Daddy username
No username field is a controlled
Field
What is a control field a control component at the larger picture
He's
Something in which
The Interchange in the UI is dictated by the state
When was time change happen status updated
I know state is updated
Did you was updated back
To this specific thing is called a control component
DeSoto fruit is
The state inside react component
The same changes on the password field as well
You can pause the video in here and tried as an exercise
Squid
Tuan change is equal to this. Handle
Crossword
Change
Handle
Password change
Left behind it as well
Etsy
It's only printing d
Admit because I'm sending it in username Exodus it's 32 password
I need to update the state of
Password
We have not seen yet implemented in login
One of the things that we did right now it's whenever you are they just username or password
It's getting updated into this date to this complete company that we have login component control company
Because everything is now
Dictated by the state which is inside the login component
When will you make a change into your status updated
The changes reflected back in the element
Who made the login component of control components
We added a event to handle that and we are now able to update the state whenever
Comedy types in something
And we also tied back
Value of the
Element
To this date as well
I see you the next time. We talked about a lot more things