Waikem you focusing on cloud
Let's start creating this to do component
Google amphitheatre through component
Display list of tools in there is creating
List
2 deuce
Components
It was component extends component
And let's
Just start with the basic stir fry to let's just say
List
How do I find the url to this
I don't need to go to the router
And after the welcome component I'll put this in and this is
List
2 deuce
Component URL
Do this when you go to fast to lose UTD
List reduce component
This is work 3000 / 2
I'm able to CD
Destroy this company. What do you want to be able to do this company
Is the show the true information
Start with diesel hardkor de to information so we put some to do in to the state and you
Use that information to display the to do
What I lose
I shoot your controller of props
Stocktwits super of crops that kind of basic thing that we do always
Then you can have this
Desert State
Is equal to
Started creating a simple to do object
When creating ID
Is Letty one
Description
How to say
So this is a simple object that including in here and putting it into state
I can do that
Create
Beautifully to do right so I can tell this to this
H1
Litters
End
It's formatted better so that we can actually
Romantic dinner by Toby
Hooks
Okay cool
And we have the hatch one
And I don't want to put the to do content right so you the truck until let's if you want to put it in a table
Let's say I'll start with a simple table
And inside this that you would have a t i r e d
It does and I'll have
I d
Inside the ass
He said you have DH
Sdh
Lakeside SSID
And that have a discontented we basically have the cable right now
And let's quickly create
Body Integrity body
You have a TIA
DH ID description and in the TV
What do we need to include is the values of the two Deuce how can I get the address of the Toulouse
Dad and estate letter
.
I d
Yes. State. To do.
What do we have
He said it's description
So that's about what happened with that page oops
I cannot just got to let you in
Yeah I didn't react
Deus Ex
Which one is element so it's all small
Start a custom component Lexi
Lisa Boothe
That's cool so we have the basic
You don't really want to do this one's actually want to do it
For a list of Clues
How can you do that
It's add a list of Toulouse right now instead of having one to do
What do you need to do is have a aerial Studios so how do we do that
Santa Cruz
End
Let's
Create
A list
I think you have
Loser List
You can have multiple photos
Let's say your tools are learn to dance
Become an expert
At 3 Act
And
Visit my home country visit India
Looks that you get this right with it
India
Has to have different IDs want to
What I would want to be able to do is to loop around the values and display them in here
How can I do that
What I'll do is I'll copy this
And go to the browser console
Shut
It's nobody about it's like no because
Distance deductible does not exist right we change it to produce
That's not a problem
Go to the console
And we didn't cancel I create a simple variable called
List
How to say
Baton Rouge
Creating this list of Toulouse in here.
JavaScript you can do a flat feet around this
And you can Define what to do with each to do
Took what I would want to do this
How to do that before you can do that is by defining a arrow function in here so I'm saying
Take each element or actually
And
What you need to do is cancel.
To do. Description
Text
Wisdot foreach
East caps
I'm defining this
Functions of the saddle function to do
This painting the description of all these three
What do you need to do in react whenever you'd want to look at on the list and display them is something say
Similar to this
What we'll do is use something called a math function
City map
Each of these truths to something else so I can say map
Blues.
Map
The foot eats to do
Map to something else
Second
Description of the to do
So what would happen
Is this spring
A tree with descriptions
What would happen
So what we're doing is taking each of the initial element and mapping it to something else
You can map it to something like this a combination of
So what do we do now is something similar to what you're doing here freedom and function
Piece of code Str should repeat
But every to do
To what it was cool. We have in here actually
What do you need to do this we would need to actually repeat this
For all the to do so first thing I can put in {around
This piece of thing in to indicate that this should repeat
What we'll do is we'll do the map
So what do you need to do this
Tattoo Lou's
Dart map take each to do so what we need to do is
Each of the two deuce
To each to do
And what should be done for each of these two days
Is this
What you need to do is not this Thursday to do variable is declared in here
Can I charge my switch needs to be picked up
And return the specific element
What happens if
Until June read this code
For each of the two Deuce which is present in here so you can actually tablet
Out even further to make it better
Smokey Row
If you want to happen now
You can see that delivers to this company this place Boise ID
And the description
Table saw you have the IDS and the descriptions shown in the table to actually do it today
Map
Define an arrow function
Data function represents how
Each of these elements should be shown
Want to do
And this is done for all the Tudors
Beat the first boss
Attitude has component
There's still work left to be done in subsequent steps