Welcome back
Enter device user ID and password and click login button what do you want to happen dude want to go to the welcome
What we're doing is just a message right now
Welcome component
And studied you need to attraction navigating Foods
If it started with the welcome component
Reading reading comprehension
Plus
Welcome component
Extends component
And Implement d
Define demented
Glenda
Auntie
Welcome
In 28 minutes from now
Enough
With this company in DePere
I can do this
In 28 minutes
The Logging company and welcome company both of them are being shown with what we would need to do this we don't really want the showboat
Both of them you don't only show one of them
Based on
The current situation
How can we do that
That's weird
Green book called react router comes into picture
React router access to route from one component
Another component
You can Define
When I type in a URL localhost 3000 / login I want to show the login complaint
When I type in the URL localhost 3000 / welcome I want to show
The welcome component and also it allows us to
The attic from
And user ID successful
I would want to show the welcome component
Gambit
All the features to build a real web application and that's where it comes in
The features to route from one page to another
I have the application I've been running from the browser
React
Router
So that's the name of the library's react router
We are going to use it to the browser sites react-router-dom
You want to add that specific thing in
If you go to the
Project
End
We look at the package. Jason
Tootsie that right now there are only three dependencies for this specific project
And no
As soon as I
Infamous prank download
That's something p.m. deposit
To download the reactor dumb and all its
Including react router
Tootsie that all of them would be downloaded into the normal and at the end of it you'll also see that it is added into
Baxter Jason the dependency
You can see that it's not dumb
We're going to go see 4.3.1 version of it
You can see that it's added in
Despacito version of react-router-dom
Now that we have is he act out there dumb in our age we can start using it in our application
Before we can actually use it will need to import a few classes
Tell him you need to import
A few things
From
React
Outer
What I think that would want input
That's about
Why do we need this
Rename browser router 1/2 cordless router be used
To icing put browser on Android
React
Hunterdon fits me
This full screen so that we can see the complete thing he's in
Inside
Certain situations you want to login company in certain situations you don't show the Belkin component to O'Hare
Router
I want to use this router
Define route
If the spot
Something
Then the component to use
He's something
If the part is something else
The component to use is something else as well for now
Sweetamine this
Jessica mint suits
Tricky Tricky lyrics
Oh here
ITunes login comment that the first one
Welcome component at the second one
But this will get the URL / login for this
BTD
/
Welcome
Achieve this notifying any browser
The reason is because we stopped at bearded dependency and restart the application
Start again to pick it up again
Okay starting it up again
Expect to see in Paris
Okay
One of them inside the router you can only have one child element just like in jsx what year we have
Route to what I'll do is I'll include it with in a fragment
Call that I need to do with empty note handed in Hindi F&L
Push this out a little down
Let's see what would happen
Cool
Ss3000 doesn't show anything
See what happens when I say login
Chelsea login page
What happens when I sodi
/ welcome
It shows the welcome page
What happens when I say / welcome
Let's see what would happen if I say / welcome /
Something else
It can use to show the welcome page
So any route starting with / login
Which OD logging companies near out starting with / welcome
Chody welcome components
Let's noad
Decide that
Even the default / doubt I would want it to go to the Logging Company in Tazewell
What's happening in here
Because / welcome / SSD
Jefferson
It matches this out
And it might just decide out exactly showing both
So we can prevent login complaint to be shown
By saying exactly when it says exact
Then do that turn off only welcome competition when I say 3000 login competition
Logging companies
In what way did is he created the Banking Company quickly
And we all typically added in this routing stuff so you're not able to
Type in the URL in the browser
And go to a specific thing
Go to welcome a few
Get in there that we need to work on like security look and feel and stuff like that but those are things which could work in the next step