Everything we talked about sessionstorage and you might be wondering why did we not use the local storage
Important things about local storage
Is that once you said about you into it
Once you say I can't do it will not be deleted until you explicitly delete it so you leave the user close a zebra
That wasn't comes back the key would still remain there
It's not really considered secure and that's the reason why we use station storage
We just cleared as soon as you close the browser and go out
Navigate to the problem at hand
Act login we added
Is that sufficient
We also need to remove it at sometime when you removed out we need to do it at logout
Start within the specific step
When is lockout what do you want to do if we want to remove all this
Conditioned storage
Let's go to the head of company and what I'll do is
When somebody clicks on logout button so
One click
Off the logout button what I would want to do is I would want to call a specific
What is the method that I would want to call let's define a tightness authentication Service login
The next method is log out
And what do you want to do on logout
What you want to do in Lockhart is session storage
Remove items just want to remove this item
Indicated
User
Do that
And what we can do now
Authentication Service
Authentication
Service.
Log out
That what we're doing in here it's weird mapping
The Gauntlet event
Could this
Method call
So I know you're somebody clicks log out what happens
Devalue from the session storage
Remote
What are the important things is you should not do this
Cinematic all what we're doing is
Mapping a event
Dedication service. Logout
Accessible defiance
Let's keep looking
Conceited
Because that's what
Happened when we did the login
No
You can see that the authenticated user is removed out from the session
That's cool right
When user logs in you put something in today
Kitchen storage in Windsor Locks out during without that's pretty cool
But you're not really using any of this stuff in the application yet
An excuse that it's not doing it I'll see you in the next