Welcome
Back to previous few steps to progress with the application
We actually added in a lot of cool features when a user logs in we are doing the fact that he has logged in
Sessionstorage
And then use a lock self-storage NBA using that
To authenticate
Access
Could the user if I think I should be logged in if I log out and do it
That's not
Hello
In addition to that
In one of the previous steps we also customize the menu
He made sure that
Based on whether user has login or not we are showing the flight details
Cleveland
Useful react features we talked about routing first
Then we talked about how to create an authenticated route
And also be
Talk about how to disable and enable links
Panda menu
We learn how to put a token
I hope you use it
Crosby
There are still a few defense to this specific application
Most of the data in the application is hard-coded
And that's what
Bewitching
The next section
We would start building our API. Building are back-end services
So that are
Ruth page the authentication services and everything
Can start talking to real apis
I'm excited with the direction that we are heading
I'm sure you're learning a lot
And I see you
In the next step