Welcome
InStep I'll show you a tip
About how you can simplify this kind of component creation forcing tulips
And we have to create a functional component to show this
Let's go to the JavaScript console and typing
True
Two and a test string
What would happen if you can see that it is Whitney best ringback
Lexi
False
End
Estwing cancel off
Your browser you can get that invited me and I think inspecting going to be canceled and I'm trying some JavaScript in here
What is Vietnamese Falls it's not actually listening guitar string bag
Alcatel simple variable length
Show something
Is equal to
So if I say
Show something
Ancestry
What would it be
Because something is true
Equity 10 testing back
I changed about your shoes and some chili
Let's execute the same thing
Try something interesting
This evening Falls
Realizing in here is
And operator
Big left hand side is a Boolean operators
This value Aziz
If the condition is true if something is Fleetwood attended swing as is false
And that's a great opportunity with
Jsx intervene show invalid credentials is equal to this end.
All that stuff we can do is we can insert a chart expression NC
This. State.
Has login failed
And
You can put in whatever you would want to return back
You can say
This expression 2x is like an expression
To everything Majestics compile to JavaScript code and it's like a JavaScript expression so you can save this
Login failed invalid credentials and now I can come in this cold out
I'm going to do a G6 command so start /
Cool and let's see if this works as it is
Login invalid credentials
Invalid credentials If I Do dummy
Isn't that cool
Violet Lux complex right one of the reasons why we are introducing this in a separate step on its own
Because this is little tricky to understand right so this old looks very very complex but what
What it does is very simple if this condition is true
Then show this as simple as that to let's do the same thing
No
Des access messages. Show success message
Let's commit this stuff out
Class.
Stop /
Calabasas
And
It's not an invalid credentials but HD
Successful
Looking successful
Enough
Amanda stuff out
Enough eutsey
Logan successful
Login
Invalid credentials
So what we're doing is not be exemplified all the logic for validation inside
Accord
Instant
VA loans are important thing if you wanted to show specific Devon a specific condition then you can
Chili use
This end operator
Alekman you to play around with The Interpreter a lot more