Welcome
Back
What are the things that you would have answered in the previous step
Please
We have to change events
But handing the changes in the two elements which are present in here what is the form has 10 elements 15
You can keep writing events like this
So what mg do in that kind of scenarios
That's what you'd be looking at in this specific step
I need username change event
It is better printing event or Target. Value
Let's see what would happen if I say even though Target. Name
Let's
Try and
Change the volume so you can see that it's finding username which is the
Name of the field which is changing
So what I can do is actually in stuff hard-coding username in here
What I can do
Is instruct username I can say
This specific thing so let's apartment this so that this
Looks a little more
Readable object
With username as a specific value
Inserting it into this
This value is actually event. Target.
Flight directly help us to make it genrikh
Does this look
When are weekly tall object of what we're doing here
The left hand side is the name
Off
The object member variable
That is typically expected to be a constant value cannot put a variable in there
If I want to use a variable in there what I would need to do is put it with him
[
Let's see what would happen
Now you can see that this date is being updated and it is being reflected back in here
That's cool so what we can do now is instead of actually
Calling this handled username
Change event
Cordless hand
Change
2 for any change of event
What do you want to do
Call Liz
Today is it can work both with username and the password field because here we are not hard coding
The name of the element in this state which is changing
One of the important things now is what do we have in the state should match with whatever we have in the formula
Names to the name of this element is
Username
Bowie State
Also we should use username same password as well
This Korean gendrich
How to change will only work when I have
This evening's performance as well as inside the state
Let's go ahead and
Do this
So now I can actually comment out
Can come on
Handle username change as well
End
I can remove the binding for this
And add The Binding foot
Distort
Handle change
Got any change.
Bind
Formal events and still have just one method for the
Kind of change
Having a tie in back
Change this
And change
Change
It's about what happened now
So what I'm typing in is going into the state
Showing down here
If you want to see what's in the state actually
Just before
The thing
You can say
This. Stitzer distance to State before
The Handler change event
You can see the state
Is getting updated Aspen
Askme keeps typing in stuff
Do Bettas how to create a jendryk event to handle
Deep changes
We created a jinchuuriki event
It can handle all
Changes
Put any text element