Welcome
Be hard coded in 28 minutes
How can you pass
The fact that in 2018 it has logged in
From
Login component
Welcome company
How can we do that
One of the options I could look at right now
He's bypassing 8s
A parameter
A spite of your url
Add
The name of who has logged in
Devout
So what I've done now
Flash
Colon name
What do you need to do
When we are going to the welcome page where are we going to do this is why we can't even complete
You don't also add in
Username
So how do we do that
Dollar
Unimportant things I can't use double quotes I should use sticks
Are you sticks
Evaluating variable
Peabody Place
Even keel
Circus in Texas inside pics
You need to use Dollar open race
Lowe's play sand
Available
So what will happen now is the user would be directed to / welcome
The welcome does not work anymore because it's welcome /
Something
Tulips
Go to
Login
Impertinent
Dummy
NC login
And you can see in 2018
Where is hard-coded Led
Value which is coming as part of the oranges in here
How do you change it to use the parameter value of the crops to what we can do
This
Trop's
.
There's something called match
Inside that it is something called
And the name of the parameter that we have configured is names this name
Should match with whatever we have configured
So let's see what happens
Change this to something else
Can see that whatever we typing here is what
Dibella, text will start printing
Look at one device you can pass values from one company to another company
I just by using d
Parameter
I see you in the next step