Welcome back
Refers to companies Woodstock with the login component and evil component
Is to create a login form with the name and the password
And to be able to have the user click login and show detail compatibility
Adjectives for the initial few steps
Let's start focusing on the login component
I go to the. ID Studio code and what we do is real reusable
Project that we created earlier so for now
What we'll do is we'll actually create a new folder inside components cycle this
To Aldi
Through management application components will be storing in the components to do folder
Let's go to the apple juice and
Let's start with creating
So I'll actually coming this out how do I come in this out
Okay this is jsx right to you need to use the complex way of commenting so I need to put it in typical
Multi-line comment and
Enclose make this a JavaScript
Quotes about
This is what you need to do so open place
If I go to the browser you don't really see anything right now
What you want to do if you'd want to start creating a to-do app
In here so I create a component
Call true app
Galactus Nadia trays
So it might saddle out to let's go to the to do and say
U5
To-do app
.
Jsx
Let's start with the import to import react
And component
From
React
Once we do that
We can actually create a to-do app
Plastic wrap extensions
Component
And let's create desire and a method to
We want to return something back
What do you want written for now let's just returned a simple dip
Class name
Is equal to
Tutuapp
Inside this I just see my
Sauvie accident component
Would it work as a tease pink
Cavities
Export
Default
A true app can be used in here
Brickwork
Imported
Al-Quran imported to import
Clue app
From
Brooks from
North / components
Spanish
Counter / accountant
/through app
Easy
Showing on the browser
Let's go to the true lab projects in this component is weekly.
All the companies related to do do app usually
In the single file
One sweet thing that's that list will move them to their own files
Logging companies
So let's talk with the login page to login component
Class login component extends
Component
And
It's traded and emitted quickly
What do you want in the login
Beach dude want a couple of buttons
Actually a couple of form elements couple of text boxes name and password
And he want a login button right so let's create them right now so can I say input
Type is equal to text
And 10 mm is equal to
Username
This is d
And after that
Enter deep
Input
Type is equal to text
Name is equal to passport text
Text to be password
So this is actually typical
HTML nothing special about it via trading in here are
The basic elements
Tobias Elementary
And
What we want to do after that
Is rude want to
Have a button to button
Hendrix College
Look
Enough
He's a Xbox One username or password
Field and a login button will this work
You think this would work is no because we need to actually put it
Nina jsx you cannot retain multiple element back you have to actually put them in a dip
Actually I could have used the ACT fragments is called react fragment in between Mt
You can do that on
As we do usually
Reproductive Medicine
If I go
To my
Good application still shows my application why
Because I'm not login component
This comes up
Cool so username password and login.
Awesome things that you can seize the login button is not getting any bigger font because of this
Theaters that we have defined elsewhere
Little worried about it right now
Turn off
You be able to enter values in here
And click login and will be able to use this login component
Component video setup for the tutuapp we created a model for tutuapp we are now having
Holly code and decompensated to do happen this specific model
Retreated login component
And we are enough
Allstate
Go ahead and implement the login page
A little more