Let's get today
Fun stuff to do with enable and disable menu items weather
Whether a user has logged in or not
Let's try and customize menu
I need to look for the helicopter and India component what do you want to do is we would want
Checking for you last login or not if you have not been then we would want the enable of fuelings
How do I disable
Which is present in here let's create a method
It's called This is
User
Log
What does it mean to check
But we can do this first when you get the
User
We can get it
Value from decision services
Dip station storage
.
Get
Item
Authenticated user
Probably thinks I can see here is we are using this
A number of times
Play David Bowie this to accountant 5
You was at
Is equal to
Sessionstorage. Get item
Authenticated user we're getting the user from the session storage
User is equal to equal to none
What should we do
How do I
Peyton
Checking if you're getting from the second storage is not
If it's not
Then the other is not logged in
Is logged into turn to
What are you doing here as I called at Nestle
As a constant because it's a constant right
He's a user
And what I'll do is under control. Log off
It's supposed to make sure that we are getting the right value in here
Look at the console electric one of the links which is present in here
I'm getting an error saying invalid on property class with Fixodent
You can see how you taste
False
It's login
And
Tea ingredients dummy
Enough
Buffalo down and see
You can see that
Is sprinting to
What is happening is
Want to login
Dispatch news being printed as
David need to use that value
Which is present in Hindi
Log out
We need to use this value is user logged in
Enable or disable links how can we do that we need to show this link
Only when
User is logged in
We already talked about the end of hereditary
This is shown
Only if
Can use the same thing
So what I do is actually
Open dress
Close the whole thing out
I'm here
I would actually used
Is user logged in
And and
What happened this link will be shown only if user has
Log encyclopedias
And I didn't see me to do sleep do you want to show it to the sink only if the user is logged into Allegan high like dealing
Empress
Open brace
And then copy this in
Let's
Do the same thing on the logout Button as well
May I bring Oven videos please
Is user logged in
Login button when should we show driving button should be shown
When will it is not loading not you love me
Let's
You see that now the login button is not shown because
Why did not shown
But if you go to the application tab
We have this token indie
Sessionstorage
Facebook logout you can see
That's only the login button is now being shown
I can see that it's cleared out from sessionstorage and we only have the login button Sean Isn't that cool
Why do things that irritates me
Is the fact that they have
Search for
Class is equal to
And replace it with
Classmate
I could have done to replace all but I just wanted to be clear about
What all places will using it
That's enough
Let's go
In today
Browser
Kayla cancel
28 minutes
Dummy
Login
Okay cool we have
Home to do
We have no doubt
We have stuff
Coming out of
It here
There's another one in between SC eat
Child in the list should have a unique key property
Take the link you see that it says
Every child in a specific list win this week
List of items everything should have a unique key
How do we
Do that
Dich Vu can a turkey is just by saying
He is equal to
We can use the idea of the to do acid
Something unique for the ACT
Keep track of the steer and if something changes
It would use the specific key ass
The starting point
If I
Okay fresh
Ipsy
Zach Davison weather
Now being highlighted
That's cool
I just made the description ass
Go to home
Kitsilano goat login
Again
Transparent with it and see if you see any warnings
Which at present
Lisa Portillo focusing on was to enable and disable menu items
They've done with login
We also fixed a few other minor works
I'll see you in the next day