Welcome
In the previous step
We disabled the menu links based on whether user has logged in or not but
That cheating users who do this
They were typing the URL and get to that
Even though you wasn't has not really love being able to get to the URL
How do you prevent it if you need to
Do some magic
We need to authenticate before we need to route
That's basically what you do in this life except
People using this route right over here
We actually use it out and we say this is the part this is the component is recombinant allowed to
What are you doing to be able to do is
Authenticated route
How many failstacks do welcome page Rd to do stage what you want to do is make sure that his login and only then
I love user to go to this route
Undo the changes
Youtube.com
Authenticated
Is out
Js
So this would be a component so very simple
Authenticated
Trout
Extends
Component
Need to return something back from dead
You need to import
Component
Module what do you want to do in Toronto
If user is logged in
Then you would want
Theory that came to this device
Country that came to the login page
We just created the authentication Service right lips
Music
Authentication Service
User
Sevis at user login
Then what do you want to do if you don't want to redirect
To draw out what you want to do is
What was
Let me change this to authenticated route what would happen is all the parameters would be passed to authenticate
What do you want to do if you'd want to take all this drops and also pass them
2D
Route how do we do that
The baby can do that is by using something called
This.
What we're doing in here called a spread operator what is the speedometer It's Quickly take a look
Simple
Erickson
I'm clean and simple
Glad you said a 1-2-3 there's a simple function called some
Some
88153 parametres a,
B, c and it's actually
Returning A + B + C which is the sum of
Quality
Twosome
All this stuff up right
Not if I call some with Lexi
195 back cool
Exactly as expected
I want YouTube views from this
Eddie and call Lisa
How can I do that
You can do that is by seeing some of
Values
I actually started zero right in extension zero values of
,
Values of
You should have ducked
Dallas group provided something called a spread operator what you can do if you can say some
Off...
Values
What happens
Is all the elements in this array
Would be positive integer parameter so what happens is 1 lb man to have to be
Spread operator what do you want to do this if you do have is fasting
To be authenticated.
Different parameters
Route
They took individual defining those properties what I'm doing is taking out
The easier route
Samsung
Take all the properties and spread them out what we need to do
We need to redirect the user
A simple as that
Let's make sure that we have All Imports
Right so let's import cloud
And redirect
Where did this come from
Come to the XL teardown
Let's also import
Authentication
Service
From
. /
Authentication Service
.
Let's save this
Now let's
Go to the
To-do app
Which all routes do we want to be authenticated
Take somebody's coming to the place we wanted to be authenticated if somebody's coming today
Listables component
But actually did to his computer link to swing dude wanted to be authenticated
If you have logged in you'll be able to love
Odessa
I'm making these roots as authenticated
Import
18 Nashville import authenticated service
From
. / authenticated
Slimport authenticated route
Starts at Southland get it out
Important things
His over here we are not really doing the default
Export default
Authenticated
Let's do that quickly
Sadist
Component is available in this specific
Let's go to the browser
Mitsuken
Automated outage Essex
How can I not return this back
What should I do
I should actually
Beauty
That I'm able to
Citi login button
So basically
Dearest not get plugged in and if I go to Toulouse
Is redirected down to the login page going to welcome and say welcome
In 28 minutes
Going back to the login page
If I enter devalues
Anoka County homepage are to be able to go there
But if I say I'll go
And then try to go to Toulouse
It does not really love me to do that
Isn't that cool
We have an almost perfect system have a good adult education
We have hardcore to do that stuff that's what they would fix over the next few steps but
We have a good system only one user is logged in he'll be able to see the details if he does not know.
Crossword never be able to go in and check any of the details
I see you in the next step