Welcome back
In the previous step
We created logo component NBA updated the photo component to have Delight styling
Let's focus on each of the individual components and style them better who started login component
We didn't go today
Welcome and then we would go to the list of those
Let's add a hedge fund
Login
And then food additive around
This
And let's give it a class of containers
Container
And
Best put that on all this stuff
Let's for my disability
The dog in Texas full message we're not going to show it anyway so you can actually remove this out
Greek last name
Is equal to
Invalid credentials
Is it morning
How to use alert
I live username and password as they are
A little Dudes Only button I'll have
A few more classified ending
Last name
Is equal to
It's
A button
Now you can see that the login page is much better
Slimes
Piketon gonna win today welcome page
Tonight let's go to the welcome page and 4matic
Now I'm falling the welcome company
What I'll do is I'll just press enter
Start afresh
Could we start with an empty fragment
Will add a hitch one
Text emojis Dave South Dakota
Are you the devil
Interest creating a new one here but that's okay we have the Vatican component done let's see how it looks okay cool
Tonneau
You go to the login in 28 minutes.
FanDuel login
To get the devel compared to go to the login
Denali password invalid credentials
So that's cool that you guys looking
Pretty decent right now
The next day that we need to focus on is the list to those type
Go to the list of those page
Is Rarity's
Could we have
Diwali
Pleasant
End up going to have a hedge fund here so what I'll do is I'll actually adding another day
Around the table or on the table I'll add another day
And
Algebra class of container
Classic sequel to container so that we get some space around it
And lips
Push this table
A little
And then
Windows will be gifted class of table
We have a little loose and we have the table displayed in here
You can see that the table is much much much better looking right now
What alarms do dissolvable bidc because he does not really make sense on a to-do. Who cares what
What to do is
Disabilities looks like now home
Truce
And
Login page
The step brings us to the end of all the styling that people doing for the last few steps
What is the starting next step is focusing on
Functional features
What are the things that you don't want to listen inspected when I login
I go down to the welcome page
You really need to login to go to the welcome page you can type a URL and directly go to the welcome page
You can eat to lose and go to the to do space without being the login
How can you prevent that that's basically what
I would start looking it in the next few steps