Welcome
We focused on the counter example
We use the counter
Example to understand
Basic components day6 State and props
Vegetable management application
Keep focusing on the components back
Along with
Adding in new features
Will add routing to the application how do you navigate from one page to another page
When you start, login page
And you pick up a new would want to go to the welcome page how do you do that
How do you implement forms
Invalidation with react
How do you call rest API
What do you want to look at
Authentication how do you implement authentication in the backing
How do you actually
Studio. Indication tokens in different thing
And use them when you make you a rest API call
I'm excited to bring the section to you where you start with the basics
I'll get through management applique
I see you in the next to you