We implemented this to display time and it doesn't really look good right now
Basic stuff
Also what we have right now functional is in 28 minutes
Dummy I go to login page
I should welcome page
And
Navigate to little space how can we do that
We can add a link in here
Activelink what we also want to do is to add
A few more attributes to the to this page we have ID and description for the to do right now
Let's add the targeted and is it completed fees
Regal those two things the specific step
Just get started with adding a link
We need to go to the welcome component and add the link in the title
Go to the welcome company this is the richest President in there
And over here
You can say
Toucan
Manage
Sure
2 deuce
What do you want to do if you want to change this to a link
How can we add a link around it
Link around it
I need to use something cool link
Which also is defined in react-router-dom
What happens if you actually Define a here
Stride Rite
Before link let's try defining an AT&T
I want the loud
And let's head
Basically the usual HTML way of doing it
Peanut close at 12
Let's Duet
Lucy
I want to go to the welcome page
I know yet if I keep this link
You see that the interface get stretched so
You can see that the incomplete page get safest however you see that when I go to
BofA login
And
The interface is not refresh specific part of the page is refreshed
Let me see this once we add the menu and the filter later
The most important thing to
Not when
You actually and unnormal
Pizza Hut
What happens if the entire page gets refreshed
And when you're doing single-page applications you don't want the entire page to get refreshed and that's with link
Comes into you can add a link
Only that specific component will be replaced with whatever is pointed to buy this this week
Component
2 / to lose
Import
The LinkedIn
Link is also defined
In tdiclub.com package select input that from there
And if you go
Michael page and you click here you can see the list to those page
Tighten up
What do we have done
To add the link is working
Right now
You might not be able to clearly see the difference that the link is making
Can we add header when we add the
Menu in University this much more clearly
Let's focus on adding in more attributes to our we have ID and description
Lip tattoo with a tribute
Done
And
Tyga dick
Good Deed
Basic stuff ready done false
And the target date I would want to add for all of these
Turn up
LC
You
Copy this into all the other stuff
Now we have de Toulouse ready
The new attributes
Use them in the displacement
Can I use them.
Done
Target
Does this work
You can see and I love you too. Except one correctly that'll be a child
What to do for now we just do a two string for both of them posting
Both of these.
What if I got to do is to a dinner theater oldies
Lcec
Gal Gadot
And I'll add another one
Sandy's completed
Completed
We'll work out a better way to 2% DEET a good day
This looks a little clumsy for now but that's okay
Right now we have the complete flow
Designed to rehab
From the login page in 28 minutes dummy
Login
You can go to D2 dispensary have the complete clothes design
So what do you do in the subsequent steps is focus on
Did you do the looking for William and you will add a footer we make this the body of the cage
And will do all that kind of fun stuff
In the next few steps with shift our attention to making our page look better
I see you in the next day