Kratom
Back
In all the previous States we did not really authenticate the user
But he has logged in or not
Before we
Actually take the user to a specific length
Even though our user has not really logged in
How do you track if a user has logged in or not
What are the often features available
Track with a user has logged in or not
Is something called a station
If you look at all the browsers
They have something called sessionstorage
And
What do I put in session storage
Available for the application
Why user is logged in into the current
And
Go down
Do the application tab
I'm using Chrome obviously
You can check out the storage section very few expanders
You can see
This basic application does not really have anything in session storage
What we can do is
When are you guys at the logs in we can set a key into session storage
And when a user logs out we can remove it
Keep out
And we can use that to check if a user has logged in or not the great thing is if you close your browser
Pictures of storage is completely cleared out
Love note
What do you do in the step is me try and put something into session storage
When are user logs in
7 lakhs in successfully dummy and clicks login
What do you want to do
If you would want to put
Anthony's Ocean storage
Dulzura is logged in
In the next it will make use of
This Pacific
Key token
Whatever you want to call it
And music to check
Before we landed all the other pages
Let's get started
Login click method this is a method which is called when logging is clicked on the tutuapp
AT&T login page
Did you already pass Willis
Find this hot code for Naf
If it is find what you want to do as we would want to put
Something in session storage
What we do is all the interaction with sessionstorage
We would do it to a new module
So what are you doing
Create a new file
How do you call this
Authentication
Sally's
This would be a JavaScript
I created
Authentication
Service
Class
And what are we doing cuz I create an instance of it export
Default
I create an instance of it and exported
So what happens is not of this gas
Is available
To-do app so if I want to make use of this authentication Service what should I do in the clue app
Student portal
Authentication Service
From
Dog / authentication Service
It's create a simple method in here
Hypothesis method
What do you want to do in here if you would want to register the fact that a user has really logged in
Cricket method for that
And I call this
Login
Hand
I'll have two parameters to this
When is the username and the other one is password
Once
Are you successfully logged in what do you want to do
If you would have want to be able to put a value in D
Storage
How do we do that sin 2 the second story so
If you look at
The white something called sessionstorage
If you go Section storage.
Set item
User
Authenticated user
Username let's not use the password for Nabi password
Not really worried about it for now
Don't know what you have done this week created a simple method
Authentication Service
I can be created a class and we created metal in It restaurant
Syndication service
Howdy-do app Beyond imported the authentication Service in steps
So what we can do in the Logging Company
When login is clicked
What we can do if we can say authentication Service
Authentication Service
Latricia
Successful login
Make sure that
Specific method is called what I'll also do is do I cancel. Lock
Vlog
Biggest sxs Footlocker
Is it safe to laugh as well
And let's see
Checking the browser
It says
ACNL it says
I'm unable to import authentication Service. Jsx
The reason is because since the extension of the spider CSX is stinking the authentication Services alter gs65
It's not it's
So let's just say authentication Service. J's
Go back. Call classes function
I forgot the new keyword
So if you want to create a new instance of this
Let's see what happens you can see
That we have
Decatur
Dixie what's happening in Dickinson
You can see that resist a successful login
Doesn't and also you can see that authenticated user
The value is undefined
Why is it undefined
Define because we did not pass the username and password
So let's pause the username and password how do we pass the username and password
Restart State. Username
End
Bishop State.
Telepathy mean
Retry
Talking
Android 8 minutes
Dummy
And login
No you can see that in session storage
We have something called authenticated user in 28 minutes
You see that as long as I am on this application
You would be mean in here it's not really going out
Ciara
What we did is we created the authentication Service
And we used it
To make sure that music likes to login
Antique shops in Texas City
Beset something into the session storage so that we know that our user has successfully logged in
I see you in the next step