Welcome back let's start customizing the header and footer
I want actually a number of links I would want Homelink or to do slink
Maybe a logo down on the left-hand corners and I would want something on the right time Carnival login and logout
Component
It's. Customizing it
So what I'll do is I would start using the HTML5
Element atom
Inside the header do you need to have an irrigation
And I actually remove the header
I want to create a div with a link to in 28 minutes in here
This one would be willing to be in 58 minutes website
An ordered list to represent
The two menu items I would have in the left
AccuWeather
LIC flashlight flashlight
And I want one more honored to represent the
Main elements that
You don't show on the right hand side login and logout
So this is kind of how I see this stuff looking like
Home
So if you want to find more about these classes go ahead to the bootstrap website Thursday boots Airport
Should be able to find a lot more information about each of these classes
Add a class
Call Napa
The Eagles
You can see how
Enough deep holding is separated out
Class name so inch of class actually suggested to use
Class
And put each of the link
Let's add a class
Call
See how this looks like
Had one all these menus
To appear from one beside the other and not in the way they're Pleasant right now
So I'll add another class to this
Not bad
Expand
Turn off everything at the s next to each other
Aldi's
Login and logout Button cell won't come over here
Thailand
-
And Justified
Content
And
Let's see what would happen
You can see that I'm having to take me to him to do to you and login logout at the end
I want to have a dark background sides and not Bardock and background back
Not many would have a dot background
That's cool
The specific thing is the name of the brand teleties
Call navbar
Save this
Lazada has stuff to the website
HTTP://www. In 28 minutes. Com
At school
You can see that the menu appears
Add links on top of each of these. So we have to lose and login logout you'd want to add
Add links on top of each one of those right to it gets
Started with
Adding a link to link to a sequel to something
I'm inside that would be the home stuff writer
Home
Billings to Cody
Flash welcome
Cruise the link would be
Login
Feeling good B
You create one very soon.
Ashley didn't go home should be slashed welcomes Less in 28 minutes
Haven't got good username in here for love
Will fix it a little later
Restart at Aldi formatting God
Lost actually we need it to add the class name on the siletz ad
Last name on the link class for each one of these
GLA
I know it's like a little boring just keep adding a little bit of classes here in there
They just look good
To that's right
Let's spend a little bit of effort to make sure that we have everything working fine to Home2 dues
Home should be login
It's dangerous Logan
Computers login and logout to todoist
If excited little later we have The Hideout working perfectly right now. I'll see you in the next