Welcome
Back
Problems that you would be facing right now is finding the components and making the changes inside the to do
Becoming very very big
It's almost 200 lines of code
What do we do now Krispy Kreme Factory. So what we'll do is we'll actually move
Is the most important component
How to separate files
Tourettes.
With the login component which is one of the most important components which is present in his late start with actual implant the movie
The TSX
Acid the authenticator drought what I would do is I would import all this stuff into
The big sleep
Have these inputs Pleasant
Also
Copy this
Make sure that Bia coffee
The entire login component including design
Enough I'd move it down today
Walking Company
At the end I would expert glass
Login
Component
Let's see if there are things which are not used to this
But it's not used in here so that's cool and what I do is I go to to do after j6 importing
From
.
Belkin components
Escape this
Recorded right first attempt at school
So home to lose everything is working fine
To be able to perfectly fax without the login component very very quickly you can pause the video in here
And try and leave Factor the list to this component into its own component
Cutting tools on Model start doing it right now so I can go to
This
Cut this out this is the
It's coffee the name
Secretariat
Is today's component
And what do you want to do this dude want to move it to its own files inside the to do you fight list
Toulouse
Component
The GSX
I should be named
It's sad that in
Let's add the usual
Imports
And
Let's add a
Export
Default
Let's do this
Integral component
And a to-do app
What do you need to
We need to know
The same thing
Let's do that quickly
Saved
Etsy
It's listed as canoes to work
Clitoris continues to work as it is
Received is actually coming from here it's actually
Make a small change is completed
Is where it's coming from
So you can see that things into individual modules is not too difficult
And actually a little bit of time it would make our application
Very maintainable of doing it one by one
I'll actually start creating another company said the same thing and start moving them
Chocolate hidden component rychlik
New file
Heather
I'll also do a important here yesterday to have a template which I can copy around
All the time
Indeed.com
But this
And also I like today
Export default
Skyrim socket
So what I'll do is I'll copy this
Enough I'll keep changing the name of the component
Futa component
What other stuff do we have to create header footer logout component
Its capital
Ctrl-c ctrl-v
And change
Next thing which we want to use header footer we have welcomed and better component
It's copied again
And I would want to call the stick
Call Fernando jsx
We have
A lot of files with errors it speaks all of them
Very very quickly so let's go back today
Have dirty sex that start with the letter component
Sport
Continental components
Explorer default
Better company
I'll go to the to-do app
And Adam portrait import
Are component from
Not necessary component.
Sex
That's cool
Let's go to the Vatican component
What is the next in here so we have data conference
T-Mobile account as well
Adele component
Header components
Save this
Indy to do app lets go to the store
Alexa import
ADA Compliant from
Opening. Sex
Cool
Helicopter component
It's next
Component video need to go video file here it is
Futa component
And that's important in as well
Import Motor Company
From. / photo component. TSX
The last one remaining
Dusters
Things you many more to log out and the welcome component
It's more Dilaudid company down here and let's to export default
And indeed to do app
Infiltrating
Import
The Clash
Have a company. SX
Glassing witches remaining is the welcome component
Let's
Aphmau
The welcome company and out as well I'm sure there will be a few errors when we actually
STD application in the browser that's fine
It's always good to be
Trying to resolve errors because that help you learn
GSX School
I'm sure that I'd missing Imports
Missing link is not defined in welcome component that's cool
Lingus
So what is it you think I'm component
Innovation component you need link
Upstairs
Rainbow dragonflies I don't need it
Island
Link
I don't need the other stuff in here so let's save it
Not the other component has a few arrows hitting authentication Service link we want to get the Authenticator
Teresa Angelique
Import
And authentication Service
Cool
Comb
Today's
Ingredients
I'm able to go in till
Looks like everything is
Find Weaver weekly Factory Texas Philly
I'm sure it was a very interesting experience with to refactor stuff do their own companies
The great thing from now on is
Whenever you want to make a change you can just search what activity
Fight and make the change and if you could accompany right now it looks much much much more
Smoothies
Semantic code
Which is present ETFs
I kind of leave alarm, decode in because a lot of students like
To have history of what was changed
The reason why I leave complete code mustard attempt but it sometimes it makes it confusing to understand
If you don't really want to have the committee code I would recommend you to remove recording all these components as well
And made the interest