Welcome back
Both of these in the specific step
What time does the sun start with the lockout Continental
Continental Coffee
Log out
Component
And inside the locker component
All that I would want to live to 10
It's a in tentative
To have a hitch one
You are
Pick up
Last name
Equal to
Container this is basically a bootstrap
Glass containers you can see what magic it brings in
Thank you for
Using
I will
Application
I don't really need a different hairstyle live that's an empty fragment that's also fine
We need a map to logout component to this route
Till it's go to the
Route
Add
Knockout
In here
Log out
So we have the Nugget map
That's cool
So you can see that do not use it says you're logged out thank you for using our application
Are Lynx here enough
Walking stick that's good that's enough customized Arabic
You can see that touching four components is becoming more complex as the size of this
Gas gross what will do at a later point is actually speed of the components into an individual
Come into their own individual component files are in visual models
Let's use the HTML5
Fruit arrangements
Will add a class name on it suitable stylet using this a little later
Conductix
Contigo box inside here
10 dad
Specific
Last name given to show something copyright information
Activate read me text
Muted
And over here
I just placed in some taxi does not really matter what that text is this week
And what we want is to configure
A little bit of styling for the footer
Total
I'll add styling in here so. Futa
And add
Starting for that specific folder
If you look at the face right now what do you want to do this we want want to make the food tilapia
Let's make the position of the footer as absolute because you would want it always add the footer
Let's add a bottom
0 to make it
Didn't see the pixels
Let it move it it's a thick solid
With available
Khalil Tate of height
40 pixels
Glitter background color
Insisted
Prostitute
We have a header and footer at the bottom
Home
2 deuce
Calgon
Log out
And a header in the filter
We created the logo company and the photo company
I know what the last few steps to your focus on styling and styling might be a little boring for a lot of people down there
When do one more step of time before we get back into the DL functionality of
We will start looking at how we would add Security on top of an application
And do wonderful stuff along with it I'll see you in the next