Like them and we implemented the navigation from
Login page to the welcome page
Let's do something
Call Erin Hanley
Why do we need a dependent
Let's go to the application
Type in url
Oops
Things shown in here and that's a good right to type something and he does not
What's happening in here
Twin that we need to add in a component
How do I clean a metal component
Very similar to the welcome company
Function
Component
And
Done
Code
I don't
No
What to do
Contact
Support
Cat
ABCD
Bfth
Hi-Tec okay
Have you ever component
But it's not getting rendered why
Define shroud Titus route
Over here we need to spread apart
Because this Friday
Company component
Component is
At our company
When none of these components match leave this empty so you need to say
Cumberland physical component
And you can see
I just don't know what to do contact support that so-and-so
If I do a proper urine
If I go to login page even then I'm seeing their component if I go to the welcome page
What do they see
Emergency
The air component
What's Happening Here
Is that more than one routes are getting matched
If you want to specify that at a point
Only one now one of these roots should match
What we can do if we can introduce us
Switch smash switch
Where does the switch come from
As expected to switch accounts from the XL teardown
So what this which ensures is at any point only one of these
Component is matched so
Health dispensary technician
Turn off Beauty.
When I type in a calculator
It shows something out of URL to something else
Control C login page
That's cool
Except we looked at adding data component and switch to make sure that
Scout is active at any point in time
I'm having a lot of fun I'm sure you have a lot of fun too and I'll see you in the next