Welcome
In the previous step being prevented the basics outing
When you go to login page
And we enter username and password in 28 minutes dummy
And keep login
I'm still showing
Jesse dog in Texas
Let's see how you can do that at
To do welcome page
Is it a very short step activity
So that's what you do that
So what happens when I click the login button let's see what happens
Hogan component
Something clicked this year so
Rent in 20 minutes and tell me what we are saying is cancel. Locks
Don't really need diesel motors
Show text messages to and has login failed as
Actually we don't really need to do all that all that we need to do is to redirect
Welcome page what is the URL to the welcome page
/
Welcome
Lights
You can actually redirect to a welcome page
In react using this by saying
Pastry
Bush
A simple as that
Monthly is redirected a different component we don't really need to update the state of the current component so you can even
Coming this stuff out
Let's see what would happen
28 minutes
Dummy
MC login
Text asking if you want to say that your ID and password
Reacting to the welcome page
You might be one we have used this. Probz. History. Bush
When is this
APA coming from and what else can I do this
If I do a search for the atrato history API
You'd go in DS react router
68 yen
BCPS One of the dependencies for react router
Curry
Adding a dependency for react-router-dom
My Little Ponies for the day's react-router
Take a Google in here
You'd have a little bit of
Documentation on what you can do you can get the current location
You can get the parts name and a little bit of stuff you can see all the other methods
Bushmaster
Methods called replace you can actually go forward go back
And all that stuff
Give me actual documentation of the escape the best place to go is this
Ski package
Take you click this link
What year
It would take you to the action
Peachtree package
Documentation
And you can see that this is
JavaScript library witches
Meant to be used to manage session history
Yeah I guess it has to be updated on Monday this picture of the kind of place where you using this API
You're going to be able to manage
The navigation
What's normal but also for Native applications
Natasha president in the history of object
So let's go Little Big Town
I need to go to the navigation
You can see that a different methods chapter sent history.
He plays go go back go forward
And all that stuff
Push is to go to this / don't want to do this
Could go to the homepage
The other thing you can do with the push method is also add some state
So I would want to go this
Go to this
Thing at this stage of this object as the state
You can also do a sweetheart go - want to go back
The same thing you can achieve by using
I recommend you to spend some time with the documentation to understand
Biggest ABA a little bit more
I'll see you in the next