Welcome back in the previous steps we added the form elements and the
Add them up to the state of the component
Intercept let's focus on the login button click
Wendy login button is clicked you'd want to
Take action we want to check whether the username and password is right
And bass on it
Ida show
Login successful message
How do we do that
Let's see that this person step
It's tied with creating a raunchy event
Is it on change event or intimidated video on take you inside to unclick
I'm sick of the button I would want to call a method to this.
Healthy login
Chuggington
SMS message important things is to make sure that we buying the title this
Talk login sleep
Is equal to
Start running slightly behind.
Now we have the login click
This. State
If everything I said fine
Logan
I can see the username and password at school so busy
Username and password I just want to be able to shoot two different messages let's look at them right now so let's say
Play I would want to show a message which is
Invalid
Credentials
I want to be able to show it is
Login
Successful
To decide the two messages that viewed want to be able to show based on
The username and password entered
If you go to the phone right now you can actually see both of them but what we want to do is conditionally show them we don't want to shoot
Always do you want to show them in specific scenarios how do we do that
Turn off to keep things simple you don't start with hard-coded validation with the only value
Valid
User username and password combination is in 28 minutes
So what we want to do is if
Username
Is equal to
In 2023 is equal to in job use equal to sin
Username
Dummy
Attend
Password
Is equal to
If this too high right where are the username and password present-day Pleasant inside this
Right to the action current values of the username and password at Pleasanton
Miss. State is Desert State. Username is equal in 28 minutes and this. Stay. Password is
Sequel to dummy what do we want to do
Successful
Cancel. Log
That's coming out the slog
Enough when I click login
Faith because in 28 minutes and
Empty password I will enter dummy
You can see that I entered tamiyasu value login
Athletes Training that way
The internet minutes dummy
When I say login password and say login
Validation in here
What do you want to do if you want to trigger these messages based on it
To be able to figure these messages bails donate what you need to do if you need to add this to the state
So what I do is add a couple of more variables to the state to ease
Class login feed
Initially to defaults
And
The last one is show
Texas message
And I put it to
Pulse Aspen what should we do when Logan Street
If
This is the
Back here if you need to do is we need to update this date site so what
What should we do in the state of Texas
Can we just visit India desert set state
What should I do check this message
Should have a value of
Else what should we do
But I should show d
Error message
Has login failed
East
So what are you doing is based on weather DC
Tinga successful or not we are actually sitting this status actually what I can also do is actually here
Alright let's see what happened now
If I go to the page and click login
I still see body messages why did conditions around this yet
I said only valid credentials and login successful conditions yet
Add conditions around this one of the easiest ways to add conditions is betting function
Valid
Credentials
Henry Bastrop Street
Actually I should create this outside the company until it's good
Mu outside and say functions of invalid credentials and brought what we do in here is
If
Throw ups
What we do is win but has login failed as a property to this specific thing to what I can do is promise
What's. Login failed if
Indus Pacific property
If
Has login failed
It's true then what we Louis Vuitton
This credentials back
Kitten invalid credentials
Otherwise return
I don't need two semicolons to insert this I want to use
Show invalid credentials
Actually I can tag in here directly and helped create a proper
Booty call
Pass login failed
And I'll pick the value for it
From this day to this. State
. has login failed
Suisun Valley pet insurance only if has login failed is true I can take a similar message for the other thing
Because I'd like to check if this is working
Gmail messages not being shown
And if I entered right user ID and password
Delete messages not being shown if I enter invalid ID and password you can see that the invalid credentials is
Because the added now he's conditioned is hemolytic Edition solution only
If
Has login failed in the state has a value of
You can possibly get in here and try and do something very similar with long and successful
Function component
Show
Login
Texas
Message
Crocs
And what we can do is if
.
Will do the same thing that we had earlier
True success message
Return
This thing which is presenting here login successful message
How do I Sweeten
Now I can use this so successful
Show login text message
Wikia
Let me get this light enough I can see
And show success message
I want to get it from this date
Is equal to
This. State.
Trusox is message and closing sentences
And that's cool now I can remove all this stuff
Logging right values login successful
Invalid credentials
What we look that is actually implementing the logic for the login button so
We added deontic event
And we actually added
Messages based on whether they had couldn't attend station that we are performing
Successful
Or not
We talked about a lot