Welcome
Let's start making the screens look better we have a few pages enough
It starts
Choosing
CSS to make them better videos of rainbow call bootstraps bootstraps is one of the most popular UI Frameworks
Pistachio pages
Peaches
We have the basic
Define since his baby have everything Define
We need to have a header and footer I to what I lose
Glass
Component
Extended Stay
Hand-lettered this one
Play the role of a head.
Englander what should I do
I just need to return
It's pretty simple live
Andre turn that back
So let's say a diff
Heather
Alex
Have a hedgehog
As a separate.
That's cool
Liposuction Utah food component
I just copy paste this
Toyota company
It's have DHR old horizontal first and then
I'm going to use the header and footer component on the page how can I do that
Do I can do that is inside a router here include
And after the switch
I would include
Photo
Component
Etsy
Please have a header and footer you have the body and the photo
Let's go to the login page
And if I say
Dummy and login
And here you can see that the header and footer remain static
Our body of the Gage keeps changing body and we have a list of to do steps
Awesome pillow start adding in bootstrap
Exercise for bootstrap the first link will take you to the homepage of bootstrap whatever is one of the most popular flavor
Books to style your pictures
All the great things about bootstrappers once you use bootstrap properly
Yep web pages would look good on the mobiles
Aspen
Cookie is bootstrap properly you'd be building responsive websites
What are the options that we have to get bootstrap into our project is to a dependency on bootstrap
And I'll actually plans
What I would touch base bootstrap 4 on package
Becky just want to be content delivery Networks
So what we'll do is we'll get bootstrap directly from there to search for bootstrap 4 and package it would take you through
One of these links
And CSS and
Take booty Batman. CSS
Capriccio
David want to import that CSS into our project
Using bootstrap across the app
I would actually created directly in the source folder
Pekingese
Bootstrap
Accident
Youth small be
WhatsApp.
And what I do in here is import
Dcss
Trump
What I'm doing is I'm taking to you Island on importing it down here
What are also do within the app. GS
I would even put
Bootstrap dirtiest in addition to be a. CSS
Hello
Including
Bootstrap
Start
CSS
SMS receive
Can you go to the to the application
Eutsey
That's d
Biggest much better formatted right now so if you go to login
You'll see that there is a little bit more space between the elements different sizes and it'll be good all that is coming
Because of
Bootstrap select a dummy login
Thank you
They just look a little better than what they were
But still I get to make proper use of the word September let's make use
Of the bootstrap
Remove and quantity header footer and also make sure that dipygus look
I see you in the next step